Chapter 4: HP vs Remus Lupin (Pt 1)

Seventh Horcrux

Ch. 4: Harry Potter vs. Remus Lupin (Pt. 1)

I was concerned about my Horcruxes. If a Weasley was capable of stealing one of them, then they weren't nearly as safe as I had presumed. My first instinct was to gather up my poor soul pieces and never again let them out of my sight. Unfortunately, after many hours of deliberation, I decided that I couldn't risk hiding five Dark artifacts under my bed, at least not with Dumbledore's keen eyes always upon me. Watching.

Yet, after destroying Diary, I was left with only four Horcruxes, two less than I'd originally intended. For my own peace of mind, I would have to create a new one. Now, I just needed to find someone I wanted to kill.

That shouldn't be too hard. Used to happen all the time.

I skimmed the Prophet, whose title proclaimed the escape of Sirius Black.

"My right hand man, hm. You think I'd remember something like that."

I shrugged. I'd certainly forgotten more important things over the past twelve years. Besides, the Blacks were a Dark family, so of course he was one of mine.

It was a pity to lose him. After all, not every minion could escape from Azkaban. That's the sort of talent that can conquer a nation.

I almost regretted abandoning my previous activities. But not quite.

"Dementors!" I ranted. "What could possibly convince Dumbledore to bring dementors into the school?"

Hermione said, "It's just to keep us safe from Sirius Black, Harry."

"Right, right, of course it is. They're protecting us from an emaciated, wandless convict who might want to kill some of us by hiring a hundred Dark creatures that definitely want to eat all of our souls. However did I forget?"

Dementors are terrifying. I might have cut up and scattered my soul, but I assure you, I'm quite attached to it.

I really needed to make that Horcrux. Surely no one would miss a Weasley or two?

"The grim!" Trelawney cried, skeletal hands fluttering around her mouth. "You're in grave danger, Mr. Potter. Very grave danger."

"I'm always in grave danger," I said. It wasn't like I sought out these things, precisely. It's more that getting what I want often involves dangerous situations, and I happen to be immortal.

"You could die," she insisted.

One of the Gryffindor girls, probably Lavender, shrieked.

I snorted. "Not likely."

"I've heard you do this every year," Hermione snapped. "Tell some poor student they're going to die and scare them. But they never do."

"Come to think of it," I mumbled. "Why don't you ever predict the deaths that actually occur? Like the Perks girl."

Hermione sighed. "Harry, Sally-Anne moved."

"Yes, that's what they told us," I said, patting her reassuringly on the arm. "Of course, most of those deaths are First or Second Years, who naturally wouldn't have your class. I imagine you wouldn't even see them except in the Great Hall…Wait, is that why you never come to meals?"

"I…" Trelawney was taken aback at my insight. "Yes, I'm afraid that's true. A prophecy, once spoken, can never be averted you know. And it's such a terrible thing to see those poor, doomed children. Now, back to your teacups, everyone. I can sense your third eyes fluttering shut!"

"We don't have Dark Magic!" Ron yelped.

I suppressed an exasperated sigh. "Ron, all pure-blood families have Dark Magic. If you don't know about yours, it's because your family doesn't trust you."

Horror filled his Weasley eyes. "Why wouldn't they trust me?"

"You're the sixth son, Ron. That's easily three more sons than they need. They won't tell you a thing until you've proven yourself worthy."

He leaned forward, desperate to learn more. "How do I do that?"

I thought for a moment. "Have you tried asking? That would show that you're smart enough to know about these things."

Ron grinned, clapping me on the back. "Thanks, mate. You're the best."

A Howler chased Ron out of the Great Hall, spitting smoke and screeching.

"HOW DARE YOU ASK US ABOUT DARK MAGIC! JUST WHAT EXACTLY ARE YOU DOING IN THAT SCHOOL, RONALD BILIUS WEASLEY? WHY, I SHOULD…"

I bit into a piece of bacon, contemplating the very public response. A brilliant ploy. The Weasley matriarch was cunning, indeed.

"Can we go back inside, now?" I whined.

"No," Ron said.

He had forced me to attend a Quidditch match because I owed him for the Howler incident. The intricacies of maintaining a friendship never ceased to baffle me. I'd usually not bother with such things. However, the boy's loyalty depended upon his delusion that he was my "best mate," and it would take months to break in a new Weasley.

I groaned. "But it's pouring rain!"

"So what? You're not even wet."

Hermione asked, "Why is that, anyway?"

"I'm Harry Potter," I said.

"That doesn't mean any-"

"Oh, look, the game's starting."

Hermione fell into a disgruntled but obedient silence while the players zipped about in the rain.

Quidditch, such a ridiculous game. It's entirely reliant upon the skill of the seeker, unless one team is ridiculously outmatched, in which case the seeker is superfluous.

Furthermore, the Quidditch games' points are far too tied into the House Cup, which irked me greatly during my first time as a student. There I was answering questions, acing tests, charming professors, and earning loads of points, only for one clumsy seeker to ruin our chances of winning.

I do not lose.

Therefore, I convinced the Ravenclaw and Slytherin seekers to sit on the field for a week while their chasers racked up so many points that one of our Houses would win even if the teachers blatantly cheated in favor of the others. That was the first year I won the House Cup for Slytherin and the reason that Hogwarts games are no longer allowed to last more than three days.

Pleased at my victory over foolishness, I'd cheerfully gone back to ignoring the sport.

"This is boring," I said.

Ron's face wrinkled with the effort of thinking. "What do you mean? Didn't you see that dive by Spinnet?"

"Yes, yes, I'm sure it was very nice. I didn't notice because it is pouring rain. It's also freezing out here."

Hermione asked, "Didn't you cast a warming charm?"

"Of course I cast a warming charm."

"I did, too," she said slowly. "So why is it so cold?"

I peered through the thick rain and the mist of my icy breath until I finally spotted the cloak of a dementor. I could feel misery creeping into my already frustrated mind, turning the world even dimmer than it already was.

Dementors both cause and feed off of unhappiness. Trying to dredge up happiness in their fog is insanely difficult and bound to work for only a fleeting period.

It's far easier to grow angry. How dare they make you sad!

That way, they'll focus on your depressed companions while leaving you alone. If you haven't escaped by the time everyone else is eaten, you deserve death.

Unfortunately, blinding fury is not conducive to good decision-making.

"Wow, Harry, I can't believe you charged a dementor!" Ron said.

At the same time, Hermione said, "I can't believe you would do something so stupid!"

"Dementors have no natural predators, so they have no idea how to react to aggression," I said. Admittedly, this hadn't occurred to me at the time, but it certainly explained the creature's terrified flight.

"It's a good thing Professor Lupin cast a Patronus before you got hurt," Hermione continued.

"I could've taken it."

Only thirteen years old and Hermione Granger was already planning her first genocide. While I admired her precocious cruelty – I hadn't even dreamed of such things until I was at least sixteen – I just had to ask…

"Hermione, why do you hate house-elves so much?"

She poked her head out from under the couch where she'd been hiding a malformed mitten. "I'm sorry?"

"I'm not judging," I hastily assured her, "just curious."

"Harry, I don't hate house-elves," she said. There was no particular reason for her to lie. It was nearly midnight, and the common room was empty of eavesdroppers.

"I'm not sure why else you'd be doing that," I said, gesturing towards the hat she'd stuffed under a table leg.

Hermione stood up proudly and proclaimed, "I'm trying to free them!"

I blinked, attempting to make sense of her logic. "…You do realize that house-elves die when you free them, right?"

Impressive actress that she was, Hermione flipped from cheerful to threatening tears in an instant. "W-what?"

"I mean, I sort of thought you knew," I said. "Free elves just lie down and die. They don't eat or sleep..."

I'd seen it happen once, and, let me tell you, it was hilarious.

She sniffled. "I, um, didn't know. I went to the library, but there weren't many books talking about them. I suppose one book said not to free elves, but it was also full of t-torture techniques and, oh, it's all so awful!"

She frantically began picking up the knitwear she'd hidden around the room.

I hummed thoughtfully. "Really, I'm not sure why you thought leaving clothes around would help at all. They do our laundry."

Hermione paused. "I hadn't thought of that."

She looked down at the clothing piled in her arms. "I don't suppose you want a hat or something?"

I chuckled and placed an arm around my minion's shoulder. "Hermione, not even the house-elves want your hats."

My classmates are so boring.

Our latest Defense teacher had acquired a boggart – a creature capable of showing one's greatest fear. But what did it show? The murder of their loved ones? The destruction of all they held dear? My own impressive self, either as Lord Voldemort or Harry Potter?

No, of course not. That would be entertaining. Instead, I had to suffer through ten straight minutes of acromantulas.

Lupin frowned as Ron's boggart skidded past on roller skates. "Another spider?"

"One killed our last Defense professor," Hermione informed him.

"It also petrified several students," I added.

Lupin said, "Acromantulas can't do that."

"It was enchanted by Salazar Slytherin," I said as the boggart morphed into a slightly taller, longer-fanged version of its previous form.

Acromantulas really aren't that frightening. It wouldn't have even succeeded in slaying Lockhart if I hadn't hit him with a tripping jinx at a crucial moment.

Therefore, I decided to add a little interest to the proceedings by revealing my own boggart.

Honestly, I wasn't certain what form the creature would take. Oh, sure, I had reasonable concerns, such as having my soul consumed by a dementor. Still, none of them would send me into a panic. Even death seemed less daunting after I'd successfully conquered it.

I stepped forward, shoving Lupin aside when he tried to block my path.

The boggart leapt at me, its black legs turning blue and melding into robes. White fangs lengthened into a beard, and the creature's two remaining eyes twinkled.

"Dumbledore," I hissed, raising my wand.

He chuckled, a sickening sound. "Dear boy, did you really think I wouldn't notice?"

I froze. "What?"

"You're just the same as the Dark Lord was at your age."

I shrank away, insisting, "No. You're wrong."

"Riddiculus!" Lupin said when he noticed my panic.

A dozen tiny bows appeared in Dumbledore's beard. A few of my more simple-minded classmates started giggling. But I wasn't so naïve. He had worn his beard in a similar manner during my first raid of Diagon Alley.

"I would have to be a fool not to see it," Dumbledore said, "and I think we both know I'm not the fool I seem to be."

"R-riddiculus!" I cried. His robes turned to a pink dress, the frilly hem resting above his wrinkled, hairy knees. But, no, that's exactly the sort of thing he would wear, hoping to catch his enemies off guard.

He smiled with false benevolence. "Don't we, T–?"

"RIDDICULUS!"

The boggart fell, eyes dull and maggots crawling from his beard. I laughed hysterically.

"He's dead," I gasped. "Oh, thank Merlin, he's finally dead."

The boggart darted over to Hermione next, turning to a skeletal house-elf wearing nothing but a pair of poorly-knitted mittens.

I sat in front of Dumbledore's desk, eyeing the various knickknacks surrounding me and wondering how many were secretly weapons. Though the headmaster seemed as serene as ever, I'm fairly certain his phoenix was glaring at me.

"Lemon drop, Harry?" Dumbledore asked.

"No thank you, sir," I said, unwilling to consume its still-unknown poison.

"Do you know why you're here?"

My hand twitched towards my wand as I stifled the urge to flee. "No, I have no idea."

"Ah" – his eyes began twinkling menacingly – "I was just speaking with Professor Lupin –"

"I have an idea, now," I blurted out. He had finally put the pieces together.

I rambled on, "It's the boggart, isn't it? Well, let me tell you, I am not afraid of you. That would be incredibly ridiculous since you are so obviously a kind, completely genuine protector of the Light. Practically a grandfather to me."

"Really? I had no idea you thought so well of me," Dumbledore asked, leaning forward.

I nodded and tried to look very thirteen, possibly younger. "Oh yes! I'm thinking that my greatest fear is really of terrifyingly powerful wizards who know where I sleep. You're more a metaphor for that."

"I would think Voldemort would be a more fitting example," Dumbledore said.

"Yes, well, I don't know what he looks like," I said. "Also, I'm pretty sure he's dead."

"I only wish I were so certain," he sighed.

"What do you mean, sir?" I squeaked. I was doomed.

"On the night Voldemort was vanquished, I'm afraid he didn't die. In fact, I believe he came to Hogwarts two years ago."

Five steps to the door. Dumbledore was old and his reflexes weren't the best. I could probably make it, so long as the phoenix didn't go after me. If I ducked around a corner long enough to put on the invisibility cloak, I would probably be alright.

He said, "You seem nervous, Harry."

"I, um, don't like being called into a teacher's office?" I said.

If I started running now, I could probably catch him by surprise. Unless that was what he expected me to do. Curse him and his elaborate traps…

"I think I understand what your greatest fear is," he said gravely. "You believe that you're like Voldemort. Don't you?"

"Uh…" I wasn't sure what facial expression would be appropriate for the occasion, but I was fairly certain that the terror currently overwhelming my features was not a good choice.

The old wizard chuckled. "Allow me to set your mind at ease. You are nothing like Lord Voldemort."

I gaped. "Really?"

"He was a cold, cruel child with no friends."

In my defense, I was very devoted to my studies, and Dumbledore is exaggerating. Lots of people liked me. Except for him.

Dumbledore continued, "He would never have gone to protect the Stone or set off into the Forbidden Forest to save his classmates from Slytherin's monster."

Admittedly, I didn't do either of those things, but I certainly wasn't going to tell him that.

"…Also" – his twinkle intensified – "I have it on good authority that he hated Quidditch."

I forced a smile. "Wow, we really are nothing alike. I love Quidditch. If only I wasn't bullocks on a broom, I'd have joined the team by now."

"I'm sure you would have," he chuckled. "Are you certain you don't want a lemon drop?"

"Very. I, um, should probably be getting back to my friends now. Goodbye, Headmaster."

I left as quickly as I could without making it obvious that I was fleeing. Either I had miraculously escaped Dumbledore's suspicion – for now – or he was just toying with me, hinting that he would leave me alone so long as I remained an amiable, Quidditch-obsessed Gryffindor.

I wondered if suffering under whatever Dark Magic Dumbledore possessed would be less painful.

"Harry, what are you still doing up here?" Hermione whispered, nose wrinkled at the heavy perfume and smoke that filled Trelawney's classroom.

"Trying to open my third eye."

The first time around, I'd dismissed Divination as unnecessary. To my great distress, that seemingly unimportant gap in my knowledge led to my downfall, short-lived as it was.

Hermione rolled her eyes. "Don't tell me you're buying into all this tripe. Trelawney is obviously a fraud."

I smiled. Sometimes I forgot how little our group encyclopedia really knew.

"Professor Trelawney," I corrected, mimicking her tone.

Though I teased her about it, I was glad to see this rebellious streak. It proved that she was waking up and seeing authority figures for what they were:

Idiots.

Upon closer observation, I had cast aside my early assumption that Hermione was this generation's Bellatrix. Her obsession with rules, goody-two-shoes personality, intelligence, and hidden cruelty were far more reminiscent of my younger self.

Hermione pursed her lips. "Really, Harry, she hardly counts as a professor. She doesn't teach anything. At least not anything useful. You don't really believe that you're going to die, do you?"

Technically, I already had.

"Of course, not, Hermione," I assured her, squinting into the mists of my crystal ball.

Hermione huffed and stormed out. Her robes billowed behind her as she disappeared into the smoke of Trelawney's poorly ventilated room. She certainly had the theatrics of a Dark Lord.

Perhaps I should use Longbottom for my Horcrux.

He had yet to swear an oath of unending loyalty, and Merlin forbid if the prophecy was correct and I'd picked the wrong child.

It wouldn't be hard to cover up. I could pretend it was a Potions accident or something. Everyone would believe that.

Except, no, much as it pained me to admit it, Longbottom was as integral to Slytherin's House Cup victory as I was. Such a resource should not be wasted frivolously.

"Since I am substituting for Professor Lupin for the seventh time in as many months, I will preemptively inform you that our topic next month will once again be werewolves," Severus said dourly.

"Can't we do something else?" Ron groaned.

"Ten points from Gryffindor for questioning a teacher."

I raised my hand. "I don't suppose we'll learn how to kill them? I feel like I know a lot about werewolves but am ill-equipped to destroy one."

Severus smiled thinly. "Yes, I do believe that will be the topic of our next lesson. Good question, Potter…Twenty points from Gryffindor."

Ron flailed his arms around in confusion, threatening to knock over my inkwell. "But you said it was a good question!"

"Ten more points for disrespect," Severus said, sweeping out of the room. I tried not to look too obviously pleased.

"Snape's a git," Ron said.

I shook my head, sighing. "Well, you can hardly blame him – what with his condition and all…"

"Huh?"

"He's obviously a werewolf," I said.

"Oh, Harry, that's ridiculous," Hermione huffed.

I raised a hand to silence her objections. "No need to cover for him. This is clearly a cry for help."

"You've gotta be kidding me," Seamus Finnegan said. "Snape's a werewolf?"

"Of course he is. That's why he's been teaching about them every time he substitutes. It's all he knows."

"He does seem to know an awful lot about werewolves," Longbottom mumbled, looking a bit green.

The class exploded into discussion, and I made sure to drag Hermione into the hallway before she finally exclaimed, "You don't seriously believe that Professor Snape is a werewolf?!"

"No, Hermione, that would be ridiculous," I said.

"Then why would you say something like that? People are absolutely awful about werewolves. Do you know what that kind of rumor could do to his reputation?"

"Yes, which is why I don't appreciate him trying to out Lupin."

She looked startled. "You know about that?"

"Snape's been teaching about werewolves for months, and Lupin's gone every full moon. I'm not an idiot," I said.

While I was growing concerned about my classmates' mental abilities, the truth is that I suspected Lupin long before his first class absence. You see, several of my minions were werewolves back when I was Lord Voldemort. I know the signs well.

"Oh," Hermione murmured.

"And I'm honestly offended that Snape is so intent upon ruining his colleague's life. Werewolves are perfectly reasonable people, so long as they're taking the proper potion. This rumor will provide a plausible explanation for Snape's actions and help to hide Lupin's secret."

She beamed. "That's very noble –"

"But, mostly, I thought it would be funny," I finished.

Chapter 5: HP vs Remus Lupin (Pt 2)

Seventh Horcrux

Ch. 4: Harry Potter vs. Remus Lupin (Pt. 2)

"We are breaking so many rules right now," Hermione fretted. "Out after curfew, out of bounds, walking around in the Forbidden Forest…"

Ron rolled his eyes. "Don't be such a stick in the mud, Hermione."

"This is a real problem, Ronald!" she cried. "Oh, and that isn't even getting into the morality of this…"

"We're hunting unicorns," I said. "What could possibly be immoral about that?"

"Hunting," she said grimly as we trudged through the forest.

"Well, it's not like we're killing them. Would you feel better if I said we were looking for unicorns?"

She huffed. "I don't know why we're doing this in the first place."

I heaved a heavy sigh. "We've been over this. Hagrid burned down half of the Forbidden Forest a couple of years ago with his evil dragon. That means we're twice as likely to find unicorns."

"But why?"

I abruptly stopped walking. Ron oafishly bumped into me, possibly because I was once again using my invisibility cloak as a regular cloak. I stared at my favorite minion. "Are you telling me you don't want a unicorn? Dear Merlin, Hermione, what kind of little girl are you? Do you even have a soul?"

She seemed unsure of how to respond, descending into sullen silence. I grinned as we continued our walk through the forest. "Now, let's go over the plan. Ron, you'll be bait."

"I don't think I like being bait," Ron said, glancing at the shadows in search of man-eating spiders.

"It's only a unicorn. Don't be a Hufflepuff," I said.

Attempting to lend some degree of comfort, I reached over to pat him on the shoulder. He shrieked. Ah right, my arm was still invisible because of the cloak. I'd take it off, but it was bound to wear down before graduation, so I hoped to get some use from it while I still could.

"Can't Hermione be bait?" Ron whined.

"No, unicorns only come to the pure of heart. She doesn't have a soul, remember?"

"Don't be ridiculous," Hermione snapped. "Really, why is having a unicorn so important, anyway?"

I sighed and reminded myself once again that my companions were still very young and naïve. "One day, Hermione, you're going to wake up and realize that you're nothing but an angry old man lashing out at everyone who reminds you of how miserable you are. And you'll think to yourself: If only I had seen just one beautiful thing. If only I could have found proof that the world wasn't entirely horrible and corrupt. If only I had seen a unicorn."

"…Okay, we can look for unicorns," Hermione mumbled.

I beamed, slinging a still-invisible arm around her shoulder. "I knew you would see things my way. Now, all we have to do is –"

"Stop!" a voice shouted from behind us. "Don't go any farther."

I cursed as Professor Lupin jogged over to us. The werewolf had followed us into the forest. At this rate, we would never find a unicorn.

"I told you we shouldn't do this," Hermione hissed.

"Oh, we'll be fine." I'd have disappeared under my cloak and continued the search, but I didn't trust Hermione to cover for me. Besides, I couldn't leave without my unicorn bait.

Lupin said, "I've finally found you. Now, where's Miss Weasley?"

"Ron's right over there," I said, pointing at him with an invisible arm.

"Hey, I'm not a girl!" Ron shouted at Lupin.

"Yeah!" I agreed.

Lupin chuckled. "I do know that, Mr. Weasley. I was talking about your younger sister. I assume she's hiding somewhere among the trees?"

I snorted and said, "Professor, we're trying to capture a unicorn. We can't afford to be slowed down by some Second Year girl who probably still plays with dolls and puts flowers in her hair."

Things were progressing slowly enough with two third years.

"She's been missing for a few hours now," Lupin said thoughtfully. "And she was last spotted leaving the castle. None of the portraits saw her come back in."

I shrugged. That didn't seem too odd for her, considering the whole Chamber of Secrets incident. "She's probably performing some sort of Dark ritual. It is the night of the full moon, after all."

Lupin suddenly became very pale. "Oh Merlin. It is."

"Professor," Hermione said slowly. "You didn't forget to take your potion today…Did you?"

"I –"

Ron yelped, "You don't think Snape's out here?"

"He probably is," I said. "Right now, he's prowling through the forest, mad with animalistic rage…Werewolves are well known for their thirst for virgin blood. Your sister is likely lost to us."

Hermione said, "First of all, werewolves don't drink blood: That's vampires. Second of all, that virgin thing is a myth. Third of all, the moon isn't even out as it's still cloudy. Finally –"

Hermione was interrupted when Lupin rasped, "Run."

He was hunched over, fur sprouting from the back of his hands. Loud cracking sounds echoed through the forest, and Hermione's eyes widened.

"Professor, are you okay?"

"Forget about me. I didn't take Wolfsbane. You're all in danger," he said – though I could hardly hear the words amid his growls. His face appeared to be twisting into a snout.

Ron said, "You mean Lupin was the werewolf the whole time?!"

"Obviously," I said. "Really, Snape spent several classes talking about them. You think you'd know the signs by now."

"But you said –"

"Ron, you really ought to know not to take me at my word. Don't you remember how I promised to feed Scabbers when you were in the Hospital Wing last year?"

In my defense, the rat did survive, and its recently declining health was almost certainly not my fault.

There was a girlish shriek – probably Ron – then a loud growl. Ah, yes, the ravenous werewolf. I'd forgotten.

I grabbed Hermione's hand and started running. What? I might be an incredibly powerful wizard, but I'm no Lockhart.

The werewolf pursued us, snapping at our cloaks and leaving deep gashes in the forest floor.

I cursed. I couldn't find a unicorn, I was in the middle of the woods, and a professor was trying to eat me…Come to think of it, this was a lot like the first time I went through Third Year.

Through some small fortune, the moon provided enough light to navigate through the trees. Hermione still occasionally stumbled on a shadowed root, but my steadying hand kept her on her feet. I found myself wishing that the werewolf would trip over one as well and give us a head start to escape.

I then realized that I was thinking like a Hufflepuff and cast a Tripping Jinx.

As usual, my quick-thinking had saved our lives. We emerged from the forest shortly afterwards and hid in Hagrid's abandoned hut. I barricaded the door with one of his comically-oversized chairs and a plank that was propped beside it for the purpose. Then, I added several locking and strengthening spells because I'm not a squib.

Hermione collapsed against the wall, still breathing heavily from our dash. I wasn't doing too well myself. It's unfortunate how academic mindedness may lead one to neglect their physical strength.

"Well, thankfully that's over," I said.

"Y-yeah," Hermione murmured.

"This actually went fairly well. We were only caught sneaking out because of the Weasley girl…"

Hermione's eyes widened as she contemplated the girl's grisly demise. "Wait a –"

"…We managed to defeat a werewolf, which is pretty impressive for three Third Years…"

"Harry –"

"…Sure, we didn't find a unicorn, but that was clearly Ron's fault" – I paused –"Galloping gargoyles, we forgot Ron! Hermione, why didn't you inform me of this?"

"I tried to –"

"Enough of your excuses," I said. "You've once again recklessly endangered our friend through your horrible apathy."

I bowed my head. It was a pity. I'd liked Ron…or at least he'd liked me. Something like that. My disappointment over his loss nearly equaled my disappointment over his failure to attract a unicorn.

"We can still save him," Hermione said. She stood up, her eyes gleaming with Gryffindor determination.

"No, Hermione. It's too late to go back for him now. He's already dead. And he wouldn't want us to tarnish his sacrifice by getting eaten by werewolves."

She bit her lip, seeming to argue with herself for a moment before pulling something from beneath her cloak. I couldn't see in the dim light of the derelict hut, so I cast Lumos. A small hourglass dangled at the end of a chain.

I gaped in a very Weasley fashion. "Hermione, why do you have a time turner? Are you a Department of Mysteries spy?"

That would explain everything. Hermione was always unsettlingly mature and had never blended in with real children. She understood magic in a primarily academic sense, as if she'd learned it already. She was an adept liar, as I'd learned early on in our friendship. Finally, it couldn't be a coincidence that she'd ended up in the same year and house as the famous Harry Potter, even though she was clearly a Ravenclaw.

Hermione frowned. "No, of course not. I got it from McGonagall so that I could take all the electives."

"Hold on, you're telling me that – if you take two extra classes – the school will give you power over time? Why don't they advertise these things?" I grumbled.

"I wasn't supposed to tell anyone, and I think it was sort of a special allowance for me," Hermione said.

"That makes it worse!"

Hermione rolled her eyes but knew better than to argue when I was obviously correct. She walked over and gestured for me to take hold of the time turner.

With a well-practiced hand, she turned the hourglass twice and we fell into the past.

I landed on my back. It seemed that I would have to get used to magical travel all over again. As I waited for my head to stop spinning, I stared up at the ceiling of Hagrid's dilapidated hut. There was a hole in it already, I noted, which was odd considering it had only been empty for a year. Perhaps the groundskeeper's home shared the castle's dramatic tendencies.

The sky was tinted orange and pink with the setting sun, and warm sunlight fell across my face from a dingy window.

"Why is the sun setting?" I asked.

Hermione bit her lip as she glanced down and said carefully, "We went back in time. You do remember, don't you? You didn't hit your –"

"I am aware that we traveled through time. I am not an idiot," I said. "Just how far back did you take us?"

"Three hours," Hermione said.

I sat up abruptly. "Why?"

"We have to plan of course." She sniffed haughtily, reaching out a hand to help me up.

I attempted to stand on my own, fell, and repeated the process until I was shakily on my feet. "What's to plan? We grab Ron and run away."

"Harry! We can't face down a werewolf without proper preparation," she chided as we made our way to the door. It was locked, so Hermione cast Alohomora. We left the door slightly open as we walked towards the forest.

"We don't have to, though. It'll be too busy trying to eat us."

"I…what?"

"Past us, Hermione, keep up." I sighed. Was no one my intellectual equal?

"But it won't be chasing us for more than a few minutes…" Hermione said.

"Yes, that's why we run. We've already been over this. But stop distracting from the issue: You took us three hours back in time, which means that I'm three hours older and three hours closer to death…You're killing me, Hermione, just as you killed Ron," I finished with a smirk.

She smacked me on the arm, snapping, "I did not kill Ron!"

"No, that won't happen for three hours," I said. "Also, his killer is technically Lupin."

"He's not going to die," Hermione said. "We're saving him."

"Can I come?"

I whirled around in surprise as the Weasley girl stood behind us.

"I'm sorry?" Hermione squeaked, stuffing her time turner under her robes.

The Weasley's chin tilted defiantly. "You traveled back in time to save Ron from Professor Lupin's werewolf form, and I want to help."

"How did you know that?!" I demanded. "Are you using Legilimency right now? Hermione, don't look at her eyes."

The redhead frowned, brow wrinkling in a very Weasley confusion. "Uh, no, I just heard you talking. You do realize that your invisibility cloak doesn't shield sound, right?"

"No, it unfortunately does not," I sighed, glancing down at my beloved cloak – or at least the space where I was pretty sure it was, since it was invisible at the moment.

"So, can I come then?" she asked brightly.

"We are short a Weasley…" I said. "I don't suppose you know your family's Dark Magic?"

Her eyes shone fervently. "No, but I think I'm getting close."

"Good, you're doing better than Ron, then." That made sense considering she was their only daughter and the seventh child. Seven is a magical number. There's no point having seven children if you aren't going to empower the last of them.

Hermione stood gaping at us.

"I'm in then?"

I hummed thoughtfully. "How's your stunner?"

"I don't know that spell," she admitted.

"Then you'll be a reasonable substitute for Ron," I assured her.

Hermione had successfully recovered from her earlier shock. Her voice was flat. "Your parents actually told you they have Dark Magic."

The Weasley girl shrugged. "Not exactly, though they leave some pretty obvious hints. I don't think I would have caught on if a friend of mine hadn't told me about it."

"Was that friend Harry?" Hermione asked with a skeptical eyebrow buried beneath her enormous hair.

"It wasn't me," I said.

"It wasn't him," she agreed.

"Then who was it?"

The redhead blushed brightly, stuttering, "I-It was an older boy. He graduated. You wouldn't know him."

"See, Hermione, even the upperclassmen agree with me," I said.

She sighed, rolling her eyes. The Weasley girl asked, "So, what do we do now?"

"I suppose we can look for unicorns again…"

"Well, that was a dismal failure," I grumbled as we walked through the forest towards the spot where Lupin attacked us. "I told you we needed Ron."

"Sorry, Harry," the youngest Weasley said.

"Consider yourself begrudgingly forgiven," I said magnanimously.

"It wasn't all bad though, was it?" she continued. "I still can't believe that your first reaction to seeing a grim is to hex it!"

"Yes," I said. "That was pretty great."

"Oh, I hope we're not too late. That meadow was awfully far out, and it wasn't even bathed in moonlight. So I'm not certain what the point even" – Hermione gasped – "That's us! Hide, we can't let them see us."

She crouched among the shrubbery while the Weasley and I stood and watched through the trees.

"…in the Hospital Wing last year?" one of the figures finished arrogantly – probably Hermione.

I raised my wand and incanted, "Accio Weasley."

The Weasley girl fell against me with a startled shriek, and Ron flew backwards, occasionally hitting a tree. He skidded to a halt a foot in front of me. In the distance, Hermione and I fled from Lupin.

Ron stared up at us stupidly. "Harry?"

"Obviously," I said. "Were you expecting a unicorn?"

He laughed weakly. "Oh, good, for a second there I'd thought you guys had just left me there."

I said, "Ron, we would never do that. You are our dearest friend, and, frankly, I think worse of you for saying something so disloyal."

Hermione flung her arms around him and began sniffling against his shoulder.

I scowled. "See, you've upset Hermione."

He turned towards our substitute Weasley. "Wait, how'd you get here?"

"She's been with us for three hours. Pay attention."

"I have," the youngest Weasley agreed.

Ron's face twisted in confusion. "But –"

"Enough of this. We have to get out of here before the werewolf comes back."

I think we all felt a little better once we entered the castle and our odds of being maimed fell to their usual, slightly less alarming level.

Ron grinned. "Glad that's over."

"Yes," I said. "Though we never did find that unicorn."

"I said I was sorry about that," the Weasley girl muttered with a tone worryingly close to rebellion.

Ron slung an arm around Hermione's shoulders. "See? We didn't even get in trouble."

It was at that moment that Severus descended from the shadows beneath the staircase, eyes gleaming. He always was overdramatic. "My, my, what have we here? Has the lost little lion decided to grace us with her presence? Oh, and of course you're in the thick of this, Potter."

He gestured towards me with a sweep of his black-robed arm.

Hermione immediately came up with a cover story. "You have to understand, Professor, we were just worried about Ginny –"

"So you decided to go after her yourselves, rather than let the professors handle the situation. Twenty points for typical Gryffindor foolishness."

"In retrospect, it was a bad idea," she said hurriedly, "but we did find her before anyone else."

"And then Lupin found us," I said. "Sir, I'm not sure if you were aware of this, but it turns out he was the werewolf all along. He tried to eat us."

Severus was clearly pleased. He said, "Continue."

"He forgot to take his Wolfsbane because he is an idiot. Fortunately, I cast a Tripping Jinx and threw him off balance."

Severus spoke approvingly. "Attacking his feet. It seems you were paying attention after all. For applying your class knowledge to a real life situation…Thirty points to Slytherin."

"Hey, you can't…" – I paused – "Did you just say Slytherin?"

Severus quirked an eyebrow and drawled, "I'm on to you, Potter."

Dumbledore sighed heavily. "I'm very disappointed in you, Harry."

He had once again summoned me to his office, but this time it seemed I was actually in trouble. I kept my eyes downcast so that he couldn't steal my thoughts. Come to think of it, I really needed to learn Occlumency at some point…and I still hadn't made that Horcrux.

Seeing that I wasn't going to answer, Dumbledore continued, "Why did you tell everyone about Professor Lupin's condition? Surely, you realized how much trouble that would cause him."

"I didn't tell everyone," I muttered. "I only told Snape. Though I admittedly should have suspected he couldn't be trusted with sensitive information considering he couldn't even keep his own lycanthropy secret."

"Professor Snape is not a werewolf," he said with a grandfatherly smile.

"No, I'm quite certain he is," I insisted. "He told me so himself. I asked if he'd been attacked by a werewolf, and he said yes."

Dumbledore coughed, no doubt trying to hide his shock at my brilliant deductions. "That aside, I have it on good authority that you announced Professor Lupin's secret to the Gryffindor Common Room."

"That's not my fault. They were asking where I'd been. What was I supposed to do: Lie? Lie, like a dirty Slytherin?"

Dumbledore accepted the insult without comment, which I assure you he never would have done when I was still Tom Riddle. "You still did not need to ruin a good man's reputation."

I stared at him incredulously. Usually, I would have meekly agreed and hoped to escape Dumbledore's wrath for one more day. However, he was acting even more insane than he usually pretended to be. "Headmaster, he turns into a ravenous monster that attacks students."

I had done many terrible things in my two lives, but I'd never accidently murdered children.

Dumbledore shook his head wearily. "You have to understand that he would normally never harm a student. So long as he takes his Wolfsbane –"

"But he didn't take it," I pointed out. "How do you even forget something like that?"

"It was a very stressful night. Miss Weasley had just gone missing, and with Sirius Black still on the loose…"

"You can't just panic every time a student goes missing!" I cried. "We would never get anything done, if we did that. We still haven't found those two Hufflepuffs."

I personally suspected the dementors.

"Be that as it may," Dumbledore said. "It was not your secret to tell. You could have spoken to me or Professor McGonagall."

"Right, because the staff handles murderous professors so well," I grumbled. "That's why the Ministry stopped Hagrid's reign of terror, and I had to take down Quirrel."

Admittedly, both of them were entirely innocent, but Dumbledore didn't know that.

"Perhaps I've been too lenient." Dumbledore suddenly looked very old. One of these days, he was going to die, and I would finally be safe.

"So, can I go now?" I asked. "I think some of the other Gryffindors are having a pick-up game of Quidditch on the grounds."

He said, "One last thing, try not to stray too far from your Aunt's house this summer. Sirius Black is still on the loose, after all."

I nodded.

Dumbledore waved me away with a strained smile. "Enjoy your Quidditch."

I burst into the Gryffindor common room and approached my best minions.

"Ron," I barked. "I need you to organize a Quidditch game."

Ron jumped up from the couch, like a proper minion. He then ruined the effect by questioning me. "But I thought you hated Quidditch."

"This is a matter of vital importance."

"What could possibly be important about Quidditch?" Hermione asked.

"Dumbledore," I said, voice flat.

Ron scratched his head thoughtfully. "I guess I can get Dean, Seamus, and Neville. Ginny's always up for a game. The twins would usually be, too, but they're pretty focused on catching some master prankster, right now."

Hermione raised an eyebrow and asked, "Master prankster?"

Ron gestured towards the wall, where Fred and George were analyzing a tapestry with a variety of spells. "Yeah, apparently somebody tossed them into the wall last night. Percy got hit, too."

"I'm surprised no one did this earlier" – I sniffed disdainfully – "They're completely insufferable."

"Harry," Hermione said, "you do realize that was you, right?"

"What?"

"Last night, when you waved your wand and said 'accio Weasley…'"

She mimed the motion with her wand, and Ron fell into her with a startled squeak. Meanwhile, the twins stumbled and looked around the room with narrowed eyes. Hermione hastily lowered her arm, mumbling, "I probably shouldn't gesture with my wand."

"Don't be a Muggle, Hermione," I said, "and, Ron, assemble our Quidditch team. I've had enough of your procrastination."

"It was then that Lupin's fur exploded outwards, his skin bursting and bloody underneath…"

I had to shout to be heard above the excited chattering of my fellow students. The Great Hall was always cacophonous during the End of the Year Feast, and Gryffindors have painfully short attention spans.

I said, "…Lupin got Ron, but we valiantly saved his life."

Ron frowned. "Mate, you've got to stop saying it like that. People are going to think I'm a werewolf."

"Ron, our classmates aren't idiots. That rumor will go away after a couple of moons. Now, what was I saying?"

"Lupin was maiming Ron," one of my classmates said helpfully.

"Yes, thank you. I hit it with a stinging hex as a distraction. This gave Hermione and I time to grab Ron and run. The werewolf followed, of course, but a well-aimed curse knocked it off its feet."

"Where was Ginny?" Longbottom asked.

I looked across the table where the Weasley girl was gazing dreamily at me. "Wait, is that your name?"

"Yes," she said.

I snorted. "That's a house-elf name."

"It's short for Ginevra," she reassured me.

"Oh, that makes more sense," I said. "Yes, well, it turns out that Ginevra had fallen asleep by the groundskeeper's haunted hut, and we found her on the way out. Without our help, she surely would have died."

Dumbledore's voice echoed through the Hall. "It's once again time to award the House Cup. This year's totals are: Gryffindor, two hundred points; Hufflepuff, three-hundred and thirty points; Ravenclaw, four hundred and thirteen points; and Slytherin, five hundred points. Congratulations, Slytherin."

Dumbledore gestured so that the banners changed to Slytherin green and silver. I clapped along with the rest of the Slytherins, earning unhappy looks from my Gryffindor housemates. The only thing that saved me from a tirade was my heavy frown. This victory was a bitter one.

"This is terrible," I declared. "We lost to Hufflepuff. What is wrong with you people?"

It was not the first time in my life that two hundred people simultaneously glared at me, but it was the first occasion I can recall that was not preceded by murder.

I stared out of the Hogwarts Express's window. While I had absolutely no intention of joining Ron and Ginevra's game of exploding snap, the loud banging made it impossible to read any of the tomes I'd stolen from the library.

That didn't keep Hermione from her latest book, of course. Nothing ever does. Therefore, we were all surprised when, with a frustrated huff, she shut it and exclaimed, "I just don't understand!"

"Wait, there's something the Great Hermione Granger doesn't understand?" Ron said, clutching his chest in mock horror.

Ginevra giggled. "Impossible."

"I believe that's a sign of the apocalypse," I said gravely.

Hermione shot us an annoyed look. "Stop being ridiculous. I was just thinking about the, um…"

With a nervous glance at Ron, she said, "…the you-know-what that helped me get to class on time."

"It's called a time turner, Hermione," I said.

Hermione stood up angrily, once again trying to use her height advantage against me. "I know what it's called! I just wasn't supposed to tell anyone else, and you promised to be discreet…"

"Hermione, I never promised that." I was quite certain of it. I avoid promises on principle – notably the principle of not being held accountable for things.

"I still wasn't supposed to tell anyone," Hermione mumbled.

I dismissed the Weasley kneeling on the train car floor with a flick of my wand. "It's not like he has any idea what we're talking about."

"What's a time spinner?" Ron asked.

"See? Completely clueless," I assured her. "You were saying?"

Hermione sat back down, though with more of a thud than was strictly necessary. "It's just this whole business with Lupin. We had to use the turner to save Ron from Lupin. But Lupin only forgot his potion because he was looking for Ginny. But Ginny was only missing because we took her with us to save Ron. So…how did it all start?"

I chuckled. "Oh, Hermione. This is time travel. These things never start. They just happen."

"That doesn't make any sense," she said flatly.

"Sure it does. You just haven't spent enough time in the magical world yet," I reassured her.

"Wait, you guys time traveled?" Ron yelped. "Was that what happened?"

It was really no surprise that Ginevra was making better progress in acquiring her family's Dark Magic. Ron simply had no cunning. "Yes, Hermione time travels to attend all her classes."

"Not anymore," Hermione quickly said. "I've given up Divination and Muggle Studies – they were useless anyway – and returned the time turner to Professor McGonagall."

My jaw dropped in a very Weasley fashion. "You returned the time turner? But Hermione, we had the power to bend time to our will. We could have done so many things."

"That's why I returned it," Hermione said primly.

Traitorous, selfish, and unrepentantly evil…Yes, she was exactly like me at that age.

A/N: Just a quick reminder that the full fic (with periodic omake updates) is available on SpaceBattles and linked in my profile. This version has gone through some minor edits, but I'm mostly posting here so that it has a more permanent (and less forum-y) position.

Chapter 9: HP vs Alastor Moody (Pt 4)

Seventh Horcrux

Chapter 5: Harry Potter vs. Alastor Moody (Pt. 4)

I fell retching on the grass, dropping the Cup as I tried to recover from the clearly shoddy portkey. A quick survey of my surroundings revealed that I was nowhere near Hogwarts.

That was a problem, since I would be unable to properly bask in my victory. Additionally, there was a Death Eater standing beside a gaping cauldron and pointing his wand at me. That was also a problem.

I rolled to avoid a hex, jumping to my feet and aiming my wand at my opponent. I smirked as I realized which of my followers was currently failing to kill me. I would know that hair anywhere. "Lucius. Who are you working for?"

Lucius immediately confirmed my suspicions because he is an idiot. "What makes you think I'm working for anyone, Potter?"

I snorted. "As if you could pull something like this off on your own."

"I could absolutely –"

A rasping voice suddenly interrupted him. "Don't argue with the boy, Lucius. When you lose, that will reflect poorly on me."

I scowled. "Who just said that?"

A guttural chuckle came from behind my former minion, and the voice said, "Turn around. I'd like to do this face-to-face."

Lucius turned around, awkwardly holding his arm so that his wand still faced me. With his free hand, he parted his luxurious, blond hair. I always knew he was hiding something in there, but I never could have imagined the truth. A second face – wrinkly and purpled – looked out from the back of his head.

It said, "Harry Potter. Kidnapped and held at wandpoint after what should have been your greatest triumph…This would be so much more poetic if you were in your Third Year."

I asked, "What do you know about Third Year? And just who are you, anyway?"

The face's mouth curled into a thin, sickly smile. "I am Lord Voldemort."

"What?! That's impossible," I said. Because it was completely impossible, unless another Horcrux had gone rogue.

"Did you truly think I was dead?" he asked. "Did you think you'd actually killed me?"

"I…" – I paused, deciding that information-gathering was the best tactic for the moment – "Yes, and I'm not sure I believe you. If you haven't been dead, then where have you been all these years?"

The face scowled. "Ah, yes. It's a fascinating tale. You see, after the destruction of my body, I was sent hurtling towards the forests of Albania, screaming the entire way. THREE HOURS OF SCREAMING."

"Really? You'd think you would stop after the first hour, when it started to become normal."

He rudely ignored me. "I wandered Albania as a wraith, until a bumbling professor stumbled upon me. I possessed him and snuck into Hogwarts right under the old fool's nose – hoping to steal the Philosopher's Stone. With it, I planned to regain my body. Unfortunately, my host died before I could acquire it because you murdered him."

I nearly dropped my wand in shock. "Quirrel? You were possessing Quirrel?"

"Yes," he said.

"But Quirrel was a horrible Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher! Why didn't you help him?"

"Why would I train Dumbledore's future soldiers? If he wants me to do that, he'll have to hire me, like all the other professors…After Quirrel's death, I wandered the Forbidden Forest, again without a clear plan. Yet, one day, I saw something that inspired me to take action."

"Was it a unicorn?" I asked.

"No, it was a grim. It raced through the forest as if in fear of its life. Suddenly, I remembered that I didn't become immortal so that I could spend an eternity as a wraith. I became immortal because…actually, I don't recall why."

I do. It was the only way I could survive Hogwarts long enough to graduate. Then I found out that seven was a magical number, and, by the time I got over my Arithmancy phase, I'd already made four and it seemed stupid to stop there.

He continued, "Regardless, I realized that it was pointless to wait for followers who would never come. I would simply have to find one so spineless that I could intimidate him while I had neither a body nor any magical power."

"So you went to Malfoy," I murmured, nodding. It was all beginning to make sense.

He snorted. "I presume you've dealt with him before?"

"The younger one, mostly," I said.

"Yes, the clone. He was very helpful in keeping me in touch with my spy at Hogwarts…in order to arrange our meeting here today."

Curse Severus and his unwavering loyalty. I glared. "So it was you, then, who's been sabotaging me all this time. I should have known the judges would never be so biased without some malicious, external influence."

The face was silent for a moment, likely marveling at my astounding intelligence, before saying, "Yes, of course I did. All…all part of my plan. I am the Dark Lord, after all. And it's far past time that I returned to my former glory. Lucius! Begin the ritual."

A curtain of blond hair once again hid the hideous face as Lucius bent down to grab a skull, tossing it into the cauldron. "Bone of the father, unknowingly given, you will renew your son…Flesh of the servant, willingly given, you will revive your master."

Lucius placed his wand atop his wrist, murmuring a severing spell. With an unsettling crack, the man's hand fell off and into the cauldron. He turned towards me, and said, "Blood of the enemy, forcibly taken, you will resurrect your foe."

"Since when are we enemies?" I exclaimed, wand still aimed at Lucius.

"We've always been enemies," was the muffled response from beneath Lucius's hair.

"I just met you today," I said.

"You killed me when you were a child."

"Well, yes, but you can hardly blame me for what I did when I was an infant."

"I manage well enough," he said.

"Well, I don't blame myself. Or you. It was just bad luck, really." I wasn't entirely sure what had happened that Halloween night, but I was completely certain it wasn't my fault.

"Lucius, turn around and move your bloody hair," the face snapped. Lucius did so, though he had to drop his wand to manage, since his left hand was currently floating in a cauldron. I presume he didn't want to get blood in his hair.

Again visible, the face continued, "…You killed my host."

"That was an accident," I said.

His voice rose incredulously. "You used the killing curse!"

"The killing part wasn't an accident. But I didn't know he was your host at the time, so it wasn't like I was deliberately defying you." That reminded me; I'd never gotten around to rewriting that list.

"…Well, I consider us enemies," he declared as Lucius again let go of his hair. "You don't have any say in the matter. If you try to argue, I'll kill you."

I rolled my eyes. "Well, fine, if you want to be stubborn about it, then I suppose we're – OW! Galloping Gargoyles, what was that?"

A trail of blood floated from the wound in my shoulder where Lucius had just cut me. It landed in the cauldron with a sizzling sound. Lucius fell to his knees, leaning backwards so that his blond locks were completely submerged in the potion. He screamed as the air around it filled with bright, sparkling light – reminiscent of some of Dumbledore's gaudier robes.

Suddenly, plumes of white smoke floated outwards and Lucius slumped to the side, groaning. His missing hand was still bleeding and, looking closer, I noticed that I could see some bone jutting out at the tip. Worse yet, his hair was soaked and clumpy, bits of bone and flesh weaved into it by the potion – completely ruined. I considered pitying him, but then thought better of it.

Amid the appropriately dramatic smoke, a figure rose. He looked intimidating and quite pureblood – tall and aristocratic. Further, he appeared hypnotically inhuman and serpentine, with no nose and red eyes. He looked like…me.

There was no doubt, now. Lord Voldemort had returned…even though he…I was already here. I would have to think on this later. "I suppose you truly are the Dark Lord."

"Of course," he said.

"So, your plan is…?"

"Kill Dumbledore, take over Britain, figure out the rest later," he said easily. "Would you like to join me?"

"I thought you said we were enemies!" I said.

He shrugged. "Yes, well, that was just for the ritual."

"Granted, I'd have done the same," I admitted. "But are you certain that deciding we aren't enemies won't nullify the ritual? It might cause your body to fall apart, which seems like a waste after all the work Lucius has done."

"I don't…think that would happen," Voldemort said slowly.

"Are you sure? Did you actually research this, or did you find a summary in a book and decide it sounded like a good idea?"

Voldemort didn't respond. I sighed. It was as if I…I mean he never learns.

He watched me keenly, remarking, "You know, I've realized something about you. You're exactly as I was at your age: cunning, curious, distant from your peers, capable of spells far beyond your classmates. Exactly the same."

I should have known he would catch on. He's me, after all, and I'm not an idiot Gryffindor, head-in-the-clouds Ravenclaw or average Hufflepuff. No, I'm far smarter than that.

"I know your secret, Potter" – he smirked – "You are like me. You're…a genius."

"Finally, someone notices!" I exclaimed. "Honestly, I get O's in every subject without even trying, except for potions – but that's because Snape is blatantly a Death Eater."

"Ah, yes. Severus, my most loyal servant," he murmured. "On that topic, I suppose it's time that my wayward followers know of my return."

He bent down, pulling something from Lucius's robe pocket. It was my old yew wand, which I'd had such fun with. I cast my first Avada Kedavra with that wand, you know. I grinned at the memories.

My other self seemed similarly pleased as he pressed the wand against Lucius's Dark Mark, jostling his injury at the same time. A whispered spell sent another pained shudder through the blond.

Voldemort stood, head tilted arrogantly and eyes cold.

"So, how long do you think they'll be?" I asked.

Voldemort shrugged, "Ten minutes? They've never been particularly punctual, and I just don't think they fear me as much as they will in about fifteen minutes."

I nodded, wandering over to Lucius, who had managed to pull himself into a sitting position. He stared blankly at his stump. His voice shook. "My hand, my lord?"

Voldemort blinked. "Oh, right."

With a negligent wave of our wand, Voldemort conjured a silver hand for the injured man. Another wave chopped off his hair, leaving him completely bald and vanishing his greatest accomplishment.

"Never let it be said that I am not a generous master," Voldemort declared pompously.

I absentmindedly healed my own wound.

It was about that time that the Death Eaters apparated in, sometimes coming in pairs. Each received a cold welcome. The last to come was over three minutes later than all the others. He arrived panting.

"You're late," Voldemort said, eyes narrowed.

"Dumbledore was being difficult," a familiar voice drawled. "Apparently the Potter boy has gone missing. Again."

Voldemort smiled in a manner that would have been more reassuring if he'd had lips. "Ah, Severus! I didn't recognize you with your mask on."

He turned towards the rest of the group. "It seems that my devoted subjects have all arrived. I cannot help wondering why none of you thought to search for your master during his long absence. Instead, you turned your backs upon me and spurned all that I taught you. Only Severus remained loyal."

Voldemort continued on for some time – ranting, crucioing, begrudgingly granting forgiveness…the usual.

"What's the Potter boy doing here, then?" one of them finally asked.

He received a bout of the Cruciatius, just for the principle of the thing, before Voldemort explained. "We were just about to duel to the death."

I blinked. "Weren't you trying to recruit me?"

"Yes, but you said no, so now I'm going to kill you. Dear Merlin, Potter, keep up."

"I'm not fighting you," I said. I didn't particularly want to kill myself, and he was probably protected by the Horcruxes, anyway. So I couldn't even kill him properly. Besides, I just put in so much effort to resurrect him. I bled.

Voldemort scowled, and a flick of his hand sent the Death Eaters hurrying to circle us and block my escape. "You don't get a choice in this."

"Fine," I grunted. I would play along, for the moment.

We bowed, raised our wands, and began. "Avada Kedavra!"

The following fight can best be described as very green. Avada Kedavras flew wildly through the air. His were weaker than mine as he was still cheerful after gaining a new body while I was carrying a grudge over his sabotaging my time in the tournament.

We effortlessly dodged each other's spells. But they found targets easily enough.

One by one, Death Eaters fell. A few realized what was going on. Lucius, for instance, was using Crabbe as a human shield. Yet their numbers kept thinning.

Voldemort's spells took out more of his people than mine did, which was surprising because I was actually aiming.

Eventually, I maneuvered myself close to a wide gap in the ring of my former and apparently current followers. With one last Avada Kedavra in Voldemort's direction, I sprinted away, headed towards the graveyard's gates.

However, I took a small detour to grab the Cup because it was mine. As I snatched its handle, something tugged at my navel and the world began to spin, eventually solidifying into the familiar grounds of Hogwarts.

Greeted by the surprised faces of my teachers and classmates, I knew immediately that I had to tell them. After all, I knew something incredibly important, something that mattered. I could not allow them to wallow in ignorance for a moment longer.

I held my trophy aloft and shouted, "I declare victory!"

"But, if you didn't manufacture the whole thing, then why was Snape there?" I asked.

Dumbledore frowned, studying the whirring gadgets on his desk for a moment before coming to a decision. "Professor Snape has been a loyal spy for the Light over a great many years, Harry."

That was quite possibly the most ridiculous thing I had ever heard. Still, I suppose even Dumbledore can occasionally overlook the obvious. Or perhaps he was simply trying to convince me of Severus's loyalty – playing the long game, as always.

He gave me a stern look. "I hope you're wise enough to not endanger him by telling anyone."

"No one would believe me, anyway," I said. "And, frankly, I don't believe you. What are the chances that I was just coincidentally kidnapped before my victory was properly recognized? It was obviously part of the tournament."

In retrospect, Dumbledore's involvement explained everything: why the Cup was a portkey, Severus's presence, the supposed Lord Voldemort's lapses into idiocy and his very existence.

Dumbledore leaned forward inquisitively. "Harry, what could I possibly gain from faking the return of Voldemort?"

The man was obviously toying with me. Fine, I would play his game.

"You could further your fame and power by giving the people of Britain a great enemy against which they can only unite under one leader: Yourself. Further, you can finally regain the respect you lost when you failed to kill him the first time."

"I have plenty of power, already," Dumbledore said.

I scowled. "Which just makes it all the more despicable."

He paused, before speaking rather slowly. "I assure you, I have no interest in furthering my political power. Even if that weren't the case, I dare say this would not be the best plan. Why reveal him in such a roundabout manner? It would be better to revive him in front of a large audience, not a lone boy."

He made a reasonable point. "There's still the possibility of –"

"Mr. Potter, I have already – at your insistence – checked you for hallucinogens and confunding spells. Whatever you saw, I've no doubt it was real."

Yet it was that possibility which I was so desperate to dismiss. After all, if Voldemort was cavorting about the English countryside with whatever followers had survived our duel, then who was I?

Worse yet, he seemed to have added me to the list of those who have wronged him, and I have never been a merciful man.

"…This might be a problem," I concluded.

Dumbledore chuckled. "I find that very likely."

For the first time in her life, Hermione Granger did not wish to go to the library. She trailed behind Ron and me, glancing back towards the Great Hall. Her hair was even more frazzled than usual as she anxiously tugged at it. "The service starts in ten minutes. If we hurry, we can still make it in time."

"I'm not going to the stupid Slytherin memorial service," I said.

She scowled. "It's not stupid, and you really should go and pay your respects."

"You assume that I respect any of the Slytherin's parents…Come to think of it, I'm pretty sure I've never met most of them. Or any of them."

It's so difficult to keep track of these things.

"Well, yes, but" – Hermione's voice dropped to a whisper – "it is you fault, after all, so you really ought to at least try to be graceful about it."

Ron wrinkled his nose, asking, "Whaddaya mean? Didn't they all die of dragon pox?"

She rolled her eyes. "Yes, and the epidemic just happened to have only affected Pureblood Slytherins."

"Well, to be fair, they don't talk to anyone else," I said.

"And dragon pox is very rarely deadly. Besides, we both heard your story. You really think it's a coincidence that several Death Eaters were killed by Voldemort, and a myriad of Slytherins die the same day?"

She made a good point, but admitting that would mean losing the argument. So I immediately discarded the notion.

"Are you implying that all Slytherins are Death Eaters? I expect this sort of bigotry from Ron, but I thought you were better than that." I shook my head with exaggerated sadness.

She huffed. "Even if it wasn't your fault, you still shouldn't be so rude. Nearly everyone's going, and so should we."

"No one's stopping you. It's not like we need to be together all the time." Although we usually were anyway.

"I…" – Hermione paused for a moment, realizing that I hadn't been insulting her this time – "Well, fine then. Come on, Ron."

"But I don't want to go see all the dead Slytherins," Ron whined.

She grabbed his arm, dragging him along. Ron didn't stand a chance against Hermione in a fight (she's far too ruthless) but he could have at least tried. It would have been funny.

I continued towards the library and the knowledge held within its looming stacks. It was time to do what I should have done fifty years ago…or any time afterwards:

Research Horcruxes.

Fortunately, Madame Pince was one of Gilderoy Lockhart's many admirers. Though my pass to the Restricted Section was nearly two years old, my passionate insistence that this was quite likely Lockhart's final wish (outside of not being eaten by an Acromantula) spurred her to allow me access. As an additional bribe, I gave her a signed copy of Sporting with Spiders.

I did not browse the stacks for long before finding the book in which I had originally found out about Horcruxes: Secrets of the Darkest Arts.

I'd only ever seen it once, reading several chapters before reaching the Egyptian section. I'd just begun reading about Horcruxes and automatically memorized the ritual, when the librarian started grumbling about curfew. Unwilling to arouse suspicion, I left the tome in the library.

The next day, I asked some of the professors a few innocuous questions. Before I could return to the book, my access to the Restricted Section had been revoked because I was "meddling in Dark Magic" or something stupid like that. That's how I knew that I was on the right track.

Now that I had finally rediscovered the book, what I found was quite peculiar.

After the usual warning about insanity, a clear ploy to ward off cowards, there were a few stories of Horcrux users:

First, there was my boyhood hero Harpo the Foul – hatcher of basilisks and spell weaver – whose Horcrux was eviscerated when some plucky adventurer tricked his favorite basilisk into biting it. Grimhilda the Widow's Horcrux, her husband's skull, was destroyed during a freak fiendfyre accident. No one's entirely sure what happened to Ignis the Handsome's Horcrux, but no one's seen him lately, so it was presumably destroyed. The last story, however, was most intriguing:

That of a living Horcrux.

Jibade the Black, a distant cousin to the royal family, aspired to be Pharaoh. Recognizing the dangers of such a quest, however, he did what all reasonable wizards do and created a Horcrux. But Jibade was clever. He wanted a Horcrux that could defend itself, one with an innate will to survive and a hatred of all living things. He chose his cat.

Unfortunately for Jibade the Black, the cat came to believe that he, too, was Jibade. In the dark of night, the wizard was murdered by that which should have ensured his survival and reduced to an angry spirit. Shortly afterwards, Jibade the Cat was assassinated by his political enemies.

I closed the book, careful to avoid its teeth. This was…unexpected, and it opened all sorts of possibilities in my mind.

It was true that I had been planning to make a Horcrux that night, and I had committed more than enough murders to fracture my soul. Was it possible that – with my body destroyed by something that was undoubtedly the Potters' fault – my damaged soul had flown in different directions? One part had gone off to be pathetic in Albania, while the better part had settled inside young Harry Potter.

Essentially, I was the vengeful cat. Thankfully, I was also the political enemy…Well, along with Dumbledore, the Weasleys, most of the Ministry of Magic –

"Quite a book you've got there, Potter," Moody said. Right, yes, him too.

I chuckled nervously. "It fell off the shelf, but I'm afraid to touch it because it's very Dark."

Moody smiled in a deeply disturbing manner, as he always does. "That's a pity. For a moment there, you almost had my respect."

I stood from my chair. "What?"

"Petrificus Totalus."

I ducked under the table, scrambling on my hands and knees away from my deranged professor.

"Not bad, Potter. Practicing constant vigilance, are you? Won't help much."

"Dumbledore sent you; didn't he?" I spat.

It all made sense. With the return of Lord Voldemort, Dumbledore had realized the same thing I had: I was Voldemort's Horcrux. He had arrogantly believed that he could control young "Harry Potter," but both of us? No, we were too dangerous. So he decided to kill me, then take out my lesser self.

Moody threw a spell at the table I'd hidden under, collapsing it. "Wrong side, kid."

I rolled to my feet and cast a Protego. "Hah! Like Mad-Eye Moody would ever be a Death Eater. Stop protecting your master."

Moody laughed, mismatched eyes never leaving my face. Then, with the dramatic timing that just doesn't exist in the Muggle World, his skin began to ripple. His peg-leg clattered to the floor, and he pocketed the fake eye. With the face of a different man, he smirked.

My eyes widened. "Of course, I knew it all along. The whole time, you were actually – Wait who are you?"

"Barty Crouch, Jr." – at my blank look, he added – "A Death Eater."

"Right, that makes sense. In fact, everything makes sense now. You were the one who was sabotaging me in the tournament all along."

He frowned. "Actually – "

"Voldemort already admitted it."

"Guess I wasn't in on the plan," the Death Eater muttered.

I snorted. "Like Voldemort would share any of his plans with a mere pawn."

The man who had recently stopped being Moody growled, throwing a spell that dispersed against my shield. "I am not a pawn! I am one of his best Death Eaters, and I am his most loyal servant no matter what he says about Snape or Sirius Bla – "

He stopped shouting, then, because he was too busy being on fire. I wandered towards his twitching, flaming body and stole his wand. "This wouldn't have happened if you'd practiced constant vigilance."

I returned Secrets of the Darkest Arts to its shelf, and wandered back to the main library. Madame Pince was slumped across her desk. Apparently she was as practiced at sleeping through Death Eater attacks as I was. I nonchalantly headed towards the entrance. It was about that time that Dumbledore and Severus showed up because of course it was.

I put on my best innocent expression. "Oh, Professors, I'm so glad you're here. Moody's a Death Eater and tried to kill me, but, thankfully, I killed him first…with love."

Gazing out of the train's window, I smirked. This year had turned out alright after all. I won the Triwizard Tournament, I won against Voldemort, I won the House Cup –

"And I won your friendship," Ginevra said.

I glanced away from the window, now frowning at the seat where Ginevra and Luna Lovegood sat. The redhead smiled apologetically, murmuring, "You were thinking aloud again."

My frown lessened. "Any progress on discovering your family's Dark Magic?"

"Well, not much so far. I've been at school, so there haven't been many chances."

"That's never stopped Hermione."

"Hermione doesn't do Dark Magic…"Ron said weakly. "Right, 'Mione?"

The aforementioned girl didn't respond, too caught up with her latest information-gathering mission. I cast an overpowered lumos to draw her attention (the underage restrictions didn't take effect until we left the train). "So, which Dark Lord are you studying, now?"

Hermione said flatly, "You."

"What?" She'd finally figured it out. I should have known she would. Why had I not better prepared for this day?

"She means Lord Voldemort," Luna said.

"What?" Two of them. Could I obliviate them both subtly enough to avoid suspicion? No, no, I was terrible at obliviations. That was why I usually just murdered witnesses. It was easier.

Luna pursed her lips. "That is what the cover says, unless the wrackspurts are playing tricks again."

The blonde riffled around in her bag, drawing out a pair of winged glasses.

"No, Luna, no unidentified and possibly nonexistent creatures are muddying your senses. I'm reading about Lord Voldemort."

I spoke. "But you said –"

"I was teasing, Harry. Although you're in here, too, and I am reading about you."

"Why?" I asked, still feeling justifiably suspicious.

She sighed. "You've told us that Voldemort is alive, so I'm studying the way he died the first time. Hopefully, we can make it happen again."

Ginevra asked, "But shouldn't the adults be handling this?"

"I used to think so, too, but we always end up doing these things anyway. I figure we're better off being proactive."

Ginevra's brow twisted, puzzled. "Don't you think that teachers and other adults are always right?"

Hermione said, "Well, I did back in first year, but then I was attacked by a mountain troll. It's all been a bit shaky from there."

Ginevra paled, wailing "Oh, I got my interpretation of you all wrong!"

Luna rested a comforting hand on her shoulder, though her bespectacled gaze never left a spot slightly above Hermione's head.

"So, have you figured out how to beat him, then? Voldemort, I mean," Ron asked.

Hermione shook her head. "It's not that simple. I've noticed something odd, though, about the night that he was vanquished."

"By me," I added.

"Yes, well it certainly wasn't the wrackspurts," she snapped.

Luna said, "You don't know that for sure. You're just assuming."

"She does that a lot," I said.

Ginevra sniffled. "At least I got that part right."

Hermione said, "As I was saying. Why would Voldemort go alone to attack the Potters? Usually, he would send his followers to do that sort of thing, while he only went on raids in public places – like Diagon Alley."

"He's crazy. Why did he do anything?" Ron said.

"Yes, of course he was crazy, but he's a very specific sort of crazy. This doesn't fit it. He likes to grandstand, to look impressive. He never seems to hurt people without an audience. So why didn't he just send Bellatrix Lestrange or Lucius Malfoy?"

"The Malfoys are idiots," I said, "Lucius would have just mucked it up."

She set down her book, too agitated to keep her hands still. "Mucked what up? What was the plan? Why the Potters?"

"The Prophecy," I muttered.

"What was that?"

I said, "There was a prophecy, about the Potter child – me – and Lord Voldemort."

"How'd you find out about that?" Ginevra asked.

"Snape told me." Technically, that was true.

"What did it say?" Ron asked.

"I don't know," I said, for quite possibly the first time in my life.

"Why didn't you tell us this before?" Hermione asked.

"Because I don't know what it says. Honestly, I expect this sort of thing from Ron, not you."

Hermione huffed. "Well, why don't you find out, then? It's right there in the Department of Mysteries."

Of course Hermione would know that. No surprise, considering her previous occupation.

"Oh. Well, I suppose we'll be taking a trip to the Ministry" – I stood to leave – "Have a good summer, and I'll call upon you when the time is right."

"Harry," Ginevra said.

"What is it now?" I snapped.

"You do realize that we're not at the station yet, right?"

"…I am perfectly aware of that at this moment, yes."

Luna turned her head towards me, squinting behind the colorful glass. "It's probably the wrackspurts. Does anyone have a butterfly net?"

A/N: With Pettigrew eaten by a grim, I wondered how Voldemort would reach his canon position. Lost, I turned to my brother, asking him, "What would Voldemort do without Pettigrew to revive him?"

He responded, "What would Harry do? Mooch off the Malfoys."

And so it was.

Chapter 11: HP vs Dolores Umbridge (Pt 1)

Seventh Horcrux

Harry Potter vs. Dolores Umbridge (Pt. 1)

I was two months into my latest attempt at brewing Felix Felicis when my home fell on its side.

"Gah!" I cried, vanishing the potion from my robes and the floor before it starting eating its way through again. I got up, unlatched the entryway, and crawled onto the floor outside.

"What is the meaning of this?" I said, staggering to my feet.

Hermione didn't even look up from her book. "Your trunk fell off the shelf."

I hastily took in my surroundings. Hermione sat primly on a seat, reading this year's Charms textbook. Meanwhile, Ron, Ginevra, Luna, and Longbottom were playing a particularly volatile game of Exploding Snap. "…We're on the train."

"Of course we are," Ginevra said.

"Why didn't anyone inform me that we were returning to Hogwarts?" I snapped.

Luna crawled away from the game, peering into my trunk curiously.

Ron said, "We couldn't get in to tell you. You locked us out."

"Of course I did. You kept trying to steal me from my bed." I waved my hands around in frustration.

Hermione flipped a page in her book. "To protect you."

"And I locked it in order to protect myself from you." I accioed my wand, sick of gesturing like a Muggle.

"You don't have a Floo in there. How were we supposed to get you?" Ron said.

"Have you ever heard of knocking?"

Luna looked in my general direction. "Do you mind if I go inside?"

"Yes, go ahead." I waved my wand dismissively.

Ron gaped. "What? She's allowed to go inside but we're not?"

"She has yet to attempt my kidnapping," I said.

Ginevra beamed up from her continued game with Longbottom. "I haven't tried to kidnap you yet, Harry."

"Yes, I just don't want you in my home," I said.

Longbottom opened his mouth, glanced at the wand still in my hand, and shut it again.

"I don't think I would like living in here very much," Luna called from my trunk. "It's not very cozy, and it's rather cold."

"Heat disrupts the brewing process."

I glared at Hermione because this latest incident was almost certainly the result of her vengeance. "…which reminds me. You ruined three months of work."

She groaned. "You're not seriously trying to make Felix Felicis again?"

"I've figured out the secret to making the most potent batch in existence," I declared.

Hermione pursed her lips. "You'll be lucky if you can make it at all. That's a very advanced potion, Harry. Most Potions Masters can't even brew it."

"Exactly."

"Excuse me?"

"It takes incredible luck for anyone to successfully brew it. I suspect that luck is actually an ingredient. The insane amount of luck necessary for me to do it would therefore add to the quality of the potion. In fact, it may actually be stealing my luck for later use, thus leading to my many failures."

"Harry," Hermione said, "that's stupid and –"

"–just the sort of thing that magic does!" Ginevra cried.

"She's got you there, 'Mione," Ron said.

Longbottom mumbled, "Makes more sense than Potions usually does."

Ginevra sat up, an uncomfortably large portion of her face taken over by a smile. "You should tell Snape about this. It might completely change potion making or at least make the class slightly less boring."

"No, that seems like a bad idea. Snape doesn't like me." Also, more people who are not me would have access to liquid luck, which would be terrible.

"I guess I could tell him for you, if you wanted," she said.

I condescendingly tapped her on the head with my wand, snatching it back when she leaned into the touch. If I wasn't careful, I'd have another Bellatrix on my hands. "Let me rephrase that. Snape hates all of us."

Luna's voice drifted out of my trunk. "Harry?"

I amended my previous statement. "Except for Luna. I don't know how he treats Ravenclaws."

"Only slightly better than Hufflepuffs," Ginevra chirped.

Luna's voice was fainter this time. "Harry? I'm lost."

Hermione nervously stroked her wand, muttering, "Harry, why do you have a shield charm up?"

I glanced around the Great Hall. There were no eavesdroppers, at the moment, aside from Ginevra. "Put yours up. Ron, hide behind Hermione. Ginevra, hide behind Ron."

Obstinate as ever, all three cast separate shields. I growled in annoyance. Hermione frowned. "No, seriously. Why are we doing this?"

"They're watching."

"Who're they?" Ginevra asked, voice dropping to match mine.

"The other students. I think they're preparing an attack." It wouldn't be the first time.

Hermione dropped her charm and said, "They're just curious."

"I sense anger, and I very rarely get that one wrong." I glared at an errant Hufflepuff who had the gall to glare back. They were rebelling, just as I always knew they would.

"Well, I guess some of them might be riled up by the papers. They've been pretty bad about you lately, what with Dumbledore saying You-Know-Who's back," Ron said.

I raised an eyebrow. "And I was not informed of this because…?"

Hermione said, "In a trunk. Besides, Rita Skeeter –"

"Wait, didn't we kill her?!" I exclaimed.

Hermione winced. "No, Harry. We didn't kill her."

"No, no. I remember this specifically. You were trying to starve her to death, and I said that was too evil. We were going to take her out some other way, though. Just what have you been doing all summer?"

An obnoxious Gryffindor said, "A murderer, too! Wait until my Ma hears about this. Of course, we all knew you were a crazy, attention-seeking liar."

Hermione pursed her lips thoughtfully. "Harry is all of those things. But rarely at the same time."

"Also, he's my best mate," Ron said. "It doesn't matter how true your insults are; I'm hexing you for having a go at him."

"I'll help," Ginevra squealed.

I raised a hand. "Down, Weasleys. I can handle this."

They reluctantly acquiesced. I stared at the Gryffindor through my shimmering shield charm. "Tell me, have I ever been quoted as saying that Lord Voldemort is back? Have you ever seen me say that? Am I saying it now?"

He appeared confused. "So you're saying he isn't, then?"

I chuckled. "Well, I wouldn't go that far. I certainly saw some snake-like man burst from a cauldron. However, I cannot say with certainty that he was Voldemort. I've never even seen a photograph of the man."

"There aren't many of them around, and they're almost never in the history books," Hermione said.

Ron snorted. "Not surprising, is it? It's bloody creepy when he smiles and waves at you."

I've always loved having my picture taken.

The Gryffindor cleared his throat. "But Dumbledore said that you said that Voldemort was back."

"Dumbledore is clearly trying to manipulate you all. I am neutral on the Voldemort issue. Tell all of your friends."

The Gryffindor, still looking dazed, wandered off.

Ron nodded, standing tall as though he had just chased the boy away single-handedly. Hermione said, "That should quiet some of the louder Gryffindors."

I quirked an eyebrow.

"You were in your trunk," Ginevra said.

I sighed. "Trust Dumbledore to sabotage my reputation."

The redhead tapped her chin thoughtfully. "Well, he hasn't done a very good job. The Gryffindors are mostly behind you, already. The Hufflepuffs think you're lying. But you insult them in public, so you never stood a chance there. The Ravenclaws who are lucid enough to understand what's going on are reserving judgment. And the Slytherins believe you because Voldemort killed most of their parents."

I hummed thoughtfully. "Yes, I suppose we have that in common."

I stared at my folded hands, Dumbledore's phoenix burning my face as it crept ever-closer. "Sir, I think your bird is hissing at me."

"Because he likes you, my boy," Dumbledore said.

The phoenix slowly backed away. A quick glance showed that its beady, black eyes still watched my every move. "You said the same thing about Snape."

"They're both rather unconventional in showing their fondness," he said.

I've often wondered if Dumbledore was attempting to orchestrate my death through negligence.

Dumbledore steepled his fingers, leaning forward. "Do you know why I called you here today, Harry?"

I spoke very quickly. "Is it because I publically denounced you in front of the entire student body?"

The old man looked surprised for a moment, an obvious act, before coughing. "I may wish to speak of that later, but no. Did you hear about the break in at the Ministry of Magic this summer?"

"No," I said, thinking of the prophecy orb which now served as a make-shift lamp in my trunk. "Why would I know anything about the Ministry? I don't keep up with politics. You should tell me about it."

"The details don't matter," he said. "What you need to understand is that Voldemort broke into the Ministry to steal something very important. Something that concerns you both. A prophecy."

I tried to channel my inner Ron. "We read about those in Divination, I think. Don't they tell the future or something?"

"They do indeed. This prophecy concerns Voldemort and yourself. I heard it many years ago, and it seems that Voldemort now knows it. I believe it is time that you do, as well."

I frowned. "I'm confused. Why am I always the last to know about these things?"

"I was trying to protect your innocence."

How would a normal fifteen-year-old respond to that? Hermione would write a book report. Ron would turn red and start sputtering. Malfoy would go brush his hair or something.

I gave up that line of thought and shrugged because scoffing seemed suspicious.

Smiling, Dumbledore prepared a pensieve and showed me his memory of Trelawney's prophecy.

As I swirled back into the real world, I asked. "Are you sure that this is genuine? This is Trelawney we're talking about here. According to her, I'm supposed to have died six times by now. I know; she usually gives dates."

"I'm quite certain of its validity."

I shivered at the thought of what disturbing rituals Dumbledore had performed to satisfy him of this. I shook myself, turning to brighter topics. "So I have to kill Voldemort, then?"

"Perhaps," Dumbledore said, as noncommittal as ever. "Or perhaps you might defeat him with love."

I snorted. "Fire doesn't kill everything, Headmaster…Wait, I have a brilliant idea."

"Oh, yes?" he asked.

I widened my eyes, which I could imagine shining with excitement. "Could you teach me your Dark Magic?"

The phoenix dived for my head.

It was a typical evening in the Gryffindor common room: Hermione was polishing off the tenth page of our five-page Charms essay, Ron was thrashing Longbottom in chess (an accomplishment that was more embarrassing than impressive), and Ginevra was by the fireplace pretending to have other friends.

"Dumbledore won't talk to me," I grumbled. This would usually be a good thing, but I now had no idea what he was plotting.

Hermione rolled her eyes. "Well, maybe you shouldn't have asked him for his Dark Magic."

"I'll admit that might have been rude," I conceded, "but he'd just told me that I had to kill Lord Voldemort. And, really, it's very selfish of him to hoard it. He doesn't even have an heir."

Ron looked up from the chessboard where his knight was busy decapitating Longbottom's queen. He said, "Mate, Dumbledore isn't evil."

"I never said Dumbledore was evil." Implied, yes, but outright stated? Absolutely not, everyone knows the portraits spy for him.

I continued, "Besides, that has nothing to do with this conversation."

Hermione got a queer look on her face and asked, "Harry, just what do you think Dark Magic is?"

I snorted. "Secret magic retained within a family, obviously. That's why they call it Dark Magic. It's kept in the dark where very few people get to see it."

"But I thought it was just evil magic," Ron said. "Like spells that make people's eyes explode and stuff."

"Well, of course it's mostly that. If I invented a spell that made eyeballs explode, I wouldn't tell everyone about it. People would start asking awkward questions like: 'Why would you make something like that?' and 'What's wrong with you?' and 'Are you the person going around exploding people's eyeballs?'

"Then they would start to use it on you, or they'd come up with a counter-curse, ruining the whole point of inventing it in the first place. Actually, that's where most of the spells we learn in class come from. Petrificus Totalus, for instance."

Hermione huffed. "That's ridiculous. Petrificus Totalus is perfectly harmless."

I said, "Oh, sure, it's all good fun now that everyone knows the counter-spell, but no one was laughing when the Parkinsons used it to bury their political enemies alive."

Hermione gasped, hands flying up to cup her mouth and Charms assignment forgotten on her lap. "That's horrible."

"Magic usually is," I said, "but Dark Magic isn't any more evil than the rest. It's just very exclusive."

A light of understanding weakly lit within Ron's Weasley eyes. "So, when you said that my family had Dark Magic…"

"I assumed that during your nine hundred year history, at least one of your ancestors invented a spell and then didn't go out and tell everyone," I said.

"Ginny isn't evil then?" Ron said.

I paused, thinking for a moment. "I'm not sure. Only one way to find out, I suppose."

"Wha-?"

I turned to towards the fireplace and shouted, "Ginevra, Hermione is recruiting for her Dark army. Would you like to join?"

Ginevra appeared thoughtful. "Are you going to join?"

"I haven't decided yet," I admitted.

"Let me know when you do." She nodded decisively and then turned back to her previous conversation.

I said to Ron, "See, she's less evil then Hermione."

"I'm not evil," Hermione said.

I chuckled. "Then we have nothing to worry about."

Ron frowned. "Someone should probly let Dumbledore know that Harry isn't evil, either."

"Hem, hem," Umbridge hem-hemed.

I turned Most Potente Potions to page four hundred and twelve.

"Hem, hem."

A flick of my wand sent three small fires dancing atop my desk. I glanced up disdainfully at her toad-like face. "What is it?"

"Can you tell me, Mr. Potter, why a cauldron is on top of your desk?"

I frowned, adjusting it slightly so that the fires evenly heated its pewter sides. "Felix Felicis is very sensitive to altitudes. This isn't ideal, but it'll have to do."

She pursed her lips so that they looked a bit like a duck's bill. "And why aren't you reading your textbook?"

"I already did that," I said.

"In this class, we read the textbook," she said slowly, smiling as if I couldn't sense her evil intentions.

"Yes, which is why everyone hates your class" – I turned around to the seat behind me – "Right, Hermione?"

"Harry! You can't say things like that to professors."

I turned triumphantly back to Umbridge. "If she didn't hate your class, she would have said that. For instance, she'll never accept that Potions might as well be self-study."

Hermione huffed. "Potions is a perfectly reasonable subject, which requires a teacher to ensure its students' safety."

"See? We all hate your class. I would blame the curriculum, but I don't think we have one of those. You're just a terrible teacher."

Her chest heaved up and down in fury. "How dare you –"

"It's not just me. Snape agrees, and he should know. He's a terrible teacher, too."

Umbridge said, "I have absolutely no interest in the opinions of a half-breed werewolf."

I laughed at her idiocy. "Snape is a full werewolf. There's no such thing as a half werewolf, and you would know that if you knew anything about your subject."

"Detention, Mr. Potter!" she cried.

I glared. "Fine, we'll talk about werewolves. Maybe you'll even learn something."

"But the only way to seal a werewolf bite is with a mixture of powdered silver and dittany. Mind you, it doesn't do much good against –"

Umbridge interrupted, and I was suddenly quite certain that she hadn't been listening at all. "Your detention will be very simple. You will write 'I must not interrupt class.'"

"There wasn't a class to interrupt."

"You will write it as many times as it takes to sink in," she said tightly, pulling out a thin, black quill.

I gestured widely with my wand. "It's sunk in. Can I go?"

"Five hundred lines, then," she said.

I sighed gustily and took the quill.

I was aware that arguing would only irritate her further, a secondary goal, but I knew a blood quill when I saw one. And that complaint had given me just enough time to cast an invisible glove charm, most commonly used by Potions Masters. You see, a blood quill is always attached to the last person whose skin touched it.

In this case, Professor Umbridge.

I smirked and wrote the first line. Umbridge yelped. I wrote the second.

"Mr. Potter!"

I wrote the third, humming merrily under my breath.

"Stop that! Stop that right this instant!" Umbridge shrieked.

I looked up from the parchment, absentmindedly doodling. "What is it, Professor?"

She trembled with rage, clutching her injured hand. "Give me the quill."

I smiled congenially. "Are you bleeding?"

"She's got you in for detention again? I figured you'd have scared her off already," Ron said, lounging in a chair near the common room fireplace.

"Honestly," Hermione huffed. "This wouldn't happen if you didn't keep antagonizing her."

"You think she's terrible, too," I pointed out.

"Yes, but I don't tell her that."

I stared at Hermione, stunned by her selfishness and cowardice. "Then how is she supposed to know?"

Ron said, "She probably already does, mate."

"No, she could not possibly know how awful she is and then do nothing about it. She's worse than Quirrel. She's even worse than Binns! At least he lets us duel in the back of the classroom."

Hermione said, "You can't keep doing that, by the way. It's disrespectful."

"Binns doesn't mind," I said.

She curled her fingers into fists. "He doesn't notice."

I nodded. "Exactly. Binns doesn't stop us from learning. He doesn't encourage it, either, mind you. I've been turning in the same essay every month, and I get the same grade every time."

"That's cheating!" Hermione said, as if she didn't do worse things on a daily basis.

"Binns doesn't think so."

Ron appeared awestruck. "That's brilliant."

Hermione scowled at him, and he hurriedly added, "But you shouldn't do that."

I said, "Why not? We essentially don't have a teacher for that class. I might as well enjoy the advantages. Regardless, Umbridge is actively ruining our ability to learn. You, of all people, should be upset about that. You'll fail your OWLs."

Ginevra giggled in the corner, calling out, "I would pay to see that. It would just be so weird."

Hermione's eyes widened until she resembled a house elf. "You're right. We, we need to do something about this. A study group, maybe. Um, you and Ron will be in it, of course. Neville, too, and I imagine Ginevra will want to join…"

"I do!"

"So that makes five of us," she said, nodding jerkily. "Good. Alright. And the Ravenclaws, too, if they haven't already organized something."

Ginevra said, "They haven't!"

"Alright, good. We'll all arrange a meeting time –"

"And I will lead it," I declared, eyes shining.

This was perfect. If I successfully prepared a class of students for their OWLs, then Dumbledore would have no choice but to give me the DADA position.

"But there's nothing here," Ron said, staring at the blank wall beside the portrait of Barnabus the Barmy and his dancing trolls.

Hermione smirked, head tilted smugly as she began another one of her history lessons. "The Room of Requirement only appears under very specific circumstances, since they tried to seal it several centuries ago, but it's definitely there."

She began walking, Ron trailing behind her. She turned abruptly, bumping into Ron, and – face reddened with exertion – continued her pacing.

I stood still and watched the wall. Recalling the storage room where I'd stashed Ravenclaw's Diadem, I frowned. "How did you find out about this room, again?"

"It's in Hogwarts a History."

Good, no one ever reads that book, so my Horcrux was fairly safe.

Hermione's eyes sparkled. "It's a fascinating story, really. Ravenclaw designed this room a few years after founding the school. It could temporarily summon anything off the grounds, and she often used it when preparing a particularly tricky ritual or spell. Of course, it also became quite popular among the students as a recreation center. But it was too enthralling for some, and a few students never came out. They say you can still find their skeletons, if you ask it for the right thing."

"Hermione, you're really not selling me on this room," I said.

"It doesn't have any sort of enchantment to lure you in. Some people just don't like their lives, I suppose. And I don't have to sell you on it" – a door shimmered into existence – "It will sell itself well enough."

I opened it, peering inside with my wand raised. The arched ceiling rivaled that of the Great Hall, and wheeled dummies darted about one section, occasionally bumping into sturdier targets. At the far end, a podium overlooked the room. To the side, a bookcase jutted out, connected to the wall by a red, velvet curtain.

"Impressive," I said.

"Oh, isn't it?" she sighed, immediately racing to the bookcase.

Ron cast a stunner at one of the dummies, grinning when it flashed bright red and collapsed. "Wicked."

I wandered about, mentally claiming the podium as my property and taking a head off of a dummy. It promptly regrew it. I wondered if I could instruct the room to not let it do that.

I then peered around the curtain. "Oh, look, there's even a bed in here for when the members are injured!"

Hermione squeaked, and a library book thudded against the floor.

I frowned. "Of course, we'll have to get rid of the skeletons first."

The grass whispered across my scales as I slithered away from the mansion. I liked it better there. There were more hiding places. But I couldn't hunt Master's minions. I wasn't allowed.

I hissed as a scuffling sound caught my attention. Venom pooled in my mouth, and I lunged forward –

"Harry?"

I blinked, suddenly aware of the Room of Requirement, which was arranged in its usual position for our study group. Hermione and the other Ravenclaws huddled in the corner, whispering, while the rest of the students practiced their Patronuses. After showing the wand motions, I'd sat this lesson out. That spell simply did not like me.

Neville hovered nearby, ready to bolt at any moment.

"Neville!" I cried, slinging an arm around his shoulder, "Just the man I wanted to see."

"Me?"

"Of course," I said. "You."

"Oh, okay…What do you want?"

I gave the boy a measuring glance. He'd always been pudgy, his timidity had yet to lessen, his classwork was abysmal, and Neville Longbottom was generally pathetic.

Exactly what I required.

"I wish to grant you a great favor," I said. "I will make you the fifth greatest Hogwarts graduate since it was first founded a thousand years ago."

Neville shoved his hands into his pocket, a nervous habit acquired from several years of owning a toad that despised captivity. "Fifth?"

"Well, there's no beating Dumbledore, Voldemort, or myself. And Hermione would probably poison you if you outperformed her."

"Y-you're kidding about this, right?" Neville asked.

"Not at all," I assured him. "I will happily do this for you. All that I ask is that you tell everyone that I was your teacher."

"Alright," he said.

I smirked. "Our training shall begin when you least expect it."

Neville nodded, looking pale. "Um, Hermione sent me to get you. You need to sign the contract…"

I snorted and stalked towards the library. "I don't sign magical contracts. Remind her of that."

Neville looked as if he might speak, for a moment, then scurried away.

"I noticed a lot of runes when I visited your house. I don't suppose you're trying to summon a demon?" Luna asked. A silvery hare hopped behind her, occasionally stopping to sniff the floor.

"Well, not actively," I said with a modest shrug.

"Oh" – Luna spent a moment staring into space – "Are you from the future?"

I don't think I've ever been quite so taken aback. "What?"

"Well, it's just that you get most spells on the first try, except when they're obscure – in which case you become upset and take slightly longer than average. Also, you know a lot of things that you probably shouldn't."

I've never been one to diminish my reputation. "It's true. I come from a time not long removed from now, where I am the Defense Against the Dark Arts professor at Hogwarts. In my timeline, I successfully defeated Voldemort but then decided that I could do better."

Luna's Patronus jerked its head up, then disappeared. Luna spoke softly. "You…you don't have to lie, you know. You could have just told me I was wrong."

She departed, her movements less floating than usual. I scowled at her retreating form. "Right. She probably wants an apology or something. Ginevra!"

Ginevra raced from the line of practicing students, and I found myself chuckling at her eagerness. "I need you to apologize to Luna for me."

"Alright," the redhead said. "What did you do?"

I shrugged. "I'm not sure. You should probably figure that out before you apologize to her, or you'll look like a jerk."

Chapter 12: HP vs Dolores Umbridge (Pt 2)

Seventh Horcrux

Harry Potter vs. Dolores Umbridge (Pt. 2)

I stormed into Dumbledore's office, summons in hand, and slammed it down upon the old man's desk. "I don't care what Umbridge has told you! Pensieve memories can be faked, and everyone knows that Veritaserum doesn't work on sociopaths."

Dumbledore remained calm, a trait which was as unwavering as it was frustrating. "Mr. Potter –"

"I have done nothing, and I will testify to this under Veritaserum."

The phoenix screeched in irritation, and I screeched back to establish dominance. Dumbledore said, "Mr. Potter, this meeting does not concern Professor Umbridge."

"Oh," I said. "That's good because I haven't done anything."

He offered me a lemon drop. "Yes, I know. You were quite vocal about that earlier."

I spoke slowly. "I don't suppose you're planning to teach me Dark Magic?"

His eyes twinkled. "No, I'm afraid not. Although Miss Weasley did enlighten me about your unique definition for the term."

I would have to talk with her about meddling in my affairs without my consent. I made a note of that and then promptly forgot it when Dumbledore said, "Have you noticed anything strange lately?"

I sank into the seat in front of Dumbledore's desk. "Well, the ghosts have been whispering among themselves a lot. Do you think they're rebelling?"

"No, that likely has to do with the Bloody Baron's deathday. I was referring to whether you have experienced something strange lately. Odd visions, voices, urges. Anything of that sort," he prompted.

I considered his question. Every few nights, I dreamt that I was once again Lord Voldemort, ordering and crucioing my Death Eaters. Just this morning, I'd missed the entirety of Professor Flitwick's lecture because I was too caught up in daydreaming that I was a man-eating snake. And I'd nearly taken Ron's head off during a recent meeting of our new study group when I felt a sudden and inexplicable flash of rage.

For quite possibly the first time in my life, I answered Albus Dumbledore honestly. "Nothing out of the ordinary."

He frowned. "Nothing at all?"

I shook my head, jumping a bit when the phoenix landed on the desk in front of me.

"Is that a problem?" I asked.

"No, no, it's very good, actually."

I peered into his eyes. "Really? You seem sort of disappointed about it."

Dumbledore spoke gravely. "I had suspected that your scar might connect you to Voldemort, allowing you some sort of window into his mind. If this had been the case, then his rebirth would have caused certain side effects to both of you. It seems I was wrong. That I was incorrect is almost certainly for the better."

"Huh," I said, yanking my hand away from the phoenix's bite, "I don't suppose I can leave now?"

Dumbledore waved me towards the door. "Go ahead. Though I do hope that Professor Umbridge will have no cause to pay me a visit today…"

"Of course not," I scoffed. "I've done nothing."

The phoenix watched me leave with black, judging eyes.

"Lucius!" I cried, waving my minion over to take a seat in front of my (previously his) desk.

Lucius, startled, said, "My lord."

"Yes, that is who I am," I said, "How are you?"

Lucius raised a trembling hand. "I'm still in pain, and I can't do any paperwork until the nerves heal…"

"Right, the crucioing," I said with a knowing nod. "Sorry about that. I had a flash of sudden and inexplicable rage."

He frowned. Really, I expected him to be more cheerful since I'd gotten that Hair-Growth Potion. I shrugged off his ungratefulness. "I had the weirdest dream yesterday."

Lucius dully asked, clearly struggling to hide his curiosity, "Was that during the nap you took after crucioing me?"

I beamed. "Yes, that's the one! I was in History of Magic, and you were there. And a Weasley. And then we started dueling in the back of the classroom, but Binns didn't stop us because he didn't notice. It angered me greatly. Do you know why?"

Lucius frowned, smoothing down his hair with a shaking hand. "Because you didn't get to crucio anyone?"

I laughed. "No, no. I just can't stop thinking: Why didn't I do that when I was still a student? Binns probably wouldn't have noticed. Oh, before I forget. One of your peacocks was being insubordinate, so I killed it. Dobby promised to have it ready for dinner I'm not actually certain if people eat peacocks, but I imagine the taste of victory will override any unpleasant flavor."

Hermione nibbled on the tip of her quill, looking at her newly-purchased planner. "This would be a lot easier if we didn't have to work around your detentions with Umbridge."

"I consider it recreation at this point," I said, "and we're making real progress. She's finally acknowledged that she has no idea how to deal with boggarts."

Hermione pinched her lips. "Why?"

"She can't even get the one out from under her bed."

She jotted something down in the margin. "Do I even want to know how you got it under there?"

"Lemon drops," I said. "I'm thinking I'll work on werewolves next."

"You can't put Professor Lupin under Umbridge's bed," she sighed.

"I was thinking Snape, though I suppose Lupin would be the better choice. He can deal with the boggart."

"Harry James Po–"

A loud boom echoed through the Room of Requirement, and we watched, stunned, as a dummy slammed into the wall and fell into pieces. Its head landed in my batch of Felix Felicis with a sickly hiss and a string of black smoke.

Finally, Hermione said, "Ron? What type of spell was that?"

"A stunner," Ron said.

"Oh," she said. "You, um, you might want to put a little less energy into it next time."

I said, "Or…you could not do that."

Meow! Mew! Rrrowr! Purrrr…

This was completely ridiculous. Kitten plates covered Umbridge's wall, constantly mewling and fighting with each other. I usually took my detentions in the DADA classroom, but it hadn't yet recovered from my last detention.

I turned away from my parchment and a quill that used actual ink and towards Umbridge, who was pretending to grade papers but primarily watching me fail to write lines. I said, "It doesn't matter how many kittens you put on your wall. No one will ever believe you have a soul."

That might have seemed a bit harsh. Still, I'd been fighting a strange urge to crucio someone all day (preferably Malfoy), and I needed to vent.

She raised an arm, pink sleeve swinging perilously close to my inkwell. "Well, I hardly think –"

"And the pink!" I cried. "Wait, of course. You're still using the methods that allowed you to appear normal during your childhood. Unfortunately, the kittens and pink and crooning voice only further alienate you from your current peers. You're sixty-seven, and it's creepy now…which reminds me: Happy birthday."

Umbridge's face was beginning to match her robes. She smiled tightly. "Are you lying again, Mr. Potter? Tut, tut. It looks like you –"

"Wait! Before you say anything else, I am obligated to inform you that, if you assign me any more detentions, I will technically be your apprentice."

"Detention" – she smiled sweetly – "A week's worth."

"…Really, Ronald!" Hermione exclaimed as we exited the Great Hall. We were stopped short, however, when Draco Malfoy, along with Crabbe and Goyle, stepped in front of us.

"Malfoy," I said, nodding.

"Potter," he said. "Still dragging along the Weasel and your pet Mudblood, eh? I don't suppose you've rethought my offer for more fitting companionship?"

"Not really. Have you reconsidered being my minion?"

Ron laughed at the suggestion, while Hermione nearly growled. She had been getting rather territorial lately. Between her and Ginevra, it was a wonder I'd recruited so many new minions this year.

Malfoy snapped, "I would never –"

We clearly had nothing to discuss, since we were once again at a standstill, so I continued walking. Ron nearly tripped, distracted by his shuddering laughter.

Malfoy gaped, "Hey! Get back here."

I turned around, eyebrow quirked.

"You can't just leave," the blond said. Right, he hadn't gotten around to talking about his father or his money yet.

Ron crossed his arms menacingly, though Malfoy's hulking minions diminished the affect. The redhead said, "You bloody well bet we can."

"Actually, you poor Weasel, that is no longer allowed under High Inquisitor Umbridge's rules," Malfoy said. "Only two students can be together outside of classes."

"Three's more than that," Crabbe put in helpfully.

Malfoy smirked. "So you'll have to split up, or I'll dock points from Gryffindor."

Hermione glared, hand flying to her prefect's badge. "Prefects are not allowed to dock points from other houses! It's a clear conflict of interest."

"Ten points for arguing with a member of Umbridge's new Inquisitorial Squad, who, by the way, can take as many points as they like" – he raised a hand at Ron's opening mouth – "And are exempt from the three-person rule."

I knew he wouldn't stay independent for long. Malfoys were born to minion.

Malfoy turned to me triumphantly. "I'll give fifty to Slytherin if you agree to an alliance."

"I'm rooting for Gryffindor now," I said regretfully.

"Bollocks," he muttered.

"How'd you even get on this squad, Malfoy?" Ron asked. "I don't remember hearing anything about it."

"Well, it's very exclusive. My father –"

Well, that's two for two.

Hermione sweetly cut in, "So you bought your place, then?"

Malfoy scowled. "Umbridge just prefers a better quality of wizard."

"Oh, my apologies," she crooned. "Nepotism. I can't say I'm surprised. That's how you get everything else: Your place on the Quidditch team, your spot as a prefect –"

"Jealous, Granger?" Malfoy asked.

"Not at all. I can't even imagine how exhausting it must be to realize that you simply aren't good enough for anything" – a very Dumbledore gleam lit her eyes – "That must be the reason you're in Slytherin, too. After all, you don't exactly fit the requirements very well. You're simple-minded, unsubtle, and unambitious."

"Typical Hufflepuff traits," I said.

Hermione ignored me, too focused on the kill. "You're Pureblood, I suppose, presuming your mother didn't – "

Malfoy trembled with rage. "Shut up, Mudblood."

He threw the first spell, but Hermione was the one that got a detention. Admittedly, that wasn't as unreasonable as it might have seemed. She could be positively vicious when aimed at an acceptable target.

Hermione slammed the Room of Requirement's door shut, startling me from target practice (with Neville as the target).

"So," I asked, shooting a spell over my shoulder. "How was detention?"

"Fine," she hissed.

I frowned. "You used the charm I showed you, right? Because, if you didn't, then that would be really dumb, and I don't take you for some sort of Hufflepuff."

In the distance, a Hufflepuff blew the head off of a dummy. Hermione said, "Yes, I used the glove."

"Did she bleed?" I prodded.

"Yes, Harry, she bloody well bled!" she shouted. "And then Malfoy waited outside to take more points for injuring a teacher because he's a great, big git!"

She stormed towards the library.

"What's got her knickers in a twist?" Ron asked, absentmindedly shooting a curse at Neville.

I shrugged. "I don't…Wait, never mind. I think I know."

I wandered over to the library's table, smiling uneasily as Hermione glared up from her hastily-acquired book. She said, "What?"

Right. How to approach this? I'd never had someone willing to have this discussion with me when I was a confused, pubescent boy. "Hermione…You are a beautiful, brilliant young woman, and it's natural for you to have certain urges."

Her eyes widened. "Harry, you do not have to –"

I forged on. "You might look around at some of your classmates who are wealthy and attractive, and want – very badly – to crush them beneath your heel."

Hermione blinked a few times in quick succession. "I have to admit, that was absolutely not where I thought this conversation was going."

I smiled, placing a hand on her shoulder. "When you see someone like Malfoy, all you want is for him to kneel down and kiss your robes."

"Harry, I don't want that. That would be horrible."

I shook my head. "No, see, you're making this a good and evil thing. It's not. This is about power. He has it, and you want him to give you that power and suffer for keeping it from you for so long."

She pouted. "Honestly, I just want him to stop bothering me and possibly never speak again."

"If he was your minion, you could make him do those things."

Hermione took a deep breath, then sighed gustily. "I don't think you understand this, so I'm going to explain it as simply as possible. He's a git, and I don't like him."

"Of course he is. He's only fifteen. One day, Malfoy is going to realize just how much he wants to be your minion, and he is going to feel so embarrassed about all this."

Hermione groaned, burying her face in her hands.

I threw the doors open, storming into Lucius's Great Hall…formal dining room…ballroom…long, high-ceilinged room which made my voice echo menacingly. I declared, "Welcome, my dearest, most loyal servants!"

I suddenly noticed the nearly empty room. Lucius clutched his snake-headed cane tightly.

Severus, meanwhile, remained stoic. I'm still not entirely certain that he experiences emotion. I'd never found any while using Legilimency.

I scowled. "Where is the rest of the inner circle?"

"Indisposed, my lord," Severus drawled.

"What could possibly be more important than attending to me?" I snapped. "That idiot Crabbe doesn't even have a job. I could kill him for this insult."

Severus smirked. "Actually, you did kill him. Several months ago."

How forward-thinking of me. I settled onto my new throne, made with a pile of Malfoy portraits. To my delight, they wailed every time I sat down. "What about Wilkes?"

"He died during the last war," Severus said.

I stroked my chin. "Zabini?"

Lucius anxiously petted his hair, as he often does. "His wife got him."

I gripped my wand, lazily pointing it at Lucius. "Rosier?"

The blond fell to his knees in a grovel. "You killed him an hour ago, my lord."

Wait, did I? "I'm well aware of that. I was testing you."

Severus watched me impassively. "Of course, my lord."

I said, "What about Bellatrix, then? I'm quite certain I didn't kill her."

"She is in Azkaban," Severus said.

"Oh…" – I tapped my wand against my chin thoughtfully – "Why?"

"You likely recall that she is a Death Eater," Severus said.

"Plenty of people are Death Eaters," I said. "They aren't in Azkaban."

"Well, yes," Lucius said, "but Bellatrix admitted to it."

"Bellatrix never struck me as a Hufflepuff," I muttered, "Why would she be so stupid?"

"There wasn't much point in denying her involvement," Snape drawled. "When they caught her, she was busy torturing the Longbottoms into insanity."

"Yes. She did always like that…So, she's been in there for…?"

"Thirteen years," Lucius said helpfully.

I leaned back on my throne, smiling as the Malfoy ancestors groaned underneath me. "That's pretty long. We should do something about that."

Hermione received the morning Prophet, eyes immediately skimming the byline for Rita Skeeter. She soon relaxed, evidence that the front page articles were written by someone else. Satisfied, the girl turned her gaze to the headline and cursed.

I'm not sure if she's ever done that before.

"You alright, 'Mione?" Ron asked.

She said, "There's been a jailbreak at Azkaban. All the Death Eaters have escaped."

Ron began to smile, then frowned, then settled for his usual confused expression. "Well, that's good, right? Yeah, a bunch of Death Eaters are probably going to attack us. More than usual, I mean, but at least now they can't say that You-Know-Who isn't back."

Hermione crumpled the paper, hissing, "They're blaming it on Sirius Black."

"Well, to be fair, it could have been Black," I said. "He hasn't tried to kill me in months, which just doesn't seem like him. He must be plotting something in his spare time."

"Harry, this is serious!"

Ron grinned through a mouthful of mashed-up toast, "Or, it cuh be Shirius. Y'know, like Shirius Bl-"

Hermione said, "Not the time. Also, finish chewing. Some of the absolute worst people from the last war could be coming here: The Mulcibers, Augustus Rookwood, Hagrid, Bellatrix Lestrange…Harry, are you even listening to me?!"

I startled back into reality. "Oh, yes, sorry. Just had a sudden feeling of déjà vu."

Hermione huffed, shoving away her half-eaten breakfast to make room for a book on hexes.

I stopped by the Room of Requirement after detention, disappointed to find Neville collapsed on the ground. "Neville, why aren't you running?"

"I can't," he panted. "Too much."

"I'm trying to make you a legend here," I said. "I thought you wanted that."

"I guess," Neville muttered.

"Then why are you giving up already?" I asked, feeling a bit like Hermione.

"It's, uh, not helping me with my magic," Neville said. "All this running around."

I scowled. Neville had completely misinterpreted this offer, but everyone now knew that he was my student and I had no intention of failing now. "I never said anything about magic. Just being great. Also killing evil wizards. Or good wizards, depending on whether you decide to join up with Hermione."

Ginevra, who was helping a Ravenclaw with his spellwork, shouted, "Hermione's studying right now, but she said that – if you said that – I should mention that she isn't evil."

"Regardless of Hermione's lies," I said. "Physical prowess is a rarely used but surprisingly effective tool for destroying your enemies. Most wizards cannot handle close-quarters combat. Even the most incompetent wizard can excel if he's good with a sword or something. Just look at Godric Gryffindor."

Neville blinked. "Oh. Okay."

It was nice to tell someone something without Hermione around to complain about fact-checking or non-existent sources or common sense.

He frowned, standing. "Why don't you exercise?"

"Oh, that's because I'm actually good at magic."

Neville swayed on his feet, looking miserable again. I'm not sure why. I'd done a perfectly good job cheering him up.

A quiet voice said, "Don't worry, Neville. Wrackspurts are attracted to the pollen on your clothes. You would probably be fine in a colder climate."

I beamed, whirling around to find Luna Lovegood. "You're back! I presume you got Ginevra's apology?"

She nodded. "Yes, she seemed very sincere about it."

"Good, good," I said while Neville trudged away from us. "Is there anything else I can help you with?"

"I've just been wondering…Are you a Department of Mysteries spy?"

I frowned, curbing the urge to build my legend. "Why do you think that?"

"I would expect Harry Potter to get special training. But they wouldn't want anyone to know about that, so they sent a spy in his place. Also, you're friends with a lot of important people: the Weasleys, the smartest girl in our generation, the son of Voldemort's right-hand man –"

"Sirius Black had a son?" Was it Ron? It was probably Ron.

"No, I mean Draco Malfoy. Although I suppose he could be Black's son," she said thoughtfully.

"Oh, he's not my friend."

"Really?" – Luna hummed to herself – "There's also the Longbottom heir and the Quibbler editor's daughter."

"I legitimately have no idea which one that is," I admitted.

She stared at me with wide, pale eyes. "Me."

"Right."

"So, you're not a spy, then?"

I chuckled. "Of course not. Hermione's the spy. The Department of Mysteries wouldn't send two spies."

Luna pouted. "Harry, Hermione isn't a spy for the Department of Mysteries. That would be silly."

"I hardly think this is necessary," McGonagall said, lips thinned with annoyance.

Umbridge merrily followed the other woman into her office. She tittered. "Now, now, Minerva, I observed all of the werewolf's career advice sessions. We wouldn't want any insinuations of favoritism, now would we?"

"That werewolf is my colleague," McGonagall spat. "Also, that's just a silly rumor among the students. They've been calling him a vampire for years."

"Well, they do say that children are intuitive about these things," she said.

McGonagall raised an eyebrow, sitting primly behind her desk. "I suspect they had little experience with children."

I lowered my invisibility cloak's hood. It was a wonder it had lasted this long. Of course, Dumbledore had likely lied about its age, as he often does. Umbridge squeaked in fright, and McGonagall's mouth twitched upwards. She asked, "Here for our meeting, Mr. Potter?"

"Of course," I said.

"You're quite early," McGonagall remarked.

I shrugged. "I was excited."

She nearly smiled but caught herself just in time. "Two hours early, in fact."

"Incredibly excited," I clarified. "Also, I have detention in two hours."

"I imagine most students would have used this as an excuse to skip detention," she said.

I smiled, taking a seat in front of her desk. "No, that's alright. I like detention."

It wouldn't be nearly as fun if I followed the professors' instructions, but, unlike the other students, I have no fear of expulsion. Dumbledore would never allow me that far from his domain.

"Ah," McGonagall said. "Tell me, Mr. Potter, what is your opinion on Professor Umbridge's presence at this meeting?"

"It seems reasonable to me," I said.

Umbridge smirked. "Thank you –"

"After all, that's perfectly within her rights as my master. If she was at any other students' meetings, however, that would be weird."

It was nice to see Umbridge scowling again. Her smile gave me the heebie-jeebies.

Umbridge turned to McGonagall and said, "I simply do not understand why you've allowed a clearly mentally ill boy to go untreated for so long while under your care."

"Mr. Potter is simply a child, Dolores. It's no surprise you don't understand that since you have so very little experience in teaching."

McGonagall turned smoothly back to me. "Now, Mr. Potter, have you given any thought to your future career?"

"Of course," I said, beaming, "I'm going to be the Defense Against the Dark Arts professor at Hogwarts."

McGonagall was silent for a few moments, no doubt impressed by how astutely I had chosen my career path. "Are you certain that's a wise decision, Mr. Potter?"

"Well, yeah, I mean, I'm pretty good at Defense, and I'm great with kids." I'd been surrounded by them for the past several years, and not one child had suffered irreparable harm while under my care. This is particularly impressive because I lead them into dangerous situations all the time.

"Besides," I said, "the position's always open."

"And that doesn't concern you," McGonagall prodded. Umbridge scribbled something on her notepad.

"No, not at all. I've survived everything that got rid of the last ones." And I wasn't very well going to murder myself.

"Perhaps Mr. Potter would be suited for a more" – Umbridge coughed lightly – "simple position. I hardly think the stresses of professorship would be well suited to his delicate mind, and his delinquent tendencies are hardly fitting for the post."

"You're the only person who ever gives me detention," I pointed out. "I could easily argue that the problem is not me, but you."

I would be lying, of course. Snape still docked points from Slytherin for my misconduct, McGonagall had devised a method of punishment whereby my favorite desserts would go unmade for days after any particularly concerning transgressions, and Filch had actively avoided me since my only detention with him back in second year.

"That's ridiculous! You earn those detentions through your disrespect."

"And you earn my disrespect by being a terrible teacher," I explained. "So, if you would stop doing that, you wouldn't have to put up with my detentions anymore."

"Detention," she hissed, stubborn as ever.

I shrugged. "Besides, I would have thought you would approve of my choice to take your job. Why else would you make me your apprentice?"

The rest of the Gryffindor's career advice meetings had to be postponed because Umbridge exploded McGonagall's office. As I explained to Umbridge during my later detention, her temper was one of many traits that made her such a terrible choice for Defense Against the Dark Arts professor.

"No, not the Bubblehead Charm," Hermione muttered. "Nearly everyone knows it already, and the few that don't can learn it from the others during their self-guided period. I…hm. Did Neville ever figure out the Patronus?"

It took me a moment to realize that Hermione was no longer talking to herself. I said, "It doesn't really matter. We've given up on magic for Neville."

"Honestly, Harry, he can't just give up on magic. We go to a school for magic."

"Actually, we go to a school for witches and wizards. Neville has more traditional talents, like swordsmanship."

Hermione glanced up from her half-filled planner. "I didn't know Neville could use a sword."

"He's working on it." I nodded to the other end of the room, where Neville was hacking at a dummy with a sword.

Hermione's lips pursed. "Is that a real sword?"

I said, "I suppose that depends on your definition of real. Yes, it cuts things, but the Room may have created it solely to fulfill our wishes."

We walked over to Neville, and Neville waved hello with his sword.

Hermione gasped, eyes wide. "Oh, Merlin, or Gryffindor, or…Oh my."

"Are you alright?" he asked. "I didn't cut you or anything, right? I, uh, don't think I was that close, but it might be magic. Well, more magic than –"

"Give it to me. I'd like to examine it," she said weakly.

He did so, and it disappeared.

Hermione stared at her empty hands.

"Well, you've destroyed it. How is Neville supposed to become good at anything now?" I grumbled.

The sword appeared in Neville's grasp. Hermione leaned forward, sucking air in through her large teeth. "This is the Sword of Gryffindor."

I snatched it from Neville, growling as it once again disappeared. A crowd had begun to gather, mumbling and eyeing Neville enviously each time the sword reappeared in his hands. Someone would make a grab for it, only for it to vanish again and again.

Above the commotion, Dumbledore's phoenix perched, watching us. As it always does.

"The Sword of Gryffindor can only be wielded by those who are worthy of the house," Hermione explained.

Finally, licking his lips nervously, Ron took the sword from Neville. He stared at it in awe. "I feel like Merlin, from that story with the stone and sword."

"You mean King Arthur, Ronald," Hermione said.

"No," he said, "I mean Merlin. Who's that other bloke?"

I crept through the dungeons, feeling like a man-eating snake stalking its prey. Sidling closer, I whispered, "Psst. Draco. Draco. Draaa-"

Malfoy jumped, head whipping about him. "Bloody hell! Potter, what are you doing?"

"I'm invisible."

Malfoy snorted. "Yes, Potter. I am aware that you're invisible. You're always invisible. What I want to know is why you're in the Slytherin common room."

I smirked. "I followed someone in. Or maybe I guessed the password. Or maybe I hissed at the wall, and it let me in. Or maybe I'm the Heir of Slytherin, and the castle recognizes my right to be here. I won't tell you which one. I'm sneaky like that."

"Potter, everyone can hear you talking," he pointed out.

My eyes widened at his idiocy and I derisively said, "You don't have a Silencing Charm up? What are you, a squib?"

He flicked his wand. "You're not the Heir of Slytherin."

"Are you sure about that?" – I hissed at him – "Ha-sha-ss-kah."

He cocked an eyebrow. "Really, Potter?"

"If I'd had a snake, that would have gone a lot better," I informed him. This is primarily true because the snake would have latched onto Malfoy's face, and he would have been too distracted to insult me.

"Sure," Malfoy said. "So, have you finally decided to drop the blood-traitor and mudblood?"

I shook my invisible head. "No, I've spent far too much time training them. I would appreciate it if you didn't mention this to Hermione, though. I don't know what's going on between you two, but I refuse to involve myself in your lover's spat."

Malfoy's face wrinkled in a very Weasley fashion. "Me and Granger? That's disgusting, Potter. Twenty points from Gryffindor for making me picture that."

I frowned, realized he couldn't see it, and frowned harder. "Malfoy, you can't do that."

"Potter, I know that you occasionally miss the simple facts of reality, so let me explain this to you. I'm a member of the Inquisitorial Squad, and we're allowed to take points –"

"I don't mean it like that," I interrupted. "I mean, you literally cannot take points from Gryffindor. Gryffindor has no points. The only house that still has points is Slytherin. The only person who even cares anymore is you. I'm telling you this because some people seem to think we're friends, so you being dumb makes me look bad."

He sneered. "I am not –"

"No, hear me out here. This is literally the worst example of cheating I've ever seen. You have made your group pointless, much like Gryffindor house, and everyone hates you. Even the other Slytherins hate you because you've all but stated that the only way your house could win the Cup is if you cheat. Which, to be fair, is true because you haven't done well in Quidditch since I bought the other three teams new brooms without burdening them with terrible seekers."

"Potter!" he shouted through the Silencing Charm.

But it was too late. I was already gone.

I sat at the head of the Malfoy table, atop my throne of wailing portraits, and watched my recently-freed followers. Rookwood was struggling to Imperio a spoon. The Lestrange brothers had slipped under the tablecloth, hissing at anyone who came too close. Hagrid was looking about as if he'd never seen any of us before and had been incredibly violent until Severus reminded him of his status.

They'd entered Azkaban as perfectly competent, if slightly sociopathic, followers and left it as raving lunatics.

Bellatrix, in contrast, had entered as a raving lunatic and left slightly mellowed.

I took a bite of cake, and then, slightly nauseous, set down my fork. "Bellatrix?"

"Yes, my love…I mean my lord?" she crooned, batting her eyes.

Unfortunately, some things even the Dementors cannot cure. "Stop dosing Dobby's cakes with love potion. I like cake. Dose something I like slightly less, such as the turkey."

"But everyone eats the turkey," Bellatrix whined.

I raised an eyebrow, baffled. "Then one of them might love you…I'm pretty sure that's what you want."

She pouted, stealing a bite of my cake.

I legitimately had no idea what she was upset about this time. I wasn't some sort of seer.

I paused. Right. The prophecy. I should probably go get that. Plus, it would be a nice excuse to get Bellatrix out of the house and finally have some cake that hadn't been tampered with.

"Bellatrix," I said. "I need you to break into the Department of Mysteries. Try to be subtle about it, will you?"

"Neville," Hermione said, staring coolly down the sword pointed at her nose. "Really?"

Neville flushed, stumbling backwards into the Room of Requirement and dropping the Sword of Gryffindor. "Um, sorry. It's just…Harry –"

She raised a hand to silence him and stalked forward. Hermione hissed, "Harry James Potter, what are you doing? Neville is dropping from the ceiling to attack people, Umbridge is prowling the school looking for you, and WHY IS THERE A PHOENIX ON YOUR HEAD?!"

I reached upwards to pat Fawkes, grateful for the invisible glove charm which protected me from his bites. "Yeah, he's been following me around for a while. I asked Dumbledore, and he said something about migratory patterns. He might think I'm another phoenix or something…Dumbledore wasn't very clear. He never is."

"I think he's trying to build a nest from my hair!" Ginevra chirped, rubbing her bald spot.

I smiled. "Now, Hermione, what's got you so upset?"

She grabbed her wand, snarling, "I just told you –"

"Well, what was the first thing that upset you?" That's usually the only one that matters.

Hermione said, "Malfoy tried to arrest me for being your friend, or something like that. Apparently, that's against one of Umbridge's new rules."

I raised an eyebrow. "You escaped?"

"No, I'm secretly Umbridge polyjuiced as Hermione Granger," she said flatly.

My eyes widened. That's what I get for trusting Neville with our defense. I raised my wand.

"Sarcasm!" she shouted.

I eyed her suspiciously, peering into her eyes for signs of the Imperius. Atop my skull, Fawkes did the same. "Right, if she used polyjuice, Umbridge would turn into your true, older form."

"Honestly, Harry. I am not a spy. I banished Malfoy on top of the lake and came straight here."

"…They did get more water in that lake, right? Because it's really deep…" The phoenix trilled in agreement.

Ginevra called from across the room, "The lake's been full for over a year. You just don't go outside."

"And Malfoy can swim?" I inquired.

Hermione pursed her lips. "Well, if he can't, I imagine he'll learn."

I placed a hand on her shoulder. "Hermione, I'm concerned about how emotionally invested you're getting in this relationship. I…I'm starting to think that you're not in love with Malfoy, after all."

Hermione gaped. "Why did you ever think that?"

I hated to ask this question so bluntly, especially considering the possible damage even voicing the possibility could do to her reputation, but I had to be sure. "Is Draco Malfoy your rival?"

She carefully evaded the question, confirming my worst fears. "I just think he's an awful person."

"So, that's a yes. You can do better than that," I said, despairing. "Malfoy is pathetic. Treating him as any sort of equal reflects poorly on you and everyone you associate with." Primarily me.

"You're kidding me," she said.

"He's not!" Ginevra cried, causing Fawkes to flap his wings menacingly.

I said, "My rival, for instance, is the Dark Lord Voldemort."

"He tries to kill you," Hermione said. "He's not your rival."

"Snape then," I acquiesced. Previously, it was Dumbledore. "You can do better. Maybe Neville."

Hermione glanced towards Neville, who had once again scaled the wall and was fiercely watching the door. "Harry, I don't want a rival."

"If I was in your shoes, I would be doubtful too," I reassured her. "But Neville is really improving. I think the two of you would be good for each other."

"No, I seriously don't want one. Also, I like Neville." With a panicked look, she hastily added, "He's my friend."

I chuckled. "Not a problem. Plenty of people don't like Neville. You can ask them about it."

"No. Also, you never did explain why he's guarding the door," Hermione said.

I twirled my wand, smirking. "We're expecting an attack."

"The twins again?"

"No, not a Weasley this time. Ginevra's contacts have informed us that we have a leak. One of the Ravenclaws has gone rogue. Umbridge could arrive any minute."

A minute later, Umbridge stormed through the door, and the phoenix dived forward, talons extended.

Chapter 15: HP vs Love (Pt 2)

Seventh Horcrux

Chapter 8: Harry Potter vs. Love (Pt. 2)

A dozen Death Eaters and I sat in Grimmauld Place's dining room. Kreacher had long ago cleared our plates, though tea and a few desserts still lingered. Against my protests, Bellatrix had spooned pudding onto my plate.

"It's good for you!" she crooned.

I raised an eyebrow. "Vanilla pudding is good for me."

Bellatrix's eyes darted about the table. "Yes."

Frowning, I turned away from her. "Lucius, any progress on our plans to break into Hogwarts and kidnap Harry Potter?"

"Yes, my lord, but I fear it will be difficult. According to my sources in Hogwarts –"

"You mean your son?" Sirius asked, earning a cuff on the back of the head from Severus.

"My. Sources. In. Hogwarts," Lucius ground out, "have informed me that Potter spends most of his time invisible and only periodically attends classes."

"He's never in Defense," Severus drawled.

I nodded. "And the break-in?"

"We've acquired a Vanishing Cabinet that has a twin in the Room of Requirement. However, it seems to be broken, and my son –"

"Sucks at magic?" Sirius said.

"In this instance, I have to agree," Severus said. "It's a wonder he's passing Defense."

"Yes, yes, you're the new DADA professor at Hogwarts," I snapped. "We're aware."

"Things are progressing well under the circumstances, my lor…oh, Trelawney," Lucius ended sourly.

Having wandered down from her floor, Trelawney watched us in silent horror. She looked like she might faint. This would be a poor decision, mind you, because the only person in a position to catch her was Bellatrix.

I smiled at the seer. "Would you like to join us?"

Trelawney shook her head, though the motion was slight enough that she may have simply been trembling. "There are thirteen of you at the table. The first of you to rise shall also be the first to die."

"But, if you join us, then there will be fourteen people at the table, and we'll all be fine."

Trelawney blinked. "Oh. Yes. I suppose that might work. Truly, fate has favored us this evening."

She shakily settled into an empty chair. I, of course, immediately darted out of mine. "HA! I've escaped."

Trelawney moaned, collapsing atop the table. Bellatrix seemed similarly upset. "But, my lord, you haven't eaten your pudding."

"I don't want the pudding," I declared.

She picked up the bowl, a maniacal look in her eye, and tried to grab my robes. Failing that, she said, "But, my lord, I made it just for you. It's really good. I love you!"

I fled the room, Bellatrix not far behind.

Slughorn surveyed the class, chins trembling in excitement. "Ah, very good. It looks like everyone's here today. We'll be brewing Amortentia. Is anyone familiar with it?"

Hermione's hand shot into the air. Slughorn chortled. "Miss Granger, reaching for the sky as usual, I see."

"Amortentia is the most powerful love potion in existence. It's identified by its mother-of-pearl sheen, smells differently to every person, and causes a strong infatuation in the drinker," Hermione said.

"Very good, Miss Granger. Been reading your textbook, I see," Slughorn said. "Mr. Potter, you had something to add?"

"I refuse to brew this potion," I said. The classroom filled with murmurs.

"Really, now! What's the trouble?" Slughorn asked.

"Love potions are vile things. They completely consume the will of the victim, leaving them horrified and disturbed when the potion eventually wears off," I said.

Ron gaped. "Really?"

"Oh, yes, it's quite terrible for them," I assured him.

"It's just a learning experience," Slughorn said, "not a suggestion. Nothing to worry about."

"Why would you teach someone how to do something if you don't want them to?" I snapped. "This is exactly the sort of thing that got that Second Year Slytherin killed."

Hermione said, "Harry has a point. I'm not sure if I'm comfortable doing this, either."

"I'd expect to see it on your NEWTs, almost no chance it wouldn't be," Slughorn said.

She bit her lip. "Even still…"

"Do you know how many crimes are committed by people under love potion?" I demanded. "More than those under the Imperius."

"Potter has a point," Blaise Zabini said. "You can talk someone under love potion into doing just about anything: running off the side of a building, taunting a Hippogriff, challenging a Goblin to a fight to the death…"

"I was very sorry to hear about your stepfather. He was a good man. Not too bright, but good," Slughorn said.

We were winning. I was certain of it. "That isn't even getting into all the crimes committed against those under the potion: robbery, sexual assault, murder."

"Putting them under at all could be considered slavery," Hermione said. Ron was looking increasingly ill.

I nodded. "And what about all the witches who give Muggles love potions and then marry them? The Muggles don't know to check for that sort of thing."

"The magicals usually don't check, either," Zabini noted.

"And think of the children!"

Ron stuttered, "W-what about the children?"

I said, "Can you imagine how it is for them? If their mother ever forgets to dose their father, he'll leave the family, and she'll die of a broken heart. Then, they'll be all alone, spurned by a man they never really knew."

Ron slumped against the desk, groaning.

Slughorn sighed. "Well, if you're all certain, I suppose we could just have an essay on Amortentia, instead..."

Hermione nodded eagerly, ignoring Ron's continued sounds of misery.

"…Of course, it really is a pity. I was planning to give a prize to the best brewer."

"What kind of prize?" I asked.

"It doesn't matter much now, you understand, since I was planning it specifically for this lesson. But I have a single vial of Felix Felicis, also known as –"

"Liquid luck," I breathed. "I rescind my earlier complaints and reject everyone who agreed with me!"

Slughorn appeared shocked. "Quite sure about that? You seemed terribly set against it."

"Who am I to get in the way of learning?" I declared, grabbing my potions set and sprinting towards the ingredient cupboard.

"Gather round, everyone," Slughorn called, waving us towards the winning potion. "What do you smell, then, Miss Granger?"

A dreamy smile lit up her face. "There's a scent of freshly mown grass, new parchment, spearmint toothpaste, and…ginger."

Ron piped up. "I smell my Chudley Cannons' shirt, cake, and…"

Slughorn sidled next to him, asking, "What is it? A certain girl, perhaps?"

"Lavender!" Ron blurted out.

I said, "Lavender the plant or Lavender the person?"

"Uh, both?" Ron asked, glancing around nervously.

Luna Lovegood sighed. "That's very romantic. Mine is mostly mistletoe, but there's a slight scent of brimstone."

"Luna, what are you doing here?" I asked.

The blonde giggled. "I had a free period, of course."

"That explains it," I said. Ron and Hermione shot us odd looks.

"What does it smell like to you, Harry?" Luna asked.

I leaned forward, taking a deep breath. "Snakes, and…I dunno. Sewers, maybe?"

Ron and Hermione huddled together, whispering and glancing in my direction while Lavender jealously watched the exchange. Finally coming to a decision, the two of them walked over to me.

Hermione took point. "Harry, I really am quite grateful that you saved me from Malfoy's conjured snake, but I have a couple of questions. First of all, why is it still wrapped around your neck?"

"I've always wanted a pet," I said, grinning down at the snake. "I think I'll call him Ophion."

"Okay," she said. "And, also, why is it not biting you?"

"I think he likes me," I said. "Also, I learned snake charming in –"

"Ginny," Ron interrupted. "Can you set up the privacy spells?"

"On it!" Ginevra cried, rushing over to us.

"Thanks," he said, then turned to me. "How'd you really do it, then?"

"I don't know why you don't believe me," I said sullenly.

Hermione huffed. "Alright, fine. I was going to give you a chance to tell the truth on your own, but you clearly have no intention of doing so. I heard you speaking to it in Parseltongue."

"You don't know that," I said. "I could have just been hissing at it. Unless you speak Parseltongue."

I narrowed my eyes at her and my new pet did the same, but the girl merely raised an eyebrow. "You hissed at it, and it immediately curled around your arm."

Ron's eyes widened. "Wait a minute! In Second Year, were you the Heir of Slytherin?"

"No!"

"Oh, that makes so much more sense than the story you told me," Hermione said.

Ron continued, "Then, when you said that you were getting rid of the Heir, did you just mean that you were going to stop?"

"I was gone for two days, Ron! If I was the Heir, what do you think I was doing during that time?"

Ron shrugged. "I dunno. Dealing with your murderous urges?"

"I'm not the Heir!"

Hermione frowned. "It's alright if you were. We won't be angry. In retrospect, that conversation about how everyone was the Heir was clearly a cry for help. Obviously, Hagrid shouldn't have been blamed, but he did turn out to be a Death Eater, so it's really for the best…"

"Look, I would love to take credit for this," I said, "but I'm not the Heir."

"Who was it, then?" Ron asked.

"Uh, I can't tell you," I muttered, stroking Ophion.

Ron and Hermione shot me skeptical looks. Meanwhile, Ginevra was standing very still, eyes wide. It seemed that she was taking her duty as a guard very seriously.

They probably wouldn't have believed me if I explained that the actual Heir was Voldemort's childhood diary. Even if they did, that might lead them…well, Hermione to realize the existence of my Horcruxes. A decoy was clearly necessary.

I said, "Because, even if you talked to him, he wouldn't remember the incident. You see, I obliviated him because I – like Dumbledore – believe in second chances."

"The red girl smells like fear," Ophion informed me.

"Quiet!" I snapped, "I'm trying to convince them that I'm not evil, and you eating someone will not help the situation."

"Harry," Hermione said. "Do you honestly expect us to believe that?"

"Yes?" I said.

At that moment, Ginevra dropped the Silencing Charm and (clearly terrified of my new pet) scurried towards the Girls' Dormitory.

There was only one word on the note: Taffy.

I scowled down at the paper, twisting it this way and that in the hopes that more words would appear. It wouldn't be that odd. Magic does that sometimes.

Growling, I shoved it into my pocket and glared around the breakfast table. "Did any of you tell Dumbledore about my…foreign language experience?"

Hermione and Ron both shook their heads, each absorbed in a book. Huh, Ron reading. That was a first.

"Ginevra?" I threatened.

"I wouldn't ever betray you," Ginevra assured me. "I owe you way too much."

She really was a very good minion. Loyal, cunning, mildly insane, even somewhat attra…I shoved away my plate.

"Ginevra, did you put love potion in my eggs?"

"No," she said, shaking her head. "I haven't got all the ingredients yet."

"If I find out that you're lying…"

"Harry, if I had dosed you with Mum's potion, you would be kissing me right now. It's a really good potion."

I nodded stiffly, glaring back down at the note. Did Silencing Charms not work on portraits? Or were the walls spying for Dumbledore, as well?

"Bloody hell, the Death Eaters were right!" Ron exclaimed.

I smirked. "Out of all my friends, I should have known that you would be the one to become a Blood Purist."

Ron frowned. "Wha? I, no, I don't mean it like that. They weren't right about most things. Murdering gits. It's just, uh, Lavender kept talking about all the stuff I dealt with as a werewolf, and I got curious about what she meant. Things really suck for them…I mean us. And, apparently, Werewolf Rights was pretty important to Death Eaters."

"Only if the werewolf was Pureblood," Hermione said. "Mudbloods were out of luck."

"Twenty points for foul language, Miss Granger," Severus said, sweeping past.

I left for the Headmaster's office.

"They're lying! The only language I know is English!"

I stormed into the Headmaster's office. His phoenix landed on my shoulder, biting at my ear with…affection, I guess?

Dumbledore seemed surprised. "Ah, Harry. I called you up here today to learn more about Voldemort. Was there something else you would like to talk about?"

"No, not at all. Let's talk about Voldemort," I muttered.

"I see," Dumbledore said, peering at me atop his glasses and stroking his beard with a shriveled hand. "Lemon drop?"

I waved it off, the movement jostling Fawkes. "The memory?"

"It is of the first time I met young Tom Riddle. Even then, he was a very cold child," Dumbledore said.

We walked to the pensieve, leaning forward until we were sucked inside. I glanced at the bird still digging its claws into my shoulder and regarding the dilapidated orphanage around us with deep suspicion.

"I didn't know phoenixes could go into pensieves," I remarked.

Dumbledore chuckled. "Fawkes can go anywhere he likes, I think."

We followed the younger Headmaster, then a Transfiguration professor, through his travels and conversation with a Wool's Orphanage worker. It was then that he met the matron.

Mrs. Cole never liked me.

Further, she seemed quite intent on ensuring that Dumbledore felt the same.

Her main complaints were that I was weird (i.e. a wizard) and creepy (i.e. well-behaved). She had some legitimate points, but I would argue that all the children at my orphanage were horrible. I was just better at it than they were.

I felt a sudden regret that I'd never murdered her. I could do it now, but she was probably already dead. It had been like fifty years.

After twenty minutes of commiserating with Mrs. Cole about how awful I was, Dumbledore decided to actually meet me.

My younger self immediately began panicking, certain that he would be sent to the asylum. I'd been threatened with it plenty of times. Some nights, I lie awake, wondering if I actually was sent there.

Dumbledore responded by setting everything I owned on fire.

There's a reason he was always my least-favorite professor.

"Is that proof enough for you, Tom?" he asked, oblivious to the phoenix flying repeatedly through his head.

"What proof? I saw nothing. You're not taking me to the asylum," Tom muttered.

Dumbledore's younger self sighed, putting out the fire. The wardrobe began shivering, then, and Dumbledore encouraged the boy to take out a box filled with small things.

"Thieving is not tolerated at Hogwarts," Dumbledore said. Of course, he didn't bother to check the other children's wardrobes to see if they had any of my things in there because that would be fair.

Dumbledore explained Diagon Alley and its many shops. "I could accompany you –"

"Hah! And let you lead me straight to the madhouse? I think not."

I probably should have let him come. I've always been terrible with directions.

On the bright side, I did discover Knockturn Alley in my travels…

The moment he heard footsteps on the staircase, Ron dove under his bed covers.

Ginevra giggled at the very noticeable lump he made under the blankets. "It's just me."

Ron said, "Uh, 'me' isn't Lavender, is it?"

"No. It's Ginny," she said. You'd think Ron would know his only sister's voice, but I suppose fear had taxed his already-limited mental abilities.

"Oh, thank Merlin…Wait, what are you doing up here?! You better not be messing around with Dean, or I'll kill him," Ron snapped, bursting out from under the bed covers.

The redhead sat on the corner of his mattress. "Dean and I broke up a couple of weeks ago."

"He didn't hurt you, did he?" Ron asked, face darkening.

She shook her head, smiling. "No, nothing like that. Dean just didn't want to date me anymore because he thinks I'm obsessed with Harry Potter. And I didn't really want to date him anymore because he got upset every time I tried to help Harry. Also, trying to maintain dozens of friendships and a relationship at the same time is exhausting."

Ron frowned. "Oh. Well, why did you come here, then?"

"Harry needs our help downstairs."

"With what?" Ron asked.

"Dunno. He didn't say" – Ginevra turned towards the door – "Harry?"

I pulled down my invisibility cloak, wrapping it around my shoulders.

Ron rolled his eyes, grumbling, "Should've know you were invisible. What's going on, then?"

I grinned. "We're killing Bellatrix Lestrange."

Ron's mouth fell open into a typical Weasley pose.

Ginevra said, "Oh, we should tell Neville. He's always wanted to do that."

"H-how?" Ron squeaked.

"Remember how Hermione suggested that we should use my connection to the Dark Lord to play upon his paranoia, causing him to kill his own people?"

"Uh, sort of," Ron said.

"Well, he's finally gone to bed at a decent hour, and I've figured out how to activate his visions," I said. "So come along before he wakes up."

Ron chuckled nervously. "I, uh, can't."

"You're very important for authenticity," I said. "He's come to expect a strong Weasley presence."

"Sorry, mate. Lavender thinks I'm a werewolf, and it's the night of the full moon. If she sees me, she'll hex me for sure."

"And break up with you," Ginevra chirped.

"Right. She'd probly do that, too," he agreed.

"I suppose we could do it up here," I muttered, glancing around the Boys' Dormitory. "You might want to put on robes first, though."

"Let us begin our latest meeting of the Junior Order of the Phoenix," I declared.

I stood on Ron's bed. Below me, Hermione, Ron, Ginevra, and Neville sat cross-legged on the floor. I made a show of slowly surveying them. "It looks like everyone is here, so we shall move on to our first order of business: What have we heard from our mother organization?"

Ron snorted. "The Order's telling us nothing."

"Dumbledore did ask us to disband, though," Ginevra said.

"He does that pretty often," Neville said.

"Order. Order. Calm yourselves," I said, gesturing for them to settle down. "Let us move on to our next topic: What have we heard from our spies?"

"I have not heard anything from Bellatrix Lestrange for weeks," Hermione said, carefully enunciating each syllable. "I believe she may be dead."

Neville slumped forward, leaning his cheek against a loose fist. "No. I don't believe it."

"Well, it was going to happen eventually," Ginevra said. "She overacts all the time."

"Yeah. Like anyone could ever be in love with V-Voldemort," Ron said, looking pleased to have stuttered out my hated, former name.

"We should not lose hope," I said. "Voldemort is too arrogant to suspect her. Bellatrix is probably fine. Now, let us discuss our group colors."

"I suggest red and gold," Hermione said.

"Who approves of that suggest – okay, he's gone," I said. "Nice job, guys. I love how you all sounded as if you had no idea what you were doing. Especially you, Ginevra."

"I've always wanted to be in a play, but we don't do those here. Or any other activities that aren't Quidditch," Ginevra said.

I grinned. "I suspect it's because the school is so old. People assume that, if we don't do something, it's because we don't do that here. And all the things that we started out doing have been outlawed for being too violent."

"Like the Triwizard Tournament?" Ron asked.

"Exactly," I said. "Of course, we did bring that back, so I suppose –"

"We just condemned a woman to death!" Hermione cried. "Are none of you even slightly upset about this?!"

I frowned. "Hermione, she's Bellatrix Lestrange."

"She tortured my parents into insanity," Neville said flatly.

"She's a Death Eater," Ron grunted.

"She tortured Neville's parents into insanity," Ginevra said.

Hermione's eyes darted between us until, finally, she groaned and buried her face in her hands. "Why am I the one everyone calls evil?"

"YOU KILLED MY SNAKE!"

Hermione looked quite justifiably horrified. "Oh, Harry. I'm so sorry. You startled me."

I clutched at the space around my neck where Ophion had just been. "THIS IS WHAT ALWAYS HAPPENS! YOU THROW AROUND DANGEROUS SPELLS AND KILL SWEET, INNOCENT THINGS!"

"For Merlin's sake, it was just a Jelly-Legs Jinx," she said. "I couldn't have known it would disappear."

"Really, Hermione? You couldn't have known? I save your life, you kill my pet, and that's all you have to say to me?"

"I'm sorry, alright?" Hermione snapped. "I can conjure you a new one."

"No, that won't work," I said. "You have to make Malfoy do it."

"I am not going to taunt Malfoy into throwing a snake at me!" Hermione shouted.

Ron shook his head, muttering, "Really? Seems like that's all you want, lately."

She whirled around, hissing, "Shouldn't you be off snogging Lavender or something?"

"I'll have you know she broke up with me 'cause she saw you sneaking off to the Boys' Dormitory and got the wrong impression," he said.

Hermione said, "Oh, so now that's my fault, too?"

"Maybe it is. Maybe, if you would spend more time paying attention to your friends and less time mooning over Malfoy, none of this would be happening!"

"I do not moon over Malfoy."

"Just stalking him, then?" he said.

I raised a hand, feeling dizzy. "Woah. You guys need to slow down for a second. I can't keep track of all these relationships."

I took a deep breath and continued, "Thankfully, I have people for that. Ginevra?"

The redhead ushered us into seats facing an empty wall, where Hermione and Ron continued sneering at each other. With a flick of Ginevra's wand, dozens of pictures flew onto the board.

She cleared her throat. "Ron's ex-girlfriend, as of this morning, is Lavender Brown. Lavender is currently trying to get together with my ex-boyfriend Dean –"

"That was quick, the bint," Ron grumbled. Hermione elbowed him in the ribs. A crowd had begun to gather, and Lavender threw a hex in Ron's direction.

"– but her first crush was Parvati Patil."

"It wasn't really a crush. We just practiced kissing together, so I would be better at it for guys like Won…I mean Deany," Lavender said.

Ginevra continued, "Now, Parvati may be a little too close to her twin, but no one talks about that for fear of being labeled a pervert. Padma likes Ron, possibly because he reminds her of her sister. Ron, meanwhile, is in love with Hermione Granger. But he hasn't realized that yet."

Ron yelped, "WHAT?!"

Hermione flushed, clearly uncomfortable with the scrutiny this declaration had earned her.

"Hermione also loves Ron, but she's waiting for him to grow up first. So it'll probly be a while. Hermione has also been stalking Draco Malfoy. Meanwhile, in the Slytherin dorms, Crabbe is dating Tracy but likes Daphne, and Goyle is dating Daphne but likes Tracy. This would be completely independent from the web, except that all of them are also stalking Draco Malfoy. Now, Draco likes his father, his money and spending inordinate amounts of time in the Room of Requirement."

"How do you know that?" Hermione asked. "I only figured it out a couple of days ago."

"Quiet," I said. "She's on a roll."

"Presumably, he uses it for disturbing and vaguely sexual purposes because Draco, like all Purebloods, is a pervert."

Ron's face twisted in confusion. "Gin, we're Purebloods."

"Nobody likes Neville," Ginevra continued, "but he likes Ginny Weasley. She hasn't noticed yet –"

"You –" Ron began, stopping short when Hermione set a hand on his shoulder.

"– because she has a HUGE crush on Harry Potter. Unfortunately for Ginny, Harry only likes inanimate objects and abstract concepts because his emotional development stalled somewhere around age eleven."

Hermione nodded, always eager to undermine my authority.

"I could widen the web to include people not directly connected and the younger years, but then I'd need a bigger wall," Ginevra finished apologetically.

"That isn't necessary," I assured her.

While Ginevra bowed to the Gryffindor common room, I turned to Hermione. "So, Draco's hanging out in the Room of Requirement, huh? We could do something about that."

"Malfoy can't get into the Room of Requirement?" Hermione said, pacing the common room. "How is that even possible?"

"I sealed the room, but it isn't foolproof. He can still collect the key, which I've broken into seven pieces and scattered across the castle. Once he's gathered them all, he'll realize that he didn't need a key. The true key was within him all along."

"So, he can get in, then?" Hermione said.

"Not for months."

She raised an eyebrow. "Why didn't you just lock the room and not leave the key lying around?"

"This is a ritual, Hermione," I said. "It's better than most magic but only works if you make it somewhat fair. Without a loophole, it isn't fair. For instance, the Fidelius will hide you from everybody, but you have to trust one person because you can't hide from everybody."

Hermione frowned. "I've never read about that before."

"It's Dark Magic."

"Huh," Hermione said, collapsing into a loveseat. "I guess I don't need to follow Malfoy around anymore."

"Not unless you want to," I agreed.

Hermione stared at the fireplace blankly. The distant squealing of Lavender Brown, new girlfriend of Dean Thomas, filled the silence. After a few minutes, she said, "I reorganized my schedule so that I would have plenty of time to investigate Malfoy. So, now, I don't actually have anything to do."

"You could always start recruiting for your Dark army."

She blinked at me, and I elaborated, "Ginevra is a good start, but now is the perfect time to network. Try getting the Slytherins. They're already trained to be minions."

"And to hate me," Hermione pointed out.

"It'll be fine. Just tell them you're a Pureblood."

Hermione laughed, no doubt delighted by my suggestion. "It isn't that simple, Harry."

"Of course it is. You say that you're from the Granger family, who are really famous in France, and they would know that if they weren't a bunch of backwards, untraveled hicks. They say that they'll check up on your story, but they never do."

"You're joking," she said.

"Happens all the time," I said. "I'm pretty sure Abraxas Malfoy was a Muggleborn. He said he was from France. Have you ever been to France? I've never been to France. I don't think Draco's been to France. If he has great-grandparents there, why hasn't he ever visited? WHERE ARE THE GREAT-GRANDMALFOYS?"

Hermione began massaging her temple (probably Lavender's fault). "You did not just accuse Draco Malfoy of being a half-blood."

"Of course not. Draco's a Pureblood. Lucius is the half-blood."

Hermione said, "Regardless, I've told plenty of people I'm a Muggleborn."

I nodded. Hermione had backed herself into a corner, and, once again, it was my job to rescue her.

"In that case, tell them that Muggleborns don't exist," I said.

Hermione merely raised an eyebrow, pointed at herself, and said, "Really?"

"No, hear me out here," I said. "What if all Muggleborn children are just magical children whose parents left them with memory-charmed Muggles and then died? Or maybe they just didn't want them."

Hermione said, "I'm sure that, if we ask Ron –"

"He wouldn't know," I said. "The Weasleys keep all of their children. That's why everyone thinks they're weird."

She sighed. "This is the most ludicrous thing I have ever heard in my life, and I've been friends with you for six years."

I stared her dead in the eyes. "Are you honestly telling me that you can't think of a single person who would charm a Muggle for free babysitting?"

Lavender's squeals split the air, and Hermione, defeated, trudged off to bed.

"…and cannot access the room where he's keeping all of his materials until he completes a quest," Lucius finished his report, placing a kiss on the hem of my robes.

"Hm. What sort of quest?" I asked.

"He must retrieve seven keys, hidden in Hogwarts," Lucius said.

I raised an eyebrow. "Are you sure the key isn't already in him?"

Lucius tensed for a crucio, silver hand curled into a fist. "I don't understand, my lord."

"You never really understand. It's more of a feeling…I presume this is Harry Potter's doing. The boy is a genius, after all."

Severus interjected, "Really? I wouldn't know. He's always been miserable at Potions, and he's failing Defense Against the Dark Arts. There are basic factual errors in all of his essays. I don't think he reads the textbook. Frankly, I'm not certain he reads."

"That you teach both those subjects doesn't make any difference at all, eh, Snape?" Sirius said. He lounged against the wall, a disrespect I would only allow from my right-hand man.

Severus sneered at him. "Potter's idiocy can hardly be blamed on me."

"Ah, come off it, Snape. We all know you hated James."

Severus said, "I assure you that I hate the boy on his own merits. While Potter, like his father, is a pompous glory hound, he is also undoubtedly a Slytherin."

Sirius growled, "You take that back!"

Snape merely smirked at the wand jabbed into his neck. I said, "Alright, let's all calm down. We've already lost enough people to Bellatrix's treachery."

In retrospect, her insistence on killing her fellow Death Eaters makes a lot more sense now. I continued, "So the previous plan is ruined, then?"

"Yes, my lord," Lucius said, trying to hide within his hair.

I sighed. "I suppose we'll just have to floo in, then."

Sirius blinked. "Wait, we can do that?"

I shrugged, rising from my throne. "I don't see why not."

A/N: While I changed the orphanage scene for my own amusement, it's worth noting that canon's young Tom Riddle is disturbingly like our Harrymort. He denies crimes he wasn't accused of, jumps to wild conclusions that he refuses to let go of, and is a total braggart. Seriously, check out HBP Ch. 13. It's freaking hilarious.

Chapter 16: HP vs Love (Pt 3)

Seventh Horcrux

Chapter 8: Harry Potter vs. Love (Pt. 3)

I tripped on my way outside of the pensieve, landing in a crumpled heap on the floor. I was viciously pleased when Dumbledore did the same, even if it was on me.

"Quite alright, my boy?" Dumbledore asked, standing and holding out a withered hand.

I grabbed the edge of his desk to haul myself up. "Fine. I was simply examining the floor for defects and found it woefully inadequate."

Dumbledore's eyes twinkled as I slumped into a chair, checking my robes for dirt. I found myself dizzy in ways unexplained by magical travel. We'd gone back to a particular class during my first time at Hogwarts, but that wasn't how I remembered that conversation at all.

Which led to the question: Was my memory faulty? Had someone obliviated me? Or oblivated Slughorn? I'm pretty sure I would recall if I had done that…Would I?

Also, what was that white fog? Potions fumes? I said, "Sir, I know the dungeons have always had ventilation problems, but was it really that bad back then?"

Dumbledore said, "That wasn't normal smoke, I'm afraid. It's proof of memory tampering."

"Who did it?" I asked. "Voldemort? A Death Eater? You? Professor –"

"He did it to himself, out of shame," Dumbledore said. "Whatever happened in that conversation has laid very heavily on Horace's conscience, very heavily indeed. It may be the very information we require to destroy Lord Voldemort."

I nodded.

"I need you to get that memory for me, Harry," Dumbledore said gravely.

It's important to remember that Dumbledore only calls people to his office when he wants to manipulate them into doing something for him. Or to manipulate them into learning some sort of moral lesson. Sometimes both.

It had been nearly a day since we first attempted to floo into Hogwarts.

Lucius had successfully made it through, but the green fire merely fizzled when Sirius tried to follow him. My right-hand man's robes still occasionally released puffs of smoke as we anxiously waited by the fireplace.

"Whaddaya bet he got captured and gave us all up?" Sirius said.

"Shut up, Black," Rodolphus Lestrange growled at him.

"Oh, come on. This is Lucy we're talking about. I bet he told them everything the moment they pointed a wand at him."

It seemed that, once again, Sirius Black had said what we were all thinking. I sighed heavily. "Well, Rookwood and Hagrid are watching the front door, so we're prepared if Dumbledore tries to break in. I presume the wards haven't alerted you of anything?"

Sirius grinned, no doubt thrilled to present me with good news. "Nope."

"I just don't understand how this happened. The plan was foolproof!" I said.

"I bet Bellatrix warned them," Sirius said.

Rodolphus sneered at him. "She's been dead longer than we've been planning this."

"Hey, she knew Trelawney," Sirius said. "Unless you're doubting our prophetess?"

"No, of course not," he muttered.

Earlier, I had ventured to the third floor, where the air is thick with exotic perfumes and ancient magic. There, I had found Trelawney hunched over a table. Her nose was half-flattened against her crystal ball, her eyes squeezed shut to better see with her third eye. While she had no clear visions of Lucius's whereabouts, or his likely betrayal, she insisted that we remain at Grimmauld Place. It was, she told me, our only hope.

I was torn from my musings as the fireplace roared to life. A robed figure stepped calmly from the green flames.

"Good evening, my lord, my fellow Death Eaters, Mutt," Severus said, nodding to each of us in turn but reserving a sneer for Sirius.

"What in Merlin's name happened?" I snapped.

"Apparently, an uninvited guest flooing into the Slytherin common room sends the entire castle into lockdown," Severus said. "We were stuck there for hours."

I frowned. "Has Lucius been captured, then?"

"No, my lord. When Dumbledore arrived to interrogate him, Lucius claimed that he was doing a surprise inspection for the Board of Governors. There was some suspicion when it turned out that the Board had not been aware of this, but he reminded us all that he did say it was a surprise," Severus drawled.

"That's Lucius. He's always been good at slithering out of trouble," Sirius said.

"Indeed. Now, why is Lucius not reporting his failure to me personally?" I stroked my wand, causing the entire group to shudder, save Sirius. There is a reason he's my right-hand man, after all.

Severus said, "He was invited to dinner, and Dumbledore expects him to perform a slightly less surprising inspection of the school before he leaves."

"How unfortunate," I muttered.

"In happier news," Severus said, "Potter nearly got himself killed doing some sort of Dark ritual."

It had been fifty-seven years since I'd visited the Hospital Wing, but it hadn't changed much. The sickly smell of potions filled the air, mingling with the citrus scent left by years of heavy cleaning charms. The bed was slightly too hard, to subtly discourage students from lingering, and, even through the bandages, I could still see its painfully white walls.

I heard Hermione lean towards me from her perch in the visitor's chair. "What have you learned today?"

"There's a reason wizards wear glasses. Eyes are complicated," I said.

She snorted. "True. What else?"

"Don't just read the summary of a ritual in the book. There might be warnings or better instructions later on," I said.

"What else?"

I frowned. "I can't think of anything else. I'm pretty sure those are the only things I learned from this experience."

"How about: Don't perform an untested ritual in the middle of a school-wide lockdown? Honestly, Harry, what were you thinking?!"

I shrugged. "I didn't want to be disturbed. It's not like I was invisible this time."

"Madame Pomfrey couldn't get to you for hours," Hermione said. "You could have died."

"Probably not died," I said. "Lost my eyes, maybe, but then I could just get better ones. Like Moody's."

"You are not getting fake, magical eyes."

I chuckled. "Well, obviously not now. The ritual didn't go that badly."

Hermione was silent for a time, probably reading. She does that a lot. "Harry, what was wrong with your old eyes?"

"Well, I did need glasses, and I wanted night vision."

"Why do you need night vision? You don't even do anything at night."

"Of course not. Without night vision, that would be stupid," I said.

I heard a soft smacking sound, likely Hermione's palm striking her forehead.

I added, "Also, I thought the whole slitted-pupil thing would look cool."

"You thought…" – Hermione took a long, deep breath – "It doesn't, Harry. It's creepy."

"Really? I thought you liked cats," I said.

A soft thump told me that she had leaned backwards into her chair, away from my bed. "This is ridiculous. It's not like your normal eyes aren't weird enough!"

"I've told you! Red is a perfectly normal color for wizards."

"Do you really expect me to believe that? No one else has red irises, Harry."

"You don't know everyone. There's a Fourth-Year Slytherin girl. Ask Ginevra. She knows."

She said, "Even Luna thinks they're odd. She doesn't think that about anything!"

"It's a very rare trait, like Parseltongue," I said. "It only appears in particularly pure lines –"

"Your mother was a Muggleborn," Hermione said. I could sense her eyes rolling.

"You take that back!" I cried, lurching forward to point my wand in her general direction.

Hermione said, "Oh, come on. You've been complaining about your Muggle Aunt for years."

"Squibs happen. Sometimes they squibble back. For instance, the Evans family are descendants of Merlin's third daughter, who was disowned for marrying a halfblood."

Hermione groaned.

"If I'm not a descendant of Merlin," I continued, proudly tapping my chest with my wand, "then how did I kill Voldemort as a baby?"

After a long pause, Hermione asked, "Harry, are you in a lot of pain or something?"

"There is some stinging while the optic nerve tries to reconnect," I said.

"Good," she said. "Usually your lies are better than this. No one is gullible enough to believe this tripe."

I smirked. "You don't talk to Slytherins much, do you?"

"I hardly think the house of the cunning would –"

I shook my head. "You're looking at this like a Muggleborn. The Slytherins think that blood matters and know that I'm amazing at magic. So, I've given them two choices: They can either believe my ridiculous story, or they can accept that a half-blood is just innately better at them in terms of everything, fundamentally changing their worldview. Which choice do you think they pick every time?"

"That actually makes a scary amount of sense. But, seriously, what is wrong with your eyes?"

She was never letting this go. I exclaimed, "Fine! Dumbledore thinks that it's because my mother loved me a lot. I'm pretty sure that's his way of saying that she dabbled in blood magic."

The stack of cards and candies left by my hospital bed didn't surprise me. I was the most powerful student at Hogwarts, a genius, and the Boy-Who-Lived. Further, I would likely achieve professorship soon enough to teach the younger years. Attempts to curry favor were to be expected.

But one of the gifts lay unsigned: A box of chocolates wrapped in a bow.

Lounging on my bed in the Gryffindor dormitory, I plucked a chocolate from the box and examined it. It was homemade, certainly, and it's easy enough to pour some potion in the mixing bowl. A quick sniff revealed a cloying scent, though that could be the result of too much sugar, and another round of detection spells revealed the same result as before: It had been tampered with.

I should have thrown it out days ago, but curiosity stayed my hand. Was it a love potion, a prank item from the Weasley twins, or another assassination attempt?

The poison-detecting spells only told me that something was there. But that gave no insight into who was attacking me. Until I knew that, I couldn't retaliate.

I was tempted to take a bite of the chocolate just to find out. Thankfully, I have people for that.

"Ron, taste these for poison."

The redhead jumped a bit in surprise, whipping his head towards me with a startled, "What?"

"Just kidding," I assured him.

He frowned. "Uh, mate, you're doing that thing where you say you're kidding, but then you get this smug look on your face that makes me pretty sure you aren't."

I glared at him. "Excuse me for trying to be nice. All I wanted to do was offer you chocolate, but then you doubted me."

Ron's eyes glazed over at the mention of chocolate. His mind is incapable of keeping track of two things at once, and food will always be his priority.

With a triumphant smirk, I continued, "Fortunately for you, I am a kind and generous master. Would you like some chocolate?"

In retrospect, I probably shouldn't have let him eat the entire box.

"Well, Ron's managed to overdose on love potion," I declared, descending the Boys' staircase.

Hermione's eyes widened, and she scrambled towards her bag in search of her Potions' textbook. "Will he be alright?"

I slumped into the nearest chair. "He'll be fine. We'll be miserable."

Hermione flipped open her book, asking, "Do you know what kind of potion?"

"Hard to tell. It was fairly fast-acting. Definitely not Amortentia. Wrong scent," I said. "We lucked out, really. At least he can't embarrass himself, this way."

Hermione glanced up from her book. "What do you mean?"

"Between the ridiculous amount of potions in his system and all the chocolate he ate, he can't stand. Of course, I tied him down to be sure. We should probably induce vomiting, soon, if he hasn't already."

"W-what?" Hermione's voice squeaked. Huh. I'd never taken her for the squeamish type. "Harry, we should probably take him to the Hospital Wing –"

I shook my head. "Ron can't run to the Hospital Wing every time something happens. He's there enough because of his lycanthropy."

"Ron is not a werewolf," Hermione said, studying a page on bezoars.

"He'll never accept himself if you keep making excuses for him."

"We can ask Slughorn –"

I shook my head. "He'll demand payment. Trust me, you don't want to owe him."

She scowled at me. "We can buy an antidote, then!"

I stared at her in horror. "Ron can't afford that!"

"We're the ones who'll be paying," she said.

I felt the familiar sting of betrayal. "I finally discover my family fortune, and the Weasleys are already trying to steal it. I always knew this would happen, but I didn't expect it so soon."

"Harry, we can't just let him sit up there in love with some love potion-brewing witch!"

"Yes we can."

Hermione gaped at me in a very Weasley fashion.

I sighed. "Hermione, look. We can't just bail Ron out every time he eats something he shouldn't. This is the only way he'll build up an immunity."

"I'm fairly certain there's no such thing as an immunity to love potions," Hermione said.

"Of course there is," I said. "You just tie yourself up and throw up every time it happens. Eventually, you become nauseous the second you feel the effects of a love potion."

Hermione's lips pursed, and her eyes grew distant as if solving a complex Arithmancy equation. "So…anytime you feel love, then?"

I shrugged. "I guess. Isn't it different when a potion causes it?"

"I'm not sure," Hermione said, appearing deeply concerned at her lack of knowledge.

Meanwhile, Ron's wailing had apparently overpowered my Silencing Charm.

"Romilda Vane!" he cried. It could have been worse, I suppose. At least he wasn't in love with his sister.

"We'll have to watch him in shifts to make sure he doesn't accidentally kill himself. There's also a key period about six hours in when he's both obsessed enough to attempt escape and lucid enough to succeed. We should probably double up on that shift."

Hermione was silent for a few moments, no doubt memorizing my instructions, before sighing and heading towards the Boys' Dormitory.

Over her shoulder, she said, "Right. I'm taking him to the Hospital Wing."

I stood upon my bed, smiling at the three students gathered below me.

"Welcome to this emergency meeting of the Junior Order of the Phoenix. Not many of you could make it, so let's keep this short. Bellatrix is definitely dead, right?"

"Yup!" Ginevra chirped. "Our spies were really upset about it."

"No surprise, there," Neville said. "After all, Rodolphus and Bellatrix were so in love. So very in love."

"At least their child lives on as a symbol of what's been lost," Luna said happily.

I blinked. "Wait, they had a kid? Why was I not informed of this?"

"It's a secret. The people in on it probably wanted to spare your feelings," she said. "You have Bellatrix's eyes, you know."

"Luna, I am not the lovechild of Bellatrix and Rodolphus Lestrange," I said slowly. "I'm pretty sure we would have noticed that before. Wouldn't we have?"

"Definitely!" Ginevra said.

Neville said, "Don't you have something to say. About this situation. And how odd it is."

I suddenly remembered the purpose of today's meeting and returned to our script. "Oh. Yes, it's very strange that Voldemort hasn't caught our other spies yet."

Ginevra said, "Especially since they're our old spy's husband and brother-in-law. Does he really think they hadn't notice that she'd switched sides?"

"Well, Dumbledore always said that Voldemort doesn't understand basic human relationships," I mused. "Also, he's an idiot."

At that moment, I slammed my head against the bedpost as hard as I could.

Well, it wasn't me, exactly. It was Voldemort. I could feel the faint echoes of his fury as he retreated from my head.

"You have done well," I said, rubbing at my forehead. "I am mildly grateful to you all for gathering on such short notice."

"Anytime," Neville said, grinning. I feared that his bloodthirstiness would soon rival Hermione's.

Luna giggled. "I was just following the Wrackspurts."

"I'll do anything for you," Ginevra said. Bellatrix was dead, but it seemed that her legacy lived on.

"We probably shouldn't tell Hermione about this," I said. "She'll only get upset, and she's already busy planning vengeance for Ron."

Dumbledore stood as I entered his office, his sleeve swooshing down to cover his blackened hand. Shrugging the invisibility cloak off of my shoulders, I held up a silvery vial.

Dumbledore said, "I didn't expect you so soon, my boy. Surely Horace didn't part with his memories easily."

Dumbledore was right. The manipulation required to convince Slughorn would take far too much time and effort to be worth the trouble. So I'd decided to use my memory of the conversation.

"I am his favorite student," I said. "Although you probably shouldn't mention this to him. I had to obliviate him of the incident."

Dumbledore sighed, clearly disappointed that I was operating independently of his orders. "Was that truly necessary?"

"It was for his own protection," I said airily, wandering over to the pensieve and uncorking the vial.

We leaned forward, tumbling deep into the basin before thudding onto the floor of the Potions' classroom. Slughorn was busy telling me that I would make a great Minister of Magic (still true). The man paused thoughtfully when I mentioned the word, Horcrux. "That's very Dark stuff, Tom. Very Dark."

"That's why I asked you about it," my younger self said.

I meant to imply that he was a knowledgeable and influential pureblood. Depending on the definition he was using, however, he might have translated it to mean something along the lines of: I think you enjoy torturing small animals in your spare time.

Of course, that made no sense in context, so I presume he understood. If he didn't, he probably would have refuted the statement.

"…A Horcrux is the word used for an object in which a person has concealed part of their soul," Slughorn prattled on.

My younger self frowned. "I don't quite understand how that works, though, sir."

"Well, you split your soul, you see –"

"No, I understand the mechanics. I meant to say: What is a soul?"

Dumbledore appeared deeply troubled, and Slughorn laughed weakly. "Surely you know what a soul is, Tom."

Irritation colored Tom Riddle's tone. "I understand the concept, sir. But this isn't some vague idea of your mind or emotions or anything like that. It's a physical object. You can cut it."

"It's more of a tear," Slughorn said.

He nodded. "Tear it, then. So, does it go perfectly in half every time? Or does just a sliver come off? How big is the soul? Let's say you make, I don't know, ten Horcruxes."

"Ten!" Slughorn exclaimed.

Tom continued, "At what point would you run out of soul? What if more of your soul is in the objects than in you? Can you walk around with nearly no soul? Does that have negative consequences?"

I'd actually learned the answer to that last one. The Horcrux-making process isn't harmful at all. In fact, it hurt less every time, so it probably makes you better.

Slughorn chortled. "The only people who make Horcruxes are insane Dark Lords. No one's researched this, Tom."

My younger self softly said, "What a pity."

Dumbledore and I fell upwards, through the ceiling and back into his office. He turned to me, asking, "Do you understand what you must do?"

"I need to make Horcruxes of my own," I said firmly.

Dumbledore frowned, reaching over to stroke Fawkes. "Ah, no, I'm afraid not."

I said, "Are you sure? Slughorn really sold me on it."

"Quite sure, my boy. You see, Voldemort's Horcruxes are what's kept him alive all these years" – Dumbledore scowled – "He may have as many as ten."

"No he doesn't," I said. After a moment, I rephrased. "I mean: NO! I don't believe it."

"As much as I wish to think the same, Voldemort has always been a twisted man," Dumbledore said. "If you'll excuse me, I have much to think on, and, if you hurry, you might be on time for Defense Against the Dark Arts."

I strolled towards the door, looking forward to a peaceful hour in the Gryffindor common room.

Lucius bowed to me before entering the sitting room. He nodded coolly to Severus and Sirius, as well, then said, "I have a new plan, my lord."

Sirius grinned. "Does this one suck, too?"

"My plans do not suck," Lucius hissed, shaking his silver fist at the man.

"To be fair, that flooing idea was atrocious," I said.

Lucius looked as if he had just sucked on a lemon. He never was any good with constructive criticism. "I assure you, this one is better."

"Didja check it with Trelawney?" Sirius asked.

"Not yet," Lucius said.

"Well, what are you waiting for? Unless you want to waste our lord's time with a plan that's doomed to failure."

Lucius stormed away, glaring at anyone who dared to look at him. Severus turned to Sirius, drawling, "You haven't changed in the slightest, Black. Still the same impudent, attention-seeking, bullying…"

Severus trailed off as Sirius bowed repeatedly to an imaginary audience. A few minutes later, he straightened, grinning. "Yup! That's me. Sirius Black, at your service."

"I hate you," Severus said. Sirius threw an arm around his shoulder, ruffling the other man's hair. Severus's wand snapped into his hand.

"Now, may I explain my plan?" Lucius asked from the doorway.

Sirius let go of Snape, playfully shoving him forward. "I dunno. That seemed awfully fast. I bet you didn't talk to Trelawney, at all. What do you think, Snape?"

"One of these days, I will kill you in your sleep," Severus said.

"So, you agree with me, then," Sirius said.

Lucius said, "I moved quickly because I didn't have to explain anything to her. She already knew and approved. Unless you're doubting our seer, Black?"

Sirius put up his hands in a gesture of surrender. "No, never. That woman's a genius."

"My lord?" Lucius implored, turning towards me.

I really did want the man to redeem himself after his earlier failures. He was such a good minion. With a thin, lipless smile, I said, "Go ahead, Lucius."

"I was speaking with the Board of Governors. It seems there's been a sudden drop in academic performance. Several parents have expressed concern. Therefore, I suggested that we choose a day to allow parents into the school. That way, they can see their children and discuss their issues with his or her head of house."

"I fail to see how this is relevant to our plans to kidnap Harry Potter," Severus said.

"I find it completely obvious," I announced. "Continue, Lucius, for Severus's sake."

Lucius smiled weakly. "Of course, my lord. Many of your Death Eaters have children in Hogwarts. It would be perfectly reasonable for them to visit."

"That's brilliant!" I declared. "We can even send in Sirius Black."

"Uh, how's that work?" Sirius asked.

"You are Harry Potter's godfather. Or was I misinformed of this?" I asked, sending a warning glare in Lucius's direction.

"Well, yeah, but I'm pretty sure somebody else is taking care of him, now."

"You would think that, but you would be wrong," Severus drawled.

Sirius said, "Oh, come on. They must have given him to Remus."

Severus said, "He's a werewolf."

"Alice Longbottom was his godmother –"

"Tortured into insanity by Bellatrix Lestrange."

"Right. She always did like that sort of thing," Sirius muttered. "What about the rest of the Potters?"

"They disappeared," Severus said. "It was very mysterious."

"Probably my fault," I admitted.

Sirius set his mouth in a firm line. "Dumbledore."

"Pawned the boy off on Muggles."

Sirius wrinkled his nose. "Oh, he's one of those wizards. Who were the Muggles?"

"Lily's sister and her family," Severus said.

"That bint?" Sirius barked. "He'd have been better off with you."

Severus raised an eyebrow. "I am a Death Eater."

"And a werewolf," Lucius added. "I think we've all heard the rumors."

"Clearly, Sirius has the best claim to Potter," I said. "Therefore, it wouldn't be strange at all for him to go in with the other parents."

"Totally normal," Sirius agreed.

Lucius's eye twitched. "My lord –"

"Leave me, Lucius," I said, waving the blond away. "I'm scheming."

I'd successfully avoided the Hospital Wing for decades, yet there I was mere days after my last visit. I sighed, making my way over to the bed where Ron was clutching a small mountain of letters to his chest. He stopped glaring at Hermione when he caught sight of me.

"Harry!" Ron cried. "Harry, Harry, Harry! You…you gotta help me, mate. You have to take these letters to Romilda Vane."

I sneered at him. "I'm not your servant. Have Hermione do it."

"I don't trust her. She burned the last ones. I think she's jealous," he said.

I nodded. "She's probably still upset about Draco, though I can't say I understand the attraction. The boy's a terrible coward. He hasn't attempted any of my trials."

"I am not attracted to him. I never was." Hermione believes that, if she says something enough times, it will suddenly be true.

"So, so, you'll help me?" Ron asked. Before I could respond, he gushed, "You are the best. My best mate. These are all for my Romillie, 'cept this one. It's for Remus."

Hermione frowned, snatching the letter over Ron's protests. "Professor Lupin?"

"His life is so haaaaard," Ron whined. "You should let him join your army. I think he'd like that."

Hermione groaned. "I don't have an army."

I smirked. "Do you spend all of your time in denial, or just most of it?"

"Come on," she said with a roll of her eyes. "We have letters to deliver."

As we left the Hospital Wing's doorway, Hermione set my pile of letters ablaze. I yelped, dropping them to the floor as she said, "I hope he's better by the time his parents visit."

"His parents?" I asked.

"For the parent-teacher conferences, of course," Hermione said primly.

"Right, I think I heard about that," I said.

"Not many Gryffindor parents are coming. It's mostly Slytherins."

"I'm not surprised," I said. "I hear they still don't have any furniture."

"Apparently, some idiot put Sirius Black's name up as a joke," she said, lips pursed in disapproval.

"Speaking of idiots, I didn't expect Ron to still be so out of it. I thought Pomfrey was going to give him the antidote."

Hermione's voice was flat. "She did."

I winced. "Oh."

Carrying Ron's letter to Lupin towards the Owlery, she said. "Honestly, how much love potion did Vane give him?"

The boat slid soundlessly across the lake, not even a ripple left in its path. I peered down at its Inferi inhabitants, looking for anyone I recognized, and exclaimed happily upon spotting Dorcas Meadows. Sitting across from me, Dumbledore seemed to be directing an imaginary symphony with his blackened hand.

"Headmaster?" I said. "I'm glad you took me on this journey and hope that you will continue to do so for all subsequent Horcrux-gathering missions, but…Don't you have parent-teacher conferences today?"

Dumbledore chuckled. "No, no, parents would only come to me if they had a problem with one of the professors. I have the greatest confidence that such a thing won't be necessary."

I raised an eyebrow. "So, you're avoiding all the complaints about Snape, then?"

"Dear boy, I'm hunting Horcruxes. I dare say this is the more pressing concern," Dumbledore said. I sometimes wonder why I am the only person who notices his selfish manipulations.

"You could have done this tomorrow," I pointed out.

"Perhaps, but then you would have missed class."

"Or yesterday."

"And rob you of a well-earned weekend?" he asked, shaking his head dramatically.

We disembarked and approached a potion-filled basin at the island's center.

Dumbledore looked at me gravely. "I'm afraid that this potion cannot be banished or physically removed. The only way to get to the locket inside is to drink it."

"I am not doing that!" I shouted, scrambling towards the safety of the Inferi-infested lake.

"Of course not," Dumbledore assured me with a cold smile. "I am the one who shall drink it. I suspect it will be terribly painful, possibly deadly. You may even have to force-feed me, in the end –"

"Woah, woah, woah," I said, waving my wand around to get his attention. "That seems pretty extreme."

I was not going be the sole witness to Albus Dumbledore's mysterious death. That would raise all sorts of suspicions, and then no one would let me work with children.

"It's a ritual," Dumbledore said. "To take a part of Voldemort's being, I must give a part of mine."

"Voldemort's paranoid, though. He probably wouldn't want to poison someone to death every time he checked on his Horcrux, right?"

Dumbledore nodded slowly. "I suppose."

"So, he probably put in a back door. A password or something. In Parseltongue."

I stepped forward, hissing, "Slytherin. Slither out."

It may seem cheesy, but that's actually the most complicated pun you can make in Parseltongue.

Dumbledore seemed surprised (almost certainly a ruse) as the emerald potion drained from the basin. "Harry, how did you know the password?"

"There are only three syllables in Parseltongue. It's mostly a matter of context and intonation."

"You're a Parselmouth, then?" he said.

"Yeees," I said slowly.

Dumbledore leaned forward, peering into my eyes atop his half-moon glasses. "Harry, were you the Heir of Slytherin?"

"No!" I snapped. "I don't know why everyone thinks that."

"It's alright if you were. No one was hurt, and you've been a paragon of the Light ever since," he said.

"I'm not the Heir," I grumbled, snatching the locket from the now-empty basin.

I looped it around my neck as we rode silently back across the lake. Something bothered me, however. The balance was off, too light and slightly lopsided, possibly a result of its prolonged exposure to the poisonous potion, but still…

I opened the locket, and a taunting note fell out.

Elsewhere, Lord Voldemort felt a sudden and inexplicable flash of rage.

"You must look at the bright side, my boy."

I glared at him.

Dumbledore cheerfully continued, "At least Voldemort does not possess the locket."

That was half of the problem. Voldemort should have the locket, and, by Voldemort, I mean its rightful owner: Me.

"And I didn't drink a mysterious yet certainly dangerous potion to retrieve a mere decoy."

I threw the locket at him, and the wizard happily pocketed it.

We came upon the gates of Hogwarts, which were badly dented and hung half-open. The grounds were torn up, and several trees had been slashed with a sword. Families were still hanging around, trading tearful goodbyes or nursing minor wounds. Among them were Ron (telling his family all about the love of his life), Ginevra (whose hair was several inches shorter than earlier that day), and Neville (with a bloody sword slung across his shoulders).

Luna was trying to balance on one foot, but, when she spotted me, her enthusiastic wave sent her tumbling to the grass. "Hello, Harry."

"Honestly, I leave the grounds for one day and everything ends up destroyed. What in Merlin's name happened?"

"WHAT IN MERLIN'S NAME HAPPENED?" I roared, glaring at my bedraggled group of Death Eaters.

Sirius Black shoved Lucius forward, natural since it was his foolish plan that had led to this mess. "My lord, I'm afraid that someone recognized Sirius Black and mobilized an attack."

"Can't imagine why. He's been on the conference list for some time," Severus drawled.

"It turns out that several members of the Order of the Phoenix have children at the school and were battle-ready," Lucius said.

"Some kid showed up with the Sword of Gryffindor, which was bloody awesome," Sirius added.

"I, for one, was shocked," Severus said. "Longbottom is failing Defense Against the Dark Arts."

Fenrir Greyback said, "Then there was some Weasley babbling about Werewolf Rights."

"Mr. Weasley is well known for his idiocy," Severus said.

"He had some pretty good points, actually. I tried to turn him, but he got me with a stunner," Fenrir said, rubbing his still-frozen arm.

"That was crazy," Goyle said. "That Romilda Vane girl sure is lucky."

"I dunno what that blonde chick was doing, but we still haven't found Rookwood," Sirius said.

"…and, then, it turned out that Potter had left on some sort of field trip, so we retreated," Lucius finished.

"I see," I murmured, stroking Slytherin's locket. Earlier, I'd had a sudden urge to check on the Horcrux, only to nearly trip over its pedestal on the way out the door.

I asked, "Sirius, is there any particular reason this locket was sitting in your parlor?"

My right-hand man shrugged. "Maybe you gave it to me for safekeeping?"

The locket jostled slightly at my nod, then settled warmly against my chest. "Right. That does seem like something I would do."

"…fifty points to Luna Lovegood. For the most exquisite haircut I've seen since my childhood, fifty points to Ginevra Weasley. For identifying Sirius Black and dueling him to a standstill, fifty points to Hermione Granger…"

Apparently, the latest battle had created quite a few heroes. Dumbledore had been going on for twenty minutes. His skin was grey, his eyes dull, yet still he spoke. The students were whispering among themselves, and even the castle was beginning to grow anxious, if the dancing silverware was any indication.

"…For Gryffindor bravery, quick feet, and sharp wit, fifty points to Neville Longbottom…"

The students laughed, clapping Neville on the back. I'm not sure why. Dumbledore was clearly insulting him.

"…For a stunning performance, fifty points to Ronald Weasley. Finally –"

A loud cheer greeted this statement, and Dumbledore paused until it quieted. "For demonstrating foreign language proficiency in a poisonous situation, fifty points to Harry Potter. It appears that Gryffindor has won the Cup. Congratulations to Gryffindor and to everyone who fought in this battle. Now, I can hear your stomachs rumbling from here. So, without further ado –"

"May I speak, Headmaster?" I said, standing up to survey the disappointed crowd.

Dumbledore sighed. "Mr. Potter, you no longer have the authority to add or remove points."

"That's fine," I said with a negligent wave of my wand. I turned to the crowd. "Many of you fought bravely, yesterday. Many more of you hid like firsties, most especially the firsties. Clearly, the Dark Lord is a dangerous foe, willing to hurt children on a whim and ready to take Wizarding Britain under his reign. Keeping that in mind, I would like to announce that I am no longer neutral on the Voldemort Issue."

I sat down, and the Leaving Feast appeared with a joyous pop.

A/N: Merry Christmas, everyone...and a joyous Thursday to everyone else!

Chapter 19: HP vs Himself (Pt 3)

Seventh Horcrux

Chapter 9: Harry Potter vs. Himself (Pt. 3)

Draco Malfoy wandered outside of the DADA classroom, a thoughtful and solitary figure. As he passed a dusty side-corridor, no doubt created during the castle's recent shuffling, I muttered, "Accio Malfoy."

Malfoy's gasp mingled with a more distant yelp as he stumbled towards us. With a nervous glance around the seemingly empty corridor, Malfoy said, "P-Potter?"

I whipped off the cloak, revealing Hermione and myself. Striding towards him, I said, "What gave me away? The strength of my spell-casting? The brilliance of my plan? The subtle scent of –"

"You were invisible," he said.

I paused, not at all appreciating Hermione's giggles. "Right, yes, I suppose that makes sense."

Malfoy glanced back towards the entranceway, which shimmered with invisibility and silencing spells. "What are you doing here, Potter? You shouldn't have…wait, have you been here all year, skulking around under your cloak?"

I leaned casually against the wall, arms crossed. "Perhaps."

Hermione rolled her eyes. "No."

"I could have been," I said.

"That doesn't change the fact that you weren't," Hermione said, maliciously diminishing my reputation.

Malfoy drummed his fingers against his wand, body half-turned towards the exit. "You still haven't explained what you're doing here."

"I have a proposition for you" – I twirled my wand between my fingers – "How would you like to join Hermione's Dark Army?"

"Harry, you are not –"

I raised a hand to silence her. "Quiet, Hermione. If you aren't going to be proactive, then I'll have to do this for you."

"Granger has an army," Malfoy said, still too blinded by Hermione's innocent image and his own lingering feelings to imagine it.

I nodded. "We're still in the early recruiting stages, which offers you a chance to get in on the ground floor. With Hermione's brilliant, vicious mind and your financial resources, as well as the lessons you've learned from my trials, you could completely replace the government within a decade. I understand that you may be reluctant to follow someone with lesser blood than you. I can assure you, however, that that would not be the case in this instance."

"You will not –" Hermione cut off as my Silencing Spell hit her.

She glared daggers at me, but I spoke firmly. "He has a right to know."

I turned back to the curious blond with a smile. "Rowena Ravenclaw had a second daughter, a squib. She never talked about her, of course, because she was a squib."

Malfoy sneered. "Understandable."

"That daughter had children of her own. Eventually, her descendants moved to Australia where their magical blood rekindled to form the Granger family. Generally, the Grangers have been an odd and reclusive clan, keeping well away from even the Australian magical society. Upon discovering their relation to a Hogwarts founder, however, they chose to send their latest child to study abroad."

Hermione had finally worked off the Silencing Charm. "I am not the Heiress of Ravenclaw."

"Really? If it isn't true, then why are you denying it?" I demanded.

Taken aback by my stunning logic, she turned to the much more gullible Malfoy. "You don't believe this tripe!"

"It would explain a few things," he admitted. "But, no, you're actively denying it, and I've learned my lesson about listening to Potter."

"Oh, thank Circe," Hermione sighed.

"I hope you'll still join," I said. "Despite Hermione's incessant secret-keeping."

Malfoy frowned, clearly put off by the heiress's antics. "I suppose."

"Wonderful!" I exclaimed. "First order of business: Eliminating the competition. Hermione?"

Malfoy let out a strangled squeak as my best minion explained, "We've been collecting several objects necessary to kill You-Know-Who. All we need is the Diadem of Ravenclaw –"

"Hermione's family heirloom," I interjected.

"Unfortunately, it's still in the Room of Requirement, which is locked."

"Luckily, you" – I tapped him on the chest with my wand – "Have part of the key. I figure we can get the rest by dinner."

Malfoy raised an eyebrow. "Dinner? It took me over a year to get the last five pieces."

"I designed it to be completed in about three months," I said. "Trust me, we'll be in by dinner."

Malfoy's eye twitched.

I smirked. "Hermione, you can grab Ron and the trunk while we tackle the next trial. Meet us at the Room of Requirement."

"Alright." Hermione cast a Disillusionment Charm on herself.

"Draco, I need you to throw a snake at me."

Malfoy paused for a moment. "Mind repeating that, Potter?"

"Throw a snake at me!" I cried. "Quickly. There's no time to explain."

Draco threw a snake at me. I recognized the pattern of black and green scales immediately. "Ophion!"

The snake peered upwards, scenting the air. "You are a speaker?"

"You don't remember me?" I asked.

The snake hissed a no. With a heavy sigh, I vanished it.

"Harry!" Hermione snapped. "Why did you do that?"

"He wasn't the same, so I killed him," I explained.

Malfoy paled and demonstrated an appropriate level of fear and awe by taking a step away from me. Hermione groaned. "Harry, are you under the Imperius again?"

"…and he kept planning partner activities even though I was the only one who attended class!" Draco ranted.

I thoughtfully caressed my wand. "So you would consider the Dark Lord a fairly bad professor, then?"

"Yes," Draco said. "I mean, he's probably the best DADA teacher I've ever had, but he's still horrible."

While talking, we had entered the third floor corridor which sometimes held the entrance to the Room of Requirement. Ron and Hermione were waiting for us by the locked door, and Hermione hurried over. "Oh, good, I was worried you would…Is Malfoy wearing leather pants?"

I glanced at the tight, black pants Draco was currently sporting. "Technically, it's dragon hide. It protects you from fire."

"Yes, but why?" she pressed, yet again demonstrating her intense curiosity about the world at a wildly inappropriate time.

"Dragons breathe fire. It's a part of their metaphysical nature –"

"Not that," Hermione snapped. "Why is he wearing them?"

I glanced towards the door to confirm that Ron and Hermione had not suddenly swapped places. "To protect him from fire, of course."

She pinched the bridge of her nose. "Then why isn't he wearing a shirt?"

"It caught on fire. For Merlin's sake, Hermione, keep up!"

Ron, noticing Draco's shirtless state, came over to glare at him. "I still don't trust you. Why are you even helping us, anyway?"

"I don't believe in the Dark Lord's tenets anymore…excepting the Creatures Rights laws," Draco said. "The fourth trial taught me a lot about acceptance, and I can't seem to unlearn it."

Ron snorted. "So you're suddenly our friend?"

Draco crossed his arms over his bare chest and sneered. "Don't worry Weasel, I still think you're a pathetic, idiotic Gryffindork."

"You didn't mention that he's poor," I pointed out.

"The second trial taught me what it's like to have nothing" – Draco smirked – "I imagine that how Weasley feels all the time."

"I DO NOT!" Ron roared, jabbing his wand against Draco's chest.

Hermione batted it down with her own wand, glaring at them. "Enough! Let's stop bickering and go into the room."

Draco paused. "…We can't."

"Why not?" Hermione said coldly, Ron looming above her.

Draco pulled six silver objects from his dragon hide pants. They glowed slightly where they touched each other. "The key still isn't complete."

"Right, yes, I almost forgot about that" – I rifled through my pockets – "Here you go, Draco."

Draco stared at the item in my hand. "You had the final piece."

"The whole time."

He snatched the rest of the key, glowering at the three of us. "Then it wasn't fair at all!"

"Sure it was. You could have learned a lesson about friendship or espionage or possibly seduction."

Ron asked, "Is that why he's not wearing a shirt?"

"But you weren't even in the castle this year," Draco said.

"Yet, when you needed the final piece, I was. Perhaps, I always would have been."

Draco growled at me and, with a burst of light, the pieces united into an ornate, silver key. He stomped towards the door and stuck it into the lock.

The key broke, its pieces disappearing, and the door remained closed.

The blond whirled around, glowering. "It broke."

I hurried forward. "Draco, don't you deserve to get in?"

Draco sneered. "Of course I do. I did all your stupid trials."

"And learned so many lessons," I mused. "If you truly deserve to go in, then why would you need a key?"

"You're kidding me," he said flatly.

I placed a hand on his shoulder. "Draco, open the door."

Young Malfoy turned the knob and the door smoothly opened.

"You see?" I said. "The true key was within you all along. All you had to do was believe in yourself!"

Draco gazed into the Room of Requirement, which was empty save for the pedestal holding Ravenclaw's Diadem. "I spent a year and a half tracking down the key pieces, all for a key that I didn't need."

I chuckled, pushing past him. "Just because the key doesn't open the door doesn't mean you don't need the key."

My three minions followed me inside.

"Ravenclaw's Diadem," Hermione breathed. She collapsed against the doorway to gaze upon her ancestor's artifact.

I grinned, opening my trunk to store the Diadem with my other Horcruxes.

"You aren't putting it on?" Ron asked.

I blinked. "What?"

"Y'know, the Diadem. The whole point of it is to put it on, right? It makes you smarter and stuff."

Hermione clucked her tongue. "It's a strange magical artifact that may very well be cursed. Of course he isn't just tossing it on his –"

"Merlin, I'm so stupid. So many missed opportunities, so many overlooked alliances, so many times I shouldn't have gotten drunk…"

"You put it on" – Hermione sighed – "Of course you did."

She thought I'd been acting foolishly, but she was wrong. Her point regarding the possibility of my Diadem being cursed was a fair one, particularly considering the fact that it was cursed. However, this was the wisest thing I'd ever done.

I should have worn it years ago, rather than making the Horcrux. Or I even could have done both. Sure, people would try to steal it, but I would guard it heavily regardless of whether it contained my soul.

"Harry?" Ron asked weakly. He sounded cautious but concerned. Of course he did, he was fond of me. And I've proven myself to be somewhat childish. Even insane. What a fool I was.

"Harry, are you alright?" Hermione asked.

No, no I wasn't. I was an idiot. Why did I even want to be the Defense teacher, anyway? Or to be immortal? What was the point?

I grabbed the Diadem, flinging it towards Hermione. "Hermione, destroy it."

Hermione rolled her eyes. "It's a relic, Harry. I won't damage a vital piece of history simply because you don't like the truth. Besides, we need it for the ritual."

She put it on.

My eyes widened. "No! You fool. Take it off right now and perhaps you'll escape –"

"Merlin. I'm so stupid…"

Ron plucked it off her head. Hermione swayed, mumbling, "Oh, that really was awful."

Ron tucked it under his arm. Draco sneered. "Aren't you putting it on? You might finally learn what it's like to have normal intelligence."

Ron rolled his eyes and remarked, "Nah, I already know I've been dumb. Why? You want it?"

Draco paled. "You can keep it."

Ron shrugged, tossing it back to me. I slung it over my shoulder, which I imagine gained incredible insight into the world but was unable to share it due to being a shoulder.

Hermione, meanwhile, had approached Ron. She smiled. "When I was wearing the Diadem, I realized that we could be dead in a couple of hours and I never would have told you that I liked you. Which is just so absolutely stupid because you obviously like me too. So I was wondering if, perhaps, presuming the Diadem isn't cursed to give misleading information –"

Ron leaned down to kiss her, and she enthusiastically reciprocated. I watched, dumbfounded.

Ron and Hermione. Wow. I did not see that coming.

Draco turned away, unable to watch his first love with another man. I said, "I'm so sorry, Draco."

He raised an eyebrow and drawled, "Potter, I'm disgusted."

"Sure you are," I said, "but, if you ever need to talk about this, I can lend you Ginevra…Come to think of it, you can keep her."

Draco sneered at me, a sure sign that he was feeling better. "I don't want your girlfriend, Potter."

He'd even discovered his sense of humor!

I said, "We should get back to the rebel base to regroup. Along the way, Hermione can devise one of her evil schemes."

Hermione tore herself from the snog for an indignant: "I don't devise evil schemes!"

I rolled my eyes. "Fine. One of your regular schemes, then."

Hermione would find a way to make it evil.

Draco stood atop the staircase. Lost in thought, he steadied himself on the slimy wall. "Even after my trial down here, I'm still shocked that you ended up being the Heir."

"Why does everyone think that? It was Ginevra."

Draco snapped out of his reverie and snatched his hand from the muck-lined wall with a wet pop. After a panicked cleaning charm, he said, "A Weasley the Heir of Slytherin?"

Ron said, "Well, why not?"

"You're Gryffindors," he spat.

I chuckled. "Just because someone is a Gryffindor doesn't mean they aren't a Slytherin. Right, Hermione?"

Hermione pushed past us and into the darkness, muttering about morons (probably Ron's fault). We hurriedly followed.

I said, "To be fair, Ginevra is a seventh child."

Draco said, "You can't expect me to believe that the Weasleys managed to squeeze a Parselmouth from their impure blood, no matter how many children they pop out."

Ron's face flushed bright red, but his angry exclamation was cut short by a calm voice below us. "I'm quite certain Ginny's a Parselmouth. She taught me how to say my name in it and everything."

There is no word in that language which comes anywhere near Luna's name. I shudder to think what horribly mispronounced nickname Ginevra had bestowed upon the poor girl.

The blonde was cheerfully waiting at the bottom of the steps with Hermione, who said, "Luna's guarding the door."

"You aren't Death Eaters polyjuiced to look like you four, are you?" the blonde politely inquired.

Draco raised an eyebrow. "If that were the case, why would I be here?"

"I'm not sure why you're here, anyway," Ron muttered.

I said, "To be fair, the Death Eaters might have run out of polyjuice."

"That would be pathetic," Draco said.

"It sounds fairly typical for them, really," I mused.

Ron chose to use his brain, and, as always, the result was a terrible disappointment. "Could you even beat that many Death Eaters, Luna?"

Hermione pursed her lips. "It's more about sounding the alarm, Ronald."

"If she couldn't, why would they bother using polyjuice?" I added.

"I'll be fine. Neville even loaned me the Sword of Gryffindor." Luna hefted the sword and waved it at us.

Hermione's eye twitched. Violently. "You are a true Gryffindor."

"Not really," she said. "It's more about how you hold it."

"I –"

"Is that my House Elf?" Draco demanded, glaring into the Chamber where Dobby was scurrying about with a tray of sandwiches.

"Oh, yes," Luna said. "Apparently, he's been stealing from you for several years. I think he's a true Slytherin."

Draco's agitated gaze swept over the room, eyes widening when he reached a small crowd towards the center. "Snape?!"

"He's more of a Ravenclaw," Luna said.

Draco rushed over to the crowd. I sedately followed. With a casual Incarcerous to tie up Draco, Ginevra said, "Hi, Harry! I didn't know you were going to kidnap Malfoy."

"Hermione recruited him, actually," I said.

"Huh" – Ginevra glanced down at the struggling, rope-bound boy at her feet – "I guess she's wanted him for a while, so good for her."

I gestured towards the man bound to a wooden chair. "I see you've kidnapped Snape."

"Astute as ever, Potter," Severus said.

"We took him right from his office," Neville said, lifting up the Sorting Hat as an odd trophy. It remained inactive, still and deflated in his grasp.

Ginevra beamed. "We've got the Headmaster, so we're pretty sure we own the school, now."

"That's ridiculous. We're in the exact same situation we were this morning," Hermione said.

"Yeah, but now Snape can awaken the castle and drive out the invaders," Ginevra continued.

Hermione eyes fluttered at this new and overwhelming information. "Awaken…I'm sorry?"

I explained, "The castle is a living being, capable of controlling all within its walls."

"Only the Headmaster can call it to action, though," Ginevra said.

"Cute. Do you two practice this?" Draco spat from his position on the floor.

"Of course not. We're simply right," I said.

Severus watched our conversation with a sense of overwhelming boredom. "No. You are not."

I jabbed him in the chest with my wand. "Really? If the castle isn't sentient, then why does it hate us so much?"

Severus merely sighed. "Regardless, I have no such power."

"He could be lying," Neville said. "He probably isn't, but he could be."

I frowned. "No way to know for sure. He fooled Dumbledore for years. Our best bet is to kill him before he sows dissension in our ranks."

"Harry, we are not killing the Headmaster," Hermione said, again showcasing her hypocrisy.

"If we kill him, I'm pretty sure we become the Headmaster."

"They got rid of that rule in the thirteenth century," she said sharply, struggling to hide her disappointment.

"Still –"

"I suspect this is a good time to mention that I am a spy," Severus said.

Neville regarded him coldly. He set the Sorting Hat on the bed and took his sword back from Luna. "We're aware."

"For Dumbledore," Severus clarified.

I snorted. "You don't actually expect us to believe that?"

Ginevra chirped, "You hate Harry, even though he's the Chosen One and great at Potions and a genius and so, so handsome."

Not wanting to encourage Ginevra's lunacy, I said, "You're a terrible teacher."

"You helped You-Know-Who take over the school," Hermione said.

"You're best friends with Sirius Black." I leaned out of biting range as Snape snarled at that suggestion.

Lavender's head crept upwards to settle on Neville's shoulder. "You made me cry every day in Second Year!"

"…Me too," Neville said.

"So sensitive!" she squealed, throwing her hands around his neck in a crushing hug.

Hermione sent them a disapproving look and Ron hastily averted his eyes. He said, "You haven't told the Order of the Phoenix anything since Dumbledore died, and I know because my family pretty much is the Order now."

I casually accioed the Sorting Hat, stuffing it into my trunk. "Finally, you're a werewolf."

"Not all werewolves are Death Eaters," Ron said.

"Of course they are."

I paused, quite certain that I hadn't spoken.

Voldemort strode towards us, backed by several of his most loyal followers. More Death Eaters were pouring through the passageway by the moment.

Right. The girl on guard duty had followed us inside and was currently giving Sirius Black, Voldemort's right-hand man, a friendly wave. Meanwhile, Fenrir Greyback bared his teeth at Ron in some approximation of a smile, Lucius anxiously tousled his hair at the thought of himself and his clone in such a filthy place, and several Death Eaters were gesturing frantically at Neville.

Voldemort beamed, as if ready to get his picture taken. "Your plan was brilliant. After all, he who commands the Headmaster commands the school. Unfortunately for you, Severus has always been my most loyal servant."

With a flick of the Dark Lord's hand, the ropes fell and Severus's wand snapped into its owner's hand. The man then leapt from the chair and threw a spell at one of his fellow Death Eaters.

Voldemort gaped. "You couldn't possibly have turned him already!"

"Of course not," Severus drawled. "They're idiots. I betrayed you decades ago."

Another slash of his wand sent a masked figure careening into the crowd. Voldemort raised his own wand, sneering. "I always knew you would betray me, one day. Crucio."

Hagrid lumbered forward to shield Severus with his enormous, half-Giant body.

"Severus, Hagrid, Bellatrix, Rodolphus and Rabastan…who's next, Sirius Black?" Voldemort laughed derisively. To be fair, the notion was completely ridiculous.

To our shock, Black leapt into the battle. "I was never one of you! You only thought that because you were idiots. I don't even have the Dark Mark."

"That was a sign of my trust!"

Voldemort was overwhelmed and heartbroken. He coped with these feelings, like all others, through murder. It was about that time that the werewolves rebelled and the battle began in earnest.

Before I could show off my own impressive skills, Hermione pulled me under the invisibility cloak with Ron and the trunk. I frowned. "What was that about?"

"We can't just fight Voldemort on his own footing," she hissed.

I said, "I could take him."

"We need a plan," she insisted.

"Bloody hell," Ron said, staring out at the battlefield. "Did Neville just take out that guy's heart?"

I smirked. "It's nice to see he's found a use for his wand."

He shook his head, freckles dark against his ghostly face. "I didn't even know they were that sharp."

I leaned in to whisper, "They aren't."

Hermione peered into my trunk. "We need to isolate him from his followers…"

"Oh, not again," Ginevra wailed as Fawkes descended from the ceiling to attack the Basilisk.

Hermione's lips pursed. "…and we still have to worry about keeping him immobile for the duration of the ritual."

"At least Luna's enjoying herself," I said as the blonde frolicked past the Malfoys, who were cowering in the corner - as they often do.

Ron nodded, wincing at the fate of the girl's newest victim.

"Honestly! Will you two pay attention? People are dying," Hermione snapped.

"Like Snape," I agreed.

"What? A-are you sure?" Hermione said. Oh, of course. Talking is a huge problem unless she's the one who wants to do it. Then it's fine.

Severus threw his hands into the air as he lurched to the stone floor. "YOU HAVE MURDERED ME!"

"Yeah, pretty sure," I said.

"A CURSE UPON YOU ALL!"

Ron laughed. "That's Snape alright."

"ESPECIALLY YOU, BLACK!"

"A death curse. That's some pretty nasty blood magic. I wouldn't want to be them," I said.

Hermione let out a shaky breath. "Harry, you have some of Voldemort's memories. Surely you know something."

"Wait, what? Why do you think that?" I said.

"I figured it out in Fourth Year, and, frankly, I'm embarrassed it took me that long," Hermione said, "It's frightfully obvious."

Ron seemed completely lost, so Hermione said, "Harry remembers some of the things from Voldemort's life due to their weird connection. That's why he knows so much magic and has so many biases."

"Right, yes," I said weakly. "That's exactly what happened. I didn't tell you because I didn't want you to think I was a dirty Slytherin."

"I would never think that, Harry," Ron said.

"Not the time," Hermione said. "Does Voldemort have any weaknesses?"

My answer was immediate. "No. He's perfect."

Hermione flinched at this disheartening news. "Can we trick him?"

I thought about it for a time, over the sounds of battle and Fawkes' ineffectual yet enthusiastic pecks at the Basilisk's scales. "Yes. I think we can."

"Oh, thank Merlin," Hermione sighed.

I turned to my best mate. "Ron, I'm going to need you to be the most Gryffindor you have been in your entire life."

A wry smile twisted Ron's lips. "I'm going to be bait again, aren't I?"

I shook my head. "No…more of a distraction."

The battlefield was red. Not with blood, but with the blinding light of a stunner.

The combatants froze, eyes wide as the light faded to reveal Ronald Weasley. He grinned and said, "Oy, Voldemort! Why don't you fight the real Chosen One?"

The Dark Lord was the first to break into action, unsurprising considering the quality of his present company. "That's ridiculous. No Weasleys were born during the end of July."

Ron said. "July's the seventh month of the Gregorian calendar. All real prophecies use the Roman one. I was born at the end of its seventh month. You'd know that, if you ever took Divination."

Voldemort frowned. "What about Harry Potter?"

"He doesn't fit the prophecy," Ron said. "The Chosen One has to be a sixth son. It says so in the part you didn't hear."

Voldemort's eyes narrowed, and his followers scuttled out of his way as he approached Ron. "I always suspected you Weasleys were up to something. Your family knew about this all along, didn't you? That's why they had so many children."

"Uh, yeah, 'course we did," Ron agreed.

"You've been preparing for this day, biding your time while using Potter as bait. How vicious of you…I don't suppose you'd be interested in joining the Death Eaters?"

"Nah. If being a Death Eater was any good, then all the other ones wouldn't have gone traitor," Ron said.

Voldemort scowled. "In that case, I'm going to kill you."

"Alright," Ron said. "We should probly set up some sorta shield or something. That way, nobody can get involved in our battle."

A swish of Voldemort's wand sent a shield shimmering darkly around them. This cut the two men off from the rest of the battlefield, who still watched in anxious silence. Only a handful of corpses shared their arena. Voldemort raised his wand.

Ron's face scrunched up in a Weasley fashion. "Aren't we supposed to bow first? Y'know, to help with our, uh…legends?"

Voldemort glanced at the crowd and said, "Yes, I suppose this would be a fitting addition to the legend of the Dark Lord Voldemort, politician, Weasley-slayer, and future, undisputed leader of the British Isles."

Ron grinned and began to bow.

Voldemort followed suit, maintaining eye contact the whole time and grasping his wand loosely in his hand. Until, of course, I accioed it.

He whirled around, not noticing the red beam until it slammed into his back. Eyes wide open, Lord Voldemort fell to the floor.

With a flick of my old, yew wand, I flung the invisibility cloak off to reveal the trunk, Hermione, and myself.

The frizzy-haired girl immediately rushed over to Ron, hugging him. I nudged Voldemort with my foot. "Ron, I need you over here immediately. This is the moment you've been training for your whole life."

My best mate came over, grinning. "Yeah?"

I pointed emphatically with my wands. "If he moves, I need you to stun him, and, if he doesn't move, then he's probably trying to trick you and you should stun him anyway."

Ron nodded gravely, casting a stunner to demonstrate his understanding. With that taken care of, I turned to the crowd. "Lord Voldemort has been defeated by me, Harry Potter."

The Death Eaters' uneasy murmurs mingled with the Light siders' cheers. "Anyone who keeps fighting on his behalf shall be crushed –"

Several Death Eaters fled towards the exit. I twirled my wands and waited for them to leave. "Good! I presume that you remaining few are his most loyal followers, so we don't need to feel bad about unleashing the really horrible spells…and there goes the rest of them."

Sirius Black let out a whoop of joy, tossing a curse at their backs. I shivered. Truly, he knew no loyalty. Hermione raised a hand for silence. "We have everything under control, so you can all get rest or medical treatment –"

"Or drunk," I added. Delighted yells and laughter rung out across the crowd.

Ron threw another stunner at Voldemort. "And somebody should probly call the Aurors."

"We, meanwhile, will be killing Voldemort with a secret technique left by Albus Dumbledore, the Lightest of Light wizards," I said.

I tossed my old wand into my left hand and, raising both arms heavenward, released plumes of red smoke. I was only casting with my Holly wand, but it was all very stylish. The smoke pushed against the shield, hiding us from the crowd.

Hermione added a Silencing Charm, and turned to me, "How precisely do we do this ritual, then?"

I snatched the locket from the Dark Lord's neck and rifled through the trunk, pulling out my Horcruxes and the still inactivated Sorting Hat. Nagini slithered off my arm, first, settling a foot away from Voldemort's head. Next, I set the other items in a circle around him. A slash of my wand cut Voldemort's arm, and a stream of blood twirled out.

Ron gaped. "Is that blood magic?"

"Just like my mother used," I said. "The ritual requires the caster's blood, but, because of Voldemort's resurrection ritual, we literally have the same blood. Or metaphorically have the same blood. Either way, I don't have to bleed."

Hermione pursed her lips. "That seems highly irresponsible."

"You're hardly one to talk, Miss Granger," a familiar voice drawled.

Our heads snapped to the corner where Severus Snape disapprovingly regarded the smoky ceiling. Hermione said, "Professor?!"

"No one bothered to check if I was dead or merely wounded. How touching."

"To be fair, you did say you were dead," I pointed out.

Hermione hurried over, making a fuss over his injuries to distract from her earlier apathy.

Severus's dark eyes flicked to the thoroughly stunned Voldemort as Ron hit the body with another spell. "It appears that, despite your bumbling idiocy and outrageous arrogance, you have successfully defeated the Dark Lord."

Hermione said, "Not yet, Professor. We still need a few minutes."

Severus inclined his head. "Fifty points to Slytherin."

"I'm rooting for Gryffindor now," I said.

"I don't care, Potter."

"…I'm also not technically a student."

His eyes were dull and without emotion, as they always are. "I still don't care."

"We kill You-Know-Who and our reward is Slytherin winning the Cup," Ron said. "It's Snape alright."

Hermione tossed a stinging hex at Ron, and Severus said, "Twenty points for your cheek."

I paused, mulling over the redhead's words. "A reward would be nice…Snape, you're still the headmaster, right?"

Severus narrowed his eyes at me. "Presumably."

I beamed. "Can I be the Defense Against the Dark Arts Professor?"

Severus said, "Potter, I spent the last year as a spy under a murderous regime, despised by all my true allies, and running a school where the students were in constant warfare with half the staff. Despite all of that, the lack of your presence has made this the most pleasant year I've had in some time. I hoped that I could spend the rest of my life pretending you didn't exist."

"So, that's a 'no,' then."

Severus stared at me silently. I stood there, wands heavy in my hands.

"Uh, mate, shouldn't we be getting rid of Voldemort?" Ron asked, casually stunning him.

"I suppose," I said morosely. "Once I get over my disappointment."

Severus scowled. "…Potter, are you holding the Wizarding World hostage to get a job?"

Hermione clucked disapprovingly.

I shook my head. "No, but I may be too upset to do the ritual, right now, and who knows what sort of daring escape Voldemort might pull while we wait."

Ron punctuated my point with a jet of red light.

"Fine, you're hired."

Colorful sparks shot gaily from my wands. "Really?"

Severus consoled himself with a muttered, "You'll be gone in a year, anyway."

"Harry, would you please do something about the genocidal maniac on the floor?" Hermione said, her natural selfishness winning out yet again.

I turned back to the ritual with a smile. A flick of my wand painted a bloody heptagon on the floor. Its points lay at myself, Nagini, Ravenclaw's Diadem, Huffepuff's Cup, Slytherin's Locket, the Gaunt ring, and the Sorting Hat.

"This ends the way it began: Avada Kedavra!"

Voldemort's soul was knocked from his body but contained in the heptagon by the bloody markings.

The ritual was conceptually simple. At each point of the heptagon lay a portion of Voldemort's soul, barring one: The Sorting Hat. To balance this out, the soul would naturally gravitate towards the empty container, forming a new Horcrux with Voldemort's death serving as the necessary sacrifice.

The bloody lines vanished as the soul settled into its new home, and the ritual's magic dispersed into the air, canceling the shield around us. Everyone peered through the smoke, not noticing as I tossed my Horcruxes inside the trunk.

At that moment, Fawkes landed upon my shoulder. He let out a shriek, directly into my ear, and burst into flames.

Later, many would describe this as a beautiful scene, symbolizing the rebirth of Wizarding Britain after Lord Voldemort's demise.

I don't know why. Fawkes does this every couple of years, and the second-degree burns he left were hardly inspirational.

Personally, I believe he did it out of spite.

A/N: Luna's Parseltongue name roughly translates to "Climbing Egg." You see, snakes rarely look up, and, when they do, they do not care.

The Epilogue is still to come, and then there'll also be an omake chapter.